[
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "1",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements most accurately describes the practice of medicine in Greece from 800 BC to 300 BC?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Greek culture stressed natural causes for disease, a patient-centered approach, and the necessity of accurate observations and record keeping.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Greek culture borrowed medical practices from the countries it conquered, and physicians were often slaves.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Major and minor surgery, children's diseases, and diseases of the nervous and urinary systems were described in Greek culture.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Medicine men (known first as shamans and later as priests) were responsible for curing ills of body and mind.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Hippocrates, born about 400 BC, was a Greek citizen who became known as the Father of Modern Medicine. He emphasized natural causes for disease, a patient-centered approach, and the necessity of accurate observations and record keeping. These priorities influenced the practice of medicine both in Greece and beyond. Persia was known to utilize slaves as physicians, and Rome borrowed medical practices from the countries it conquered. Ancient India emphasized hygiene and prevention of sickness and described major and minor surgery, children's diseases, and diseases of the nervous and urinary systems. Medicine men were characteristic of the Mayan and Aztec civilizations."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "2",
        "Question": "Florence Nightingale fostered the development of nursing as a profession. What was the basis of her nursing theory?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The nurse's role is to assist individuals (sick or well) to carry out those activities that they would perform unaided if they had the necessary strength, will, or knowledge.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The goal of nursing is to put the patient in the best condition for nature to act upon him, primarily by altering the environment.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The focus of nursing is the spiritual subjective aspects of both the nurse and the patient and the “caring moment” relating to the time when the nurse and the patient first come together.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The focus of nursing is the care of human beings who are viewed as open systems in constant interaction with their environments.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Florence Nightingale, in her Notes on Nursing: What It Is and What It Is Not, described the nurse's role as one that would “put the patient in the best condition for nature to act upon him” (Nightingale, 1954, p. 133), a definition that often is quoted today. This action was prioritized over physically assisting the patient. Watson emphasized the spiritual subjective aspects of the nurse and the patient, and the “open systems” concept is central to King's theory of nursing."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "3",
        "Question": "Which one of the following statements accurately describes an element of the process of providing a definition of nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Researchers can pinpoint the period in history when nursing first evolved.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nurses agree on a single definition of nursing, partly because of the history of nursing.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  There is an obvious distinction between nursing and medicine.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nursing theorists developed definitions of nursing consistent with their conceptual frameworks.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  As nursing has grown into a true profession, many nursing theorists have developed definitions of nursing consistent with their conceptual frameworks; these frameworks provide the foundation for any given definition of nursing. The historical emergence of nursing did not take place at one particular time, and there are multiple definitions of nursing. While nursing and medicine indeed differ, the distinctions between the two professions are not always clear."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "4",
        "Question": "A nurse wishes to document nursing actions using a standardized language. Which of the following systems might the nurse use?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  NANDA International (NANDA-I)",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nursing Outcomes Classification (NOC)",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Minimum Data Set for Nursing Home Resident Assessment and Care Screening (MDS)",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nursing Interventions Classification (NIC)",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Started in 1996 at the University of Iowa, the Nursing Interventions Classification (NIC) is a comprehensive, standardized language that describes actions that nurses perform in all settings and in all specialties and includes both physiologic and psychosocial interventions. NANDA and NOC provide standardized language for nursing diagnoses and outcomes. The MDS is an assessment tool specific to long-term care settings."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "5",
        "Question": "An RN who practices in a community clinic recognizes the need for a standardized classification and documentation system. Which of the following systems of nursing care classification and documentation would best fit the RN's needs?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  NANDA International (NANDA-I)",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nursing Outcomes Classification (NOC)",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The Omaha System",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Patient Care Data Set (PCDS)",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The Omaha System is a research-based comprehensive practice documentation standardized taxonomy designed to document client care from admission to discharge. It was designed as a three-part, comprehensive yet brief approach to documentation and information management for multidisciplinary healthcare professionals who practice in community settings. NANDA and NOC provide frameworks only for nursing diagnoses and outcomes, while the PCDS is specific to hospital settings."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "6",
        "Question": "The number and size of nursing schools in the United States grew significantly in the years of the early 20th century. Which of the following characteristics was emphasized in these schools?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A thorough knowledge of anatomy, physiology, and epidemiology",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Critical thinking, assertiveness, and autonomy",
        "Choice 3": "C)  An understanding of the relationship among mind, body, and spirit",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Religious devotion and subservience to authority",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In early nursing schools, the nurse in training was expected to yield to her superiors and demonstrate the obedience characteristics of a good soldier with actions governed by the dedication to duty derived from religious devotion. These expectations superseded the importance of critical thinking, scientific knowledge, or the holistic nature of health."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "7",
        "Question": "Florence Nightingale is acknowledged as one of the individuals who contributed most significantly to the development of nursing as a profession. What other phenomenon contributed most to this development?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Labor-saving technology that freed many women from working in the home",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The social recognition of the importance of public funding for the treatment of disease",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Increased understanding of the pathophysiology of illness and the importance of infection control",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The high mortality rates that existed during times of war",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The death and disease that accompanied conflicts such as the Crimean War and the Civil War provided the impetus for much of the development of the nursing profession. Nursing did not primarily grow out of the availability of a female workforce, public funding for health, or increased scientific knowledge."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "8",
        "Question": "Nurses have historically had difficulty identifying a single, comprehensive definition of nursing. What factor most accounts for this difficulty in agreeing on a definition for nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  It can be challenging to reconcile the theoretical and practical aspects of nursing.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nursing exists in the psychomotor (hands-on) domain rather than in the cognitive domain.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Compared with medicine, nursing has a relatively short history.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nurses have traditionally been reluctant to acknowledge the outcomes of their practice.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A major factor that has made it difficult to define nursing is that it is taught as encompassing both theoretic and practical aspects, but it is pursued (and continues to be defined) primarily through practice, until recently a little-studied area. Nursing spans psychomotor and cognitive domains, and it has a very long history. Nurses have often failed to document and publish the results of their practice, but there is no indication that nurses tended not to acknowledge their influence on health."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "9",
        "Question": "One of the challenges that nurses have faced in the past, and which continues to the present, is the need to distinguish the practice of nursing from that of medicine. Which of the following statements best conveys a defining characteristic of nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Education within a formal, credential-granting setting",
        "Choice 2": "B)  An emphasis on objective, rather than subjective, health assessment",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A holistic perspective on the health of individuals",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A recognition that health is not always attainable for all individuals",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Nursing is concerned with caring for the person from a holistic perspective in a variety of health-related situations. Both nursing and medicine are taught in formal educational settings, though these settings differ. Nursing does not denigrate subjective health assessment nor does it claim that health is unattainable for some individuals."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "10",
        "Question": "Society has sometimes questioned whether nursing can be considered to be a true profession and whether nurses can be considered to be professionals. What characteristic of nursing is among the characteristics that social scientists use to define a profession?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The median annual nursing wage is greater than $45,000.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nurses use the scientific method to enhance their body of knowledge.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Nurses can be held legally accountable for their actions.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nursing has a demonstrated commitment to the well-being of the public.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Social scientists have identified seven criteria for a profession, including the use of the scientific method to enhance knowledge. Earnings and commitment to the public are not among the defining characteristics of a profession. Autonomy and accountability are criteria that are used to define a profession, but legal accountability for actions is not restricted to professionals."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "11",
        "Question": "Among the traditions that exist in nursing education is a “passing of the lamp” ceremony that is sometimes conducted during graduation. This ceremony communicates",
        "Choice 1": "A)  the “light” that nursing provides in communities and society.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  an acknowledgment of the contributions made by important nurses in history.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  the continuity of care from practicing nurses to newly graduated nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  the need to continually build the nurse's base of knowledge.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Some schools use the tradition of a “passing of the lamp.” A representative of the graduating class hands a lamp to a representative of the next graduating class, thus reinforcing the concept of the continual caring represented in nursing. This ceremony does not primarily emphasize the “light” of the profession, the contribution of nurses in history (though the lamp symbolizes the lamp carried by Florence Nightingale), or the need to add to existing knowledge."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "12",
        "Question": "A nurse who provides care on a medical unit at a community hospital is concerned about negative portrayals of nurses in the media. Why should this nurse be concerned with the image of nurses and nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A negative image of nursing can dissuade potential nurses from entering the profession.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A negative image of nursing reduces patients' adherence to treatment regimens.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A negative image of nursing interferes with professional accountability in hospital settings.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A negative image of nursing reduces the development of nursing knowledge.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Negative attitudes about nursing may discourage many capable prospective nurses, who will choose another career that offers greater appeal in stature, status, and salary. The image of nursing is not noted to influence patient adherence to treatment or accountability. A negative image may indirectly limit nursing knowledge through reduced funding for research, but this phenomenon is less pronounced than the effect on potential nurses."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "13",
        "Question": "Megan, a 21-year-old junior college student, has been frustrated by her unsuccessful attempts to gain entry to the nursing program at the local university despite her strong academic record and work experience. Which of the following factors has most contributed to the limited number of seats available in many nursing programs?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Technological developments that have decreased the projected need for nurses",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The tendency of practicing nurses to delay retirement until after the age of 65 years",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The high cost to educational institutions of providing nursing education",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The negative image of nursing in the media and popular culture",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A factor affecting the nursing supply is the limited number of spaces in nursing programs. Because nursing education is costly, many educational institutions have not been able to increase the size of their programs in the past decade. This trend is not attributable to technological change, increased length of service, or the negative image of nursing."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "14",
        "Question": "Mrs. Jimenez is a 28-year-old pregnant woman who is in labor. Due to the fact that her labor was progressing very slowly, she was started on an infusion of oxytocin, a drug used to increase the progression of her labor. In the planning of Mrs. Jimenez's care, the nurse has documented a “Risk of Fluid Volume Excess” in light of this common adverse effect of oxytocin. The nurse has demonstrated the use of what nursing classification system?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The Minimum Data Set (MDS)",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nursing Outcomes Classification (NOC)",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Nursing Interventions Classification (NIC)",
        "Choice 4": "D)  NANDA International (NANDA-I)",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  “Risk of Fluid Volume Excess” is an example of a nursing diagnosis, which is the focus of NANDA-I. This does not denote an intervention or desired outcome. The MDS is an assessment tool specific to long-term care settings."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "15",
        "Question": "During the years of the 20th century, there was exponential growth in the number and quality of research studies that were conducted about nurses and nursing. What factor provided the original motivation for these studies?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The entry of larger number of men into nursing schools and the nursing profession",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A desire to lessen the knowledge gap between nurses and physicians",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The low quality of nursing schools and nursing graduates",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Allocation of federal and state funding for nursing research",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In the early 20th century, nurses, doctors, friends, and critics of nursing became concerned that the preparation being offered was inadequate. Before the problem could be corrected, it was necessary to learn more about the programs and how nurses were being used in the employment market. To accomplish this, studies about nursing and nurses were initiated. These studies did not primarily result from increased funding opportunities, the entry of men into the profession, or the knowledge gap between doctors and nurses."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "16",
        "Question": "Several national organizations have addressed the issue of adverse events in healthcare settings. The National Quality Forum (NQF) of 2002 included which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A list of serious reportable events that was aimed at increasing public accountability",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A cross reference of standards for nursing care with the most common adverse events in healthcare",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A list of aims for improving the overall quality of the American healthcare system",
        "Choice 4": "D)  An algorithm for responding appropriately to safety violations in healthcare settings",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In 2002, The National Quality Forum (NQF) created and endorsed a list of serious reportable events (SREs)—also referred to as adverse or “never events”—to increase public accountability and consumer access to critical information about healthcare performance. This did not encompass standards for nursing care, appropriate responses to specific adverse events, or a list of general aims for the healthcare system."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Multiple Selection2.  A nurse is aware that sentinel events that occur in the care setting must be followed up in a timely and thorough way. Which of the following occurrences would be considered a sentinel event? (Select all that apply.)",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A nurse's shift is cancelled at short notice.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A patient accesses the medication chart and takes a medication.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The family member of a patient physically threatens a nurse.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A physician makes sexually inappropriate comments to a nurse.",
        "Choice 5": "E)  A nurse places a patient on a bedpan despite the fact that the patient can ambulate with assistance.",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "2, 3, 4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Sentinel events encompass a wide variety of events that threaten the safety of patients, families, and care providers. Examples include patient access to secured drug storage and inappropriate or threatening conduct. Late cancellation of a shift would be unlikely to constitute a sentinel event. Substandard care, such as the inappropriate use of a bedpan, requires correction but would not be considered a sentinel event.",
        "Test Number": "17"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "18",
        "Question": "One of the safe practices identified by the National Quality Forum (NQF) is to match healthcare needs with service delivery capability. This practice is demonstrated by",
        "Choice 1": "A)  matching the health status of a community with the specific mandate of the local hospital.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  conducting high-risk procedures in hospitals that perform a large numbers of the same procedure.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  encouraging Americans to seek care in healthcare institutions that have the fewest number of adverse events.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  ensuring that hospitals are equipped and staffed to provide neither too much nor too little care.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A practice identified by the NQF was to match healthcare needs with service delivery capability. Research has consistently demonstrated that patients undergoing certain high-risk procedures have lower-than-expected mortality rates in hospitals that perform large numbers of those procedures, and conversely, higher-than-expected mortality in institutions that perform low volumes of those procedures."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "19",
        "Question": "The nursing leadership in the local hospital has recognized the need to minimize the number of sentinel events that occur in the hospital by implementing a number of practice improvements. These nurse leaders should recognize that the largest proportion of sentinel events involve which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Lapses in communication",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Violence",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Violations of care providers' scopes of practice",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Gaps in education and training",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  It has been estimated that communication errors are factors in more than 70% of sentinel events."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "20",
        "Question": "The Joint Commission has taken action to encourage healthcare organizations to reduce the incidence and impact of errors. How has the Joint Commission acted to facilitate these improvements in care?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  By delineating the scope of practice for registered nurses and practical (vocational) nurses",
        "Choice 2": "B)  By providing a forum for patients to report errors and substandard care",
        "Choice 3": "C)  By funding safety education in medical schools and nursing schools",
        "Choice 4": "D)  By standardizing the measures by which safety in hospitals is gauged",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In 2004, the Joint Commission and the Centers for Medicare & Medicaid Services (CMS) began working together to align measures common to both organizations. These standardized common measures, called “Hospital Quality Measures,” are integral to improving the quality of care provided to hospital patients and bringing value to stakeholders by focusing on the actual results of care. The Joint Commission has not directly addressed the scope of nursing practice, the healthcare education, or the reporting process."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "21",
        "Question": "A senior nurse on a medical unit is aware of the role that she can play in establishing a culture of safety on the unit. What characteristic is most important to care settings that possess a culture of safety?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Anticoagulants, opioids, and insulin are cosigned by two nurses.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Physicians' orders are entered into a computerized system rather than a handwritten section of patients' charts.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Nurses feel that they can report errors, near misses, and adverse events without being punished or denounced.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Direct patient care is provided by ADN and baccalaureate nurses rather than practical (vocational) nurses.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A central attribute of a culture of safety is the existence of trust and mutual respect. This encourages healthcare providers to report errors, near misses, and other adverse events without fear of retribution. Cosigning medications and eliminating handwritten orders are specific measures that may augment safety, but they are not characteristics of a culture of safety. Excluding PNs from care is not necessary to ensure safety."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "22",
        "Question": "A county hospital has recently implemented a practice change in which the SBAR technique is now used to communicate between nurses and physicians. The nurse has contacted an elderly patient's physician to report the patient's adventitious lung sounds and decreased oxygen saturation. Which of the following statements best exemplifies the “R” component of the SBAR tool?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  “Mr. Young has a do-not-resuscitate order.”",
        "Choice 2": "B)  “Mr. Young's oxygen saturation is 86% on oxygen at 3 liters per minute by nasal prongs.”",
        "Choice 3": "C)  “Mr. Young was admitted on January 14 with a diagnosis of failure to thrive.”",
        "Choice 4": "D)  “I think that we should decrease Mr. Young's IV rate.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The SBAR tool consists of four components: situation (S), background (B), assessment (A), and recommendation (R). A suggested course of action, such as reducing a patient's IV rate, is an example of a recommendation. A patient's code status and original diagnosis are examples of background and oxygen levels are assessment findings."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "23",
        "Question": "A busy operating room has begun using time outs in an effort to reduce errors and promote patient safety. What action will the care team perform during a time out?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Systematically teaching the patient about the risks of surgery while the patient is still in the preoperation area",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Gathering each member of the surgical team to acknowledge and confirm that the correct surgery will be performed on the correct patient",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Pausing to review the patient's diagnosis and the indications for surgery",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Completing a checklist that reviews the major areas for preoperative assessment and which contains the patient's consent for the procedure",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  All relevant members of the team actively communicate during the time-out and agree, at a minimum, that the patient identity is correct as is the site and the procedure to be done. Time outs do not normally involve preoperative teaching, assessment, or review of the patient's diagnosis."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "24",
        "Question": "“Failure to rescue” has been defined as “deaths per 1,000 patients having developed specified complications of care during hospitalization” (AHRQ, 2007). A hospital that wishes to reduce the rate of failure to rescue should prioritize what measure?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Encouraging nurses to spend a greater amount of time at the bedside.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Implementing mandatory continuing education programs.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Improving the communication between members of different health disciplines.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Reducing distractions to nurses while they are providing care.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Failure to rescue has been tied to the amount of time that the nurse spends at the bedside with incidence of failure to rescue decreasing when nurses spend more time at the bedside and less on other activities. Being present at the bedside influences failure to rescue more than continuing education, improving communication, or reducing distractions, even though each of these measures has the potential to improve safety."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "25",
        "Question": "Alana is a registered nurse with an ADN degree who floats between several different medical and surgical units of a hospital. Today was Alana's fifth 12-hour shift in a row and she committed a medication error while providing care for one of the four patients to whom she was assigned. What factor is most likely to have contributed to this adverse event?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The fact that Alana has an ADN degree",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The fact that Alana floats between several units",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The fact that Alana was working overtime",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The fact that Alana was responsible for four patients",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  While it is not possible to establish causative factors without knowing more details of this situation, there is known to be a close correlation between overtime and adverse events. Adverse events are not typically linked to having an ADN degree or providing care for four patients. Unfamiliarity with a unit is a safety risk, but overtime is a more likely cause of an error."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "26",
        "Question": "A nurse who provides care in a long-term care facility is charged with improving the safety of residents. Which of the following measures has the greatest potential to reduce the incidence of injuring among residents?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A comprehensive falls prevention program",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A program aimed at eliminating resident-to-resident violence",
        "Choice 3": "C)  An automated medication administration system",
        "Choice 4": "D)  An algorithm that guides the delegation of tasks among the care team",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Falls are a common cause of morbidity and the leading cause of nonfatal injuries and trauma-related hospitalizations in the United States. Nearly half of all residents in nursing homes fall each year, with many sustaining fractures. As a result, a falls prevention program is more likely to be of benefit than a violence-prevention program, automated medication administration, or a delegation tool."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "27",
        "Question": "A nurse is transcribing a physician's new drug order on to a patient's medication administration record. In light of the potential for drug errors, how should the nurse best record the drug order?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Digoxin 0.125 mg PO daily",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Digoxin .125 mg PO daily",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Digoxin 0.1250 mg PO daily",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Digoxin .1250 mg PO daily",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The Institute for Safe Medication Practices requires that leading zeros before the decimal point always be included and trailing zeros after a decimal point never be used."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "28",
        "Question": "A hospital has recently implemented a barcode point of care (BPOC) system. This system will require the nurse to",
        "Choice 1": "A)  scan barcodes on patients' charts and their wristbands before administering drugs.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  cross-check physicians' orders and patients' medication administration records.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  scan patient wristbands and medication containers prior to medication administration.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  provide an electronic record of his or her nursing activities over the course of a shift.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  BPOC systems cross-check bar codes printed on patient wristbands, nurse identification badges, and medication labels. The system matches the provider's orders with the patient identification and verifies the “six rights” of medication safety by comparing the bar code on medications with the prescribed medications. Patients' medical charts are not normally scanned and BPOC do not provide a record of most aspects of nursing care. Comparing physicians' orders to MARs is not an activity that is limited to BPOC systems."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "29",
        "Question": "A nurse is aware that the incidence of medication errors at the hospital is much higher than it should be and that it is possible to reduce this incidence. Which of the following measures carries the greatest potential to reduce medication errors?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Implementing team nursing, whereby every medication is administered by a pair of nurses",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Attaching physicians' orders to medication administration records (MARs)",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Keeping medication administration records (MARs) at the patients' bedsides",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Taking action to reduce distractions to nurses while they are administering medications",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  One of the causes of errors most frequently reported by nurses is that of interruptions while administering medications. Team nursing, attaching MARs to orders, and keeping MARs at patient bedsides are not measures that have been widely proposed or that have been shown to reduce medication errors."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "30",
        "Question": "A nurse who works in a busy, university hospital is committed to improving patient safety at the hospital. In order to meet this goal, what action should the nurse prioritize?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Advocating for continuing education programs and funding of nurse educators",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Encouraging patients to be active participants in their care by communicating their expectations to caregivers",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Critically examining systems and processes at the hospital with the aim of suggesting improvements",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Teaching unlicensed care personnel about safety in the hospital setting",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In order to promote a systematic culture of safety, nurses need to look at systems and processes to identify areas that need to be studied and changed to be safer. This broad and holistic approach to safety likely has a greater potential to effect change than the other cited efforts that have more narrow focuses."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: DMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 11: The Nursing Profession and the Community1.  A goal of community nursing is to provide primary prevention from disease. Which of the following nursing actions reflect this goal?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A nurse creates a pamphlet discussing heart-healthy foods and distributes it in the neighborhood community center.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A nurse starts an intravenous line on a dehydrated baby who has been brought to the emergency department.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A nurse performs range-of-motion exercises for a patient in traction.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A nurse repositions an elderly patient confined to a wheelchair to avoid the formation of pressure ulcers.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Primary prevention involves the efforts to prevent disease from ever occurring. Primary prevention can be aimed at stopping the cause of disease. Generalized efforts to educate people regarding healthy diets are aimed at this type of primary prevention. Tertiary prevention focuses on preventing long-term disability and restoring functional capacity, as exemplified by repositioning an immobile patient, rehydrating a patient, or assisting with exercises.",
        "Test Number": "31"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "32",
        "Question": "A nurse decides to pursue a career in community-based nursing. Which of the following statements represents the environment in which the nurse will be working?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Community-based nursing is limited to work in public clinics, schools, and industry.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The key to community-based settings is that the nurse is in charge.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The nurse serves as an educator, guide, and resource person and determines the action taken by the client.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Care in the community is cost-effective.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Care in the community is cost-effective and often more acceptable to the client because it causes less disruption in life. It takes place in a wide variety of settings and involves the nurse entering into a collaborative relationship with clients."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "33",
        "Question": "The movement of a client from acute care to a long-term nursing care facility involves planning to provide continuity of care. What is the term for this type of planning?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Discharge planning",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Comprehensive planning",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Ongoing planning",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Transition planning",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Transitions are the movement of the patient from one care environment to another. Transition planning refers to the planning process that takes place to assure that the patient's well-being is maintained throughout the time of transition. Organizing this transition from one care setting to another is not termed discharge planning, comprehensive planning, or ongoing planning."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "34",
        "Question": "A nurse is called into work to perform triage in the aftermath of an earthquake. Which of the following are the expected responsibilities of this nurse?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Set up and monitor IV lines.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Prepare the emergency room for multiple victims.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Screen victims to prioritize treatment.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Check available blood products and assist with transfusions.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Triage involves the initial screening of victims for the purpose of prioritizing treatment and making the most effective and efficient use of both human and material resources. The other noted tasks are within the scope of disaster nursing but are not triage activities."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "35",
        "Question": "A client asks a nurse for help in obtaining an alternative healthcare provider. Which of the following is an accurate fact regarding alternative care that the nurse should share with this client?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Most alternative healthcare practitioners do not have education-based credentials to practice their medicine.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Alternative providers are not usually included in the federal HIPAA legislation that mandates confidentiality in conventional healthcare settings.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The cost of alternative therapy is never covered by insurance carriers or healthcare plans.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  It is easy to find accurate safety and efficacy data for alternative medicine on the Internet.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Alternative providers are not normally included in the federal Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 legislation that mandates confidentiality in conventional healthcare settings. Alternative practitioners do not necessarily lack credentials. Accurate online information can be difficult to find and costs for treatment may be covered by some insurance plans."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "36",
        "Question": "There is an increasing trend for nursing care to move from the hospital setting into the community. Nurses who are to provide excellent care in a community setting should prioritize which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Integrating culture and family into the planning and delivery of care",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Becoming more assertive in client education and the planning of client care",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Encouraging clients to limit their interactions with physicians",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Teaching clients to replace biomedical interventions with complementary therapies",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The move to community care heightens the importance of family-centered, culturally-competent nursing. Community nursing does not necessarily require that a nurse become more assertive with client. It would be simplistic, and in most cases inappropriate, to guide clients to replace biomedical interventions or avoid doctors."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "37",
        "Question": "In spite of the important role that hospitals play in American healthcare, there is growing importance of community-based healthcare and community-based nursing. Which of the following statements best conveys a central aspect of the philosophy of community care?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The client is in charge of his or her health and healthcare in the community.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nurses maximize their scope of practice in noninstitutional settings.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Community settings allow for the greatest number and variety of treatment options.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The nurse becomes the key member of the healthcare team in a community setting.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A central premise of community healthcare is the fact that patients/clients are in charge. The move toward community care is not motivated by an increased role for nurses. There are a greater number of treatment options in hospitals than in the community, but this fact does not negate the importance of community care."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "38",
        "Question": "Mr. Hammond is a 70-year-old man with a diagnosis of type 1 diabetes who developed a diabetic foot ulcer earlier this year. He has recently been discharged from the hospital and now requires regular wound care. Karen is a community health nurse who provides wound care for Mr. Hammond twice weekly. Which of Karen's actions is most likely to empower Mr. Hammond?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Encourage Mr. Hammond to acknowledge his contribution to the development of his wound.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Provide information to Mr. Hammond that matches his expressed needs.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Encourage Mr. Hammond to involve members of his family in his care.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Delegate wound care to Mr. Hammond and reduce the frequency of her visits.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Client empowerment is often fostered by assessing and meeting a client's need for information. Encouraging an acknowledgement of the client's contribution to his or her current health state is beneficial in many circumstances, but it less likely to make the client feel empowered. Similarly, family involvement can be beneficial but does not directly foster empowerment. Empowerment does not necessarily mean that the nurse does less and the client performs his or her own care; delegation may not be appropriate."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "39",
        "Question": "An elderly female client who resides in the community tends to defer decisions regarding her care to her eldest son. How should the community health nurse respond to the client's reluctance to make independent decisions?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Discuss this observation with the client and her son in an open manner and explore alternatives.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Organize care so that it takes place at times when the son is not present in the home.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Accommodate this aspect of the client's family dynamics when planning and carrying out care.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Teach the client assertiveness skills that she can apply in her interactions with her son.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The nurse should respect the client's desire to organize her care in the way that she prefers. It is not the responsibility of the nurse to reorganize or overcome this family's dynamics."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "40",
        "Question": "A client with a long-standing diagnosis of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD) has been enrolled in a disease management program. Which of the following activities will be prioritized in this program?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Providing comprehensive and evidence-based care of the client's COPD",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Creating collaborative relationships between the client and the care team",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Ensuring that the client qualifies for Medicare and Medicaid",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Liaising between the client and his health maintenance organization (HMO)",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Disease management focuses on providing the best evidence-based care for an individual with a specific chronic illness. This does not necessitate enrollment in an HMO, Medicare, or Medicaid. Collaborative relationships facilitate effective disease management but this is a means to the end of positive health outcomes rather than an end in itself."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "41",
        "Question": "One of the expressed goals of Healthy People 2020 is to achieve health equity and eliminate disparities. What health indicator can most accurately gauge whether this goal is being achieved?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Environmental quality",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Injury and violence",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Mental health",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Access to healthcare services",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Health equity is achieved when all Americans have equitable access to health services and there a fewer disparities in health access and health outcomes. Environmental quality, mental health and injury, and violence are important health indicators but these are less directly indicative of health equity and the elimination of disparities."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "42",
        "Question": "Nurses have the potential to positively impact the health of communities. Which of the following actions is most likely to improve the health of a community?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Publicizing the consequences of unhealthy lifestyles",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Advocating politically for laws and policies that foster community health",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Ensuring that nurses are practicing to the full extent of their scope of practice",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Providing nursing care to individuals who are not patients or clients",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  One important role of nurses in the promotion of healthy communities is as a supporter and advocate for political measures that would improve the health of the community. Publicizing negative health outcomes is appropriate in some contexts but this is likely less effective than promoting broad change politically. It is not normally appropriate to provide nursing care for individuals who are not patients or clients. Practicing to the full extent of one's scope of practice is not likely to impact community health in a direct way."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "43",
        "Question": "A nurse who provides care in an acute medical unit is aware of the importance of thorough discharge planning. The discharge planning process should begin",
        "Choice 1": "A)  once the patient has stabilized and is assured of positive outcomes.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  as soon as possible after the patient is admitted.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  once the patient has received a discharge order from his or her primary care provider.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  48 to 72 hours before the projected date of discharge.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  If possible, discharge planning should begin immediately upon admission."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "44",
        "Question": "A hospital patient has discussed with the nurse her use of visualization, biofeedback, and relaxation exercises in managing the chronic pain that results from her fibromyalgia. The nurse should recognize this patient's use of what category of complementary/alternative medicine (CAM)?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Biologically-based practices",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Manipulative practices",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Traditional indigenous medicine",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Mind-body medicine",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Examples of mind-body medicine include relaxation exercises, hypnosis, meditation, dance, prayer, visualization, and biofeedback. Biologically-based practices focus on food and dietary supplements while indigenous medicine applies the collective health knowledge of a particular culture. Manipulative practices involve the systematic application of touch."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "45",
        "Question": "A hospital patient who suffered a spinal cord injury has expressed an interest in exploring complementary/alternative therapies. The nurse should encourage the patient to begin this process by doing which of the following activities?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Asking practitioners of different therapies to provide lists of satisfied clients",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Asking the patient's primary care provider for permission to explore nonbiomedical treatments",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Finding reliable evidence regarding the safety and effectiveness of therapies",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Determining whether the patient's health insurance would cover the cost of alternative/complementary therapies",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The first step for an individual interested in complementary/alternative therapies is to assess the safety and effectiveness of the therapy in relationship to his or her own condition. This must precede the identification of specific practitioners or making financial arrangements. Communication with the care team is important, but the patient does not need to seek permission before exploring treatment alternatives."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: EMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 12: Initiating the Leadership and Management Role1.  Which of the following statements accurately reflects the nurse's responsibility for patient outcomes in today's workplace?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Tasks can be delegated, but accountability cannot be delegated.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  In today's environment, authority is more often given to management.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Most nurses who are accountable have the authority to affect the situation or effect change.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nurses are protected against legal action being taken in cases of malpractice in the hospital setting.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Tasks can be delegated, but accountability cannot; nurses who delegate tasks to assistive personnel continue to be accountable for that care. Many nurses experience frustration because they must be accountable for activities without the authority to affect the situation or create change. Authority is often shared in contemporary care settings. Nurses are legally responsible for the care they provide and are vulnerable to malpractice suits.",
        "Test Number": "46"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "47",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements accurately describes a basic guideline for using communication skillfully?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Managers should communicate how to perform a task even if it is something the subordinate has already learned.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Managers should not be afraid of making judgmental statements when dealing with a subordinate who has broken policy rules.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Managers should attempt to formulate a response to an individual who is still speaking to avoid awkward pauses in the conversation.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Managers should present direction as briefly as possible while still providing adequate data.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Effective managers state the necessary information as briefly as possible while still providing enough data to be clear. Interruptions, judgmental statements, and repeated explanations are characteristics of ineffective communication."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "48",
        "Question": "What is the primary objective of a performance appraisal?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Establish written documentation of incompetent behavior to facilitate dismissal",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Maintain and develop employee performance",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Establish criteria for accreditation standards",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Determine who receives pay raises",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The primary objectives of performance appraisal are to maintain or improve employee performance and to enhance the development of employees. They are not intended to be punitive measures or criteria for accreditation. Performance appraisals may have an influence on a nurse's pay but this is not their primary objective."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "49",
        "Question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of an effective performance evaluation system?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The appraisal system operates outside of the scope of administration.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Employees do not know in advance who will be evaluating them.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The final disposition of the appraisal is shared with the employee.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Evaluation concentrates on the personality of the employee.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A sound performance appraisal is shared with the employee who is the subject of the appraisal. The appraisal system should be strongly supported by administration and employees should be made aware of who will appraise them. An employee's personality should not be the focus for appraisal."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "50",
        "Question": "A nursing student finds that she has difficulty with procrastination. Which of the following is a recommended guideline to help this student manage her time?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Start working on a project for 10 minutes, and quit if tired or bored.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Schedule 2 or 3 days a week in which to concentrate her tasks.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Avoid spending the time it takes to make to-do lists.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Schedule down-time first and work second.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Kanarek (1996) provides five suggestions for dealing with procrastination. First, she suggests that you start working on a project for 10 minutes and quit if tired or bored. Work times should be prioritized carefully and spread out over time. The creation of lists is a useful tool."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "51",
        "Question": "A nursing leader has expressed a desire to foster the characteristics and behaviors associated with transformational leadership. Which of the following actions best demonstrates transformational leadership?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The leader makes it clear to employees that positive work performance will be rewarded and that sub-standard performance will bring consequences.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The leader ensures that decisions are based on the consensus of every employee.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The leader prioritizes the needs of each individual employee over the interests of the larger organization.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The leader takes action to build trust and relationships between him or her and the employees.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Leader activities associated with transformational leadership include creating a vision, building relationships, developing trust, and building self-esteem. An emphasis on rewards and punishment is associated with transactional leadership. Consensus is not appropriate for every decision, and the interests of individual employees cannot always supersede the interests of the organization."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "52",
        "Question": "The manager of a hospital unit has unilaterally decided on a change in the way that overtime is distributed among the nursing staff and has followed up this decision with an e-mail to all employees. What leadership style is exemplified by this manager?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Participative leadership",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Permissive leadership",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Laissez-faire leadership",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Autocratic leadership",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In autocratic or authoritarian leadership, the leader/manager makes the majority of the decisions without direct consultation with employees. Laissez-faire or permissive leadership occurs when little or no direction or guidance is provided. Participative leadership involves extensive input from employees."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "53",
        "Question": "Experts have identified a close relationship between the practice of transformational leadership and the empowerment of employees. What action should a nursing leader take to foster employee empowerment?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Have the performance of each employee appraised by his or her peers rather than by a manager or leader.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Share information as openly as possible in order to make employees aware of problems.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Adopt a hands-off approach in order to allow leadership to organically emerge from within the group of employees.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Eliminate the practice of conducting performance appraisals of employees.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Transformational leaders foster empowerment by openly sharing information with workers so that everyone is aware of problems and the need for action. Performance appraisals are not necessarily contrary to the philosophy or practice of transformational leadership, and these should not be conducted by an employee's peers. Transformational leadership is characterized by constructive engagement, not a hands-off approach."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "54",
        "Question": "Jennifer is a registered nurse who works in a busy emergency department. As one of her goals for the current year, Jennifer has resolved to develop her emotional intelligence. How should Jennifer best meet her goal?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Try to remove emotion from her clinical decision-making whenever possible.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Become more assertive when responding to the emotional responses of patients, families, and coworkers.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Become more aware of the way that her emotions function and how they influence her actions.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Try to limit her expressions of emotion to times when she is not interacting with others.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Self-awareness is one of the central aspects of emotional intelligence. Emotional intelligence does not necessarily involve removing emotion from decision-making or removing emotion from interpersonal interactions. Awareness of others' emotions is a dimension of emotional intelligence, but the appropriate response to this is not normally increased assertiveness."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "55",
        "Question": "A recent nursing graduate has asked an expert nurse how best to foster her leadership abilities, since she wishes to explore leadership opportunities later in her career. How should the expert nurse best respond?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  “Even if you don't trust a decision that you have to make, act like you chose the best option.”",
        "Choice 2": "B)  “Become as specialized as possible in your nursing experience.”",
        "Choice 3": "C)  “Develop your interpersonal skills by having a wide variety of interactions.”",
        "Choice 4": "D)  “Become as assertive as you can and take every opportunity to guide the behavior of others.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The development of sophisticated interpersonal skills is important to building leadership abilities. Effective leadership does not depend on feigned confidence, though self-confidence is a trait that can be fostered. In most cases, variety and depth of experience are superior to narrow specialization. Effective leadership is more nuanced and complex than simply directing the behavior of others or demonstrating assertiveness."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "56",
        "Question": "A nurse has responded to a patient's call light for the fourth time in the past hour only to be berated by the patient for taking so long to come to the bedside. Rather than responding in a confrontational tone the nurse has paused to think of the best response to the patient's statements. In doing so, the nurse has exhibited",
        "Choice 1": "A)  self-regulation.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  sympathy.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  manipulation.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  self-strategy.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Self-regulation refers to the ability to control inappropriate impulses and to think before acting or speaking. Research on mindfulness training indicates it is a positive strategy for managing emotionally charged situations. The nurse has not acted in a manipulative way. Sympathy involves feeling sorrow for another person's pain, a dynamic that is not evident in this interaction."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "57",
        "Question": "A patient is receiving a transfusion of packed red blood cells and consequently requires frequent vital signs. A set of vital signs was just due during the nurse's scheduled lunch break and so a colleague took the patient's vital signs. After returning from lunch, the nurse confirmed with the colleague that the scheduled vital signs were taken, to which the colleague replied, “Yes, it seems like I'm covering you a whole lot lately.” How should the nurse best respond to the colleague's statement?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  “I don't think that's a fair thing to say because I can't help when a set of vitals are due.”",
        "Choice 2": "B)  “If you're implying that I don't pull my weight I think that you're badly mistaken.”",
        "Choice 3": "C)  “Well, what goes around comes around, right?”",
        "Choice 4": "D)  “Could you explain what you mean by that?”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  An important principle of communication is to ensure that meanings are clearly understood by both parties. This is especially true in the case of a statement that may be accusatory. Responding confrontationally or sarcastically is rarely appropriate."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "58",
        "Question": "The nurse manager of a busy medical unit prioritizes effective communication with the employees of the unit. In recent years, an increasing amount of this communication has involved e-mails and text messages. When using these communication media, the nurse should",
        "Choice 1": "A)  take action to ensure that patient confidentiality is maintained.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  “cc” upper management and human resources with all e-mails.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  avoid using a smartphone on the unit whenever possible.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  follow up e-mails with a paper copy of important messages.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Patient privacy can be difficult to ensure when communicating electronically. As a result, nurse leaders must take measures to protect confidentiality. Electronic messages do not always need be followed up with paper copies and it is unnecessary to “cc” superiors on all communications. Smartphones are an effective communication tool, provided they are used in an appropriate manner."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "59",
        "Question": "It has been a frantic morning on the hospital unit and the nurse is unsure whether she will be able to complete her required tasks on time before her scheduled lunch break. Which of the following is the nurse's most appropriate response to this problem?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Skip lunch or trade her lunch break with a colleague who is scheduled for a later break.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Determine if more of her tasks could be delegated to another member of the care team.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Ask the unit manager for advice.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Explain to a colleague that she will likely be unable to complete her required work.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Delegation is an appropriate and useful strategy for effective time management. This would be a preferred approach over changing the lunch schedule. The nurse should attempt to delegate before approaching her manager for a solution or resigning herself to the fact that she will not complete her work."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Multiple Selection15.  All performance evaluations, whether formal or informal, should be based on appropriate standards of performance. In the context of a performance appraisal, which of the following are appropriate performance criteria? (Select all that apply.)",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The manager's experience base",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The nurse's written job description",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The institution's policies and procedures",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nursing standards of practice",
        "Choice 5": "E)  The nurse's career goals",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "2, 3, 4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Standards of performance include job descriptions, policies and procedures, and professional standards of practice. A leader's personal experience base and the nurse's goals may be relevant but neither is an objective measure for appraising the nurse's performance.",
        "Test Number": "60"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: DMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 13: Working with Others in a Leadership Role1.  The nature of healthcare requires the development of healthcare teams and collaboration among its members. Which of the following statements represents an element of this teamwork?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Each group member of a team is the leader of the team.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The organization sets the goals for its teams.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Communication patterns in teams flow both up and down.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Team members are not legally responsible for decisions and outcomes.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Teams may be led by facilitators or coaches, have members who share responsibility for decisions, setting goals, and achieving outcomes, use communication patterns that flow both up and down, and have members who share responsibility for decisions and outcomes. Not every member of the group is in a leadership role and goals may be set independently. A team may be legally responsible for the decisions its members make.",
        "Test Number": "61"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "62",
        "Question": "A client receives the care of a physician, a nurse, an occupational therapist, and a counselor working together as a team. What is the term for this type of healthcare?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Cross-discipline healthcare",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Comprehensive healthcare",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Holistic healthcare",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Interdisciplinary healthcare",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Interdisciplinary healthcare involves collaboration and extensive communication between members of different health disciplines. This model is not termed cross-discipline, comprehensive, or holistic healthcare."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "63",
        "Question": "A nurse will soon become a member of a newly-established care team. Which of the following is a goal of team building?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Acknowledging individual achievements",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Providing client care based on the direction of the team leader",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Creating a type of synergy when addressing client care",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Allowing care to be determined by nurses who are not “too close” to the situation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The goal of team building is to create a type of synergy, in which the effect of everyone working together toward the shared goal results in a greater total effect than could be achieved by the sum of the efforts of everyone working individually. Individual achievements should be acknowledged, but this is not the goal of team building. The process of building the team does not immediately result in changes to client care"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "64",
        "Question": "A registered nurse is responsible for organizing the care at a facility that has several UAPs. Which of the following tasks can an RN delegate to a UAP?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Performing an ongoing assessment",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Answering call lights",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Administering medications",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Counseling clients",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Any activity that requires knowledge and judgment that is unique to the function of an RN cannot be delegated to others. Such activities include ongoing assessment, medication administration, and counseling clients. Answering call lights is within the scope of a UAP and can thus be delegated."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "65",
        "Question": "A nurse recognizes the importance of safely and efficiently delegating tasks in order to achieve a high standard of care. Which of the following is one of the NCSBN's five “rights” of delegation?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Right education",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Right assessment",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Right circumstances",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Right motivation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The five rights of delegation include the right task, circumstances, person, direction/communication, and supervision/evaluation."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "66",
        "Question": "A nurse is aware of the pivotal role that motivation plays in the formation of effective teams and the provision of excellent nursing care. Which of the following actions is most likely to motivate a team member?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Ensure that the consequences of substandard performance are well-known.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Publicize those individuals who have made exceptional contributions and point out those who have failed to perform adequately.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Openly acknowledge team members who have made a particularly valuable contribution.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Be clear that only the highest levels of performance are acceptable to the team.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  There are numerous ways to foster motivation in others, including the use of genuine praise and acknowledging high performance. Negative methods, or punishments, have been shown to be less effective. These would include emphases on consequences, shame, and threats."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "67",
        "Question": "A registered nurse is responsible for overseeing the care that is provided in a long-term care facility. The skills mix at the facility includes the registered nurse, a practical nurse, and several unlicensed assistive personnel (UAP). Which of the following statements is true of the delegation that the RN performs?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The RN is accountable for the care that the other members of the team provide.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The RN may only delegate tasks that are outside of her own scope of practice.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The RN can delegate tasks that are outside the PN's or UAPs' scope of practice if she first provides adequate teaching.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Once a task is delegated, the person who performs the tasks is solely responsible for the outcomes.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  It is critical to remember that although you have asked someone else to carry out a nursing task, you are still accountable for the care that is given. A person cannot be delegated a tasks that is outside his or her scope of practice, regardless of whether teaching is provided. A person cannot delegate a task that is outside of his or her own scope of practice."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "68",
        "Question": "Healthcare is a field that continues to undergo constant and profound change, both planned and unplanned. Which of these situations is an example of reactive change?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Hospital administrators have announced a desire to implement the principles of evidence-based practice.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A hospital's accreditation review revealed systemic problems and the hospital has been directed to resolve these.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The introduction of automated medication dispensing machines at a hospital is scheduled for later this year.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A transition will soon begin whereby the practical (vocational) nurses will begin to practice within their full scope.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Planned change has a definite design and structure established to facilitate the process, including time lines, identification of stake holders, goals, plans for implementation, and processes for evaluation. Thoughtful planning often results in more effective and efficient change processes and is essential for projects that are complex or large in scope and that require greater time, resources, or skills. Change also may be unplanned and occur as a reaction to another issue, such as a failed accreditation. This is referred to as reactive change. Reactive change occurs when some problem or event arises that requires a different way of doing things."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "69",
        "Question": "Kurt Lewin's force-field theory of change is one of the most widely accepted and remains in current use today. The central concepts of this theory of change include",
        "Choice 1": "A)  the forces that govern intrinsic and extrinsic motivation.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  the relationship between driving forces and restraining forces.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  the forces of resilience and inertia in an organization.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  the relationship between the will for change and the ability to effect change.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  According to Lewin, change requires an imbalance between the forces that call for change–the driving forces, which push the system toward change and the restraining forces that pull the system away from change. Lewin does not explicitly address the issues of motivation, inertia, resilience, and will for change."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "70",
        "Question": "A nurse has identified glaring inefficiencies in the way that care is organized on a medical unit. Which of the following tasks will this nurse perform if he or she is to act as a change agent?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Informing others about the need for change",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Ensuring that others comply with any change that is implemented",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Establishing punishments and rewards to foster compliance with change",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Evaluating the long-term outcomes associated with change",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A change agent is the person who seeks to create change and is responsible for facilitating the change process with others. Having gathered data, identified the problem, and decided that change is needed, the change agent sets about making others aware of the need for change. A change agent is not necessarily involved with evaluating a change or ensuring compliance."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "71",
        "Question": "A nurse leader has been commissioned to implement a new electronic documentation system in a hospital, replacing the existing paper-based system that has been in place for decades. What is the first step that this nurse should take toward facilitating this change?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Enlist the support of the physicians and advanced practice nurses in the hospital.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Publicize the deficits of the existing documentation system.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Understand how and why individuals are often resistant to change.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Begin the process of evaluation before the change is implemented.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A first step in facilitating change is gaining a thorough understanding of resistance to change. This should precede the evaluation process, even though this should indeed begin early in the change process. An understanding of the change process is necessary before the nurse begins eliciting support from care providers or publicizing the deficits of the current system."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "72",
        "Question": "Jessica is a recent nursing graduate who was able to secure a position on the postsurgical unit where she completed the final preceptorship of her baccalaureate degree. Jessica has just received word that there will be sweeping changes in the organization of care on the unit, a development that she finds intimidating since she has only recently become adept at working in the existing system. How should Jessica best respond to this news?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Elicit support from nurses who support maintaining the existing system",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Learn as much as she can about the proposed system",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Research alternatives to the change that has been proposed",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Express her concerns about the proposed change to the nurse manager",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  As a novice nurse, you should take all available opportunities to learn about any anticipated changes. This is more beneficial that actively or passively opposing a change and should precede a presentation of concerns to the manager."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "73",
        "Question": "Healthcare institutions are frequently the site of conflict. Which of the following situations exemplifies interpersonal conflict?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A nurse is undecided whether to pursue a management position or to continue providing bedside care.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A recent graduate and a more experienced nurse disagree on the thoroughness of the recent graduate's assessments.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A cohort of experienced nurses have concerns about the way that younger nurses dress and present themselves.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The nurses on a unit are having difficulty getting physicians to return pages.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Interpersonal conflict occurs between or among individuals. This is where differences in values, ideas, perceptions, and goals play an important role. Intrapersonal conflict occurs within one's self in circumstances in which a choice must be made between two alternatives. Intergroup conflict exists between defined groups of individuals, such as recent nursing graduates, experienced nurses or physicians."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "74",
        "Question": "Alex is a nurse who has been taken aside by a colleague and the colleague has described another nurse as a “backstabber” and “battleaxe”. The colleague has gone on to give Alex details of ongoing conflict between the colleague and this nurse. Which conflict management technique should Alex apply in this situation?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Withdrawing from conflict",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Accommodating the conflict",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Negotiating",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Collaborating",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The strategy of avoiding or withdrawing from the conflict is employed when you choose not to address the issue at hand. There are many times when this approach is appropriate. This includes situations in which the conflict clearly is not your problem or when there is little or nothing that you can do about it. This is the case when a conflict is limited to two other individuals and does not involve patient safety. Accommodating, negotiating, and collaborating are likely not appropriate responses by the nurse to this interpersonal conflict."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "75",
        "Question": "The approach that a nurse chooses in the management of a conflict is entirely dependent on many of the factors and variables involved in the specific conflict. In which of the following situations would the nurse be most likely justified in forcing the issue or competing?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A nurse is embarrassed that a colleague discovered the nurse's medication error and completed an incident report.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A nurse observed a colleague remove an opioid analgesic from the locked medication cupboard and put it in her pocket.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A nurse disagrees with a colleague about the need for increased staffing levels.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A nurse has received constructive criticism from his manager during his latest performance appraisal.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Forcing the issue might be the best approach if the nurse observes a violation of ethical or legal standards, such as suspected substance abuse. Interpersonal disagreements about feedback or staffing levels are more likely to benefit from a more collaborative or constructive conflict management technique."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: DMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 14: Facing the Challenges of Today's Workplace1.  A nurse begins to feel comfortable on her unit and views client care in terms of long-range goals. She is able to prioritize among clients and deliberately plan her actions, which may still lack speed and flexibility. Which of Benner's levels of function has this nurse achieved?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Novice",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Advanced beginner",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Competent",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Proficient",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Characteristics of the competent nurse include beginning to see the current situation in terms of long-range goals. This nurse is able to prioritize among patients and base actions on conscious deliberate planning but may still lack speed and flexibility. As such, the competent nurse is more adept than the novice and advanced beginner but less skilled than the proficient nurse.",
        "Test Number": "76"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "77",
        "Question": "A novice nurse apprehensively reflects on what she considers to be an impossible task of delivering quality care on her ward as it is assigned to her. What is the name of this phenomenon first coined by Marlene Kramer?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Burnout",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Reality shock",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Culture shock",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Job disorientation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  One problem confronted by the new graduate is the seeming impossibility of delivering quality care within the constraints of the system as it exists. Kramer characterized this phenomenon as reality shock, not burnout, culture shock or job disorientation."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "78",
        "Question": "A counselor diagnoses a critical care nurse with having the syndrome known as burnout. Which of the following is a characteristic of this condition?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Burnout occurs when a nurse first enters the workplace and is overwhelmed by the workload.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  All of the symptoms of burnout are psychological in nature.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Burnout is accompanied by a decreased ability to function on the job and at home.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Burnout occurs less often in high-energy areas, such as critical care or burn units.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Burnout is accompanied by a decreased ability to function both on the job and in the personal life. Burnout occurs more frequently in nurses who work in particularly stressful areas of nursing, such as critical care, oncology, or burn units. It does not typically occur early in a nurse's time in a particular setting and it can result in physical manifestations."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "79",
        "Question": "A hospital manager is accused of quid pro quo sexual harassment. Which of the following is an action that might have been involved?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Making persistent unwanted attempts to initiate a personal relationship",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Granting job-related benefits in return for sexual favors",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Using suggestive or obscene language",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Making direct sexual advances",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Quid pro quo sexual harassment involves the explicit offer of job-related benefits in return for sexual favors. It is not defined by direct advances, attempting to initiate a relationship, or suggestive language, though some or all of these activities may be present in the exchange."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "80",
        "Question": "A hospital manager evaluates the workplace to ensure that ergonomics are working. Which of the following statements describes this scientific theory?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Ergonomics is the study of client outcomes related to economic theories in healthcare.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Ergonomics empowers clients to have a voice in their own plan of care.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Ergonomics ensures that jobs are fitted to the physical abilities of the employees.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Ergonomics provides guidelines for delegating responsibilities for client care.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Ergonomics is the science of fitting a task to one's physical characteristics in order to enhance safety, efficiency, and well-being. When the task does not conform to one's physical characteristics, musculoskeletal stress and injuries may occur. Ergonomics does not address client outcomes, delegation, or client autonomy."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "81",
        "Question": "Researchers have noted a high incidence of burnout among nurses. Which of the following nurses most likely faces the highest risk of burnout?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  An experienced nurse who has long neglected her own physical health and who leads a sedentary lifestyle.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A nurse who provides pediatric palliative care and who is disillusioned with the overall quality of care on the unit.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A nurse who has recently graduated with an ADN degree and begun working in a busy, inner-city emergency department.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A nurse who is few months away from retirement from her current position in community health.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Prominent among the causes of burnout is a conflict between ideals and reality. As well, practice environments with high mortality rates are associated with burnout. Poor physical health predisposes a nurse to burnout, but this is likely less salient than the combination of disillusionment and high acuity. New graduates and those approaching retirement are not particularly predisposed to burnout."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "82",
        "Question": "Melissa is a nurse who graduated earlier this year with a baccalaureate degree in nursing and immediately began working on a busy surgical unit with a high turnover of both the patients and the staff. As a result, Melissa has found the adjustment to full-time employment particularly stressful. Which of the following actions should Melissa take in order to manage the stress in her life?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Schedule a vacation for later in the year and focus on this upcoming trip when she is experiencing high levels of stress.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Reduce her workload to part-time and supplement this with casual employment on a lower-stress unit.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Be vigilant in personal habits that result in adequate rest, a healthy diet, and adequate physical exercise.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Reduce or eliminate the specific interactions in the clinical setting that cause her the most stress.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Attending to diet, rest, and activity is important in the management of job-related stress. These measures are more likely to be of benefit than trying to endure until a distant vacation. Adding another workplace has the potential to increase stress and it is not normally realistic to eliminate stressful interactions in the workplace."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "83",
        "Question": "A recent nursing graduate has become overwhelmed with reality shock in recent weeks, despite the fact that he secured a job in the setting that was his first choice. This nurse's best response to his experience with reality shock is to",
        "Choice 1": "A)  confront the manager of the unit with the details of his experience.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  reduce the performance expectations that he places on himself.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  prioritize physical assessments and interventions over patients' psychosocial needs.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  seek input from a trusted nurse who can act as a coach or mentor.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A coach or mentor can be of great assistance when recent nursing graduates are faced with reality shock. Such a person may be of more benefit than the manager of the unit, who may be too busy to assist the nurse with his adjustment. Reducing the quality of care or reducing expectations may place the burden of the nurse's reality shock on patients themselves, which is inappropriate."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "84",
        "Question": "A nurse who provides care in a busy ambulatory clinic knows that there are numerous occupational hazards associated with the provision of nursing care. What is the employer's responsibility in minimizing the nurse's risk of experiencing an injury or infection?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The employer must provide all the necessary supplies and equipment to prevent injuries and infections.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The employer must ensure that staffing levels are maintained at a level specified by the state board of nursing.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The employer must have dedicated occupational health officers present at all times.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The employer must release nurses from tasks that may present a threat to their health.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Employers must be held accountable for providing the supplies and environment to make work settings safe. All risks cannot normally be eliminated and dedicated occupational health staff may or may not be available or necessary. Safe staffing levels are important, but these do not necessarily mitigate the risk of workplace injuries and infections."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "85",
        "Question": "Racial and ethnic discrimination has been identified as a reality within healthcare institutions. Which of the following goals for the nursing profession is most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The nursing workforce should transcend racial and ethnic categorization and should not be appraised through this lens.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The nursing workforce should have fewer Caucasian members and more racial/ethnic minorities.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The nursing workforce should be made up of members from as many cultures as possible.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The nursing workforce should reflect the population for whom it provides care",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A workforce that reflects the population is more likely to meet the healthcare needs of that population in a culturally sensitive manner. It is simplistic to presume that the solution to discrimination lies with fewer Caucasians and more minorities. Similarly, increasing the number of cultures represented within nursing will not necessarily eliminate discrimination."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "86",
        "Question": "A nurse who works in a rural hospital has become frustrated and disillusioned at the steady increases in nurse to patient ratios at the same time that patient acuity has increased. When planning to address this issue with the hospital's leadership, the nurse should cite which of the following statements about increased nurse to patient ratios?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Increased nurse to patient ratios are associated with a decline in patient outcomes.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Reality shock is more common and severe when there are increased nurse to patient ratios.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  An increased nurse to patient ratio increases the incidence of disruptive behavior in hospital settings.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Discrimination and stress increase when there is an increase in nurse to patient ratios.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Increased nurse to patient ratios have been shown to result in decreased patient outcomes. There are other deleterious effects on nurses, including reality shock and stress, but patient outcomes should be the primary consideration."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "87",
        "Question": "A nurse was helping a colleague boost a patient higher in his bed she felt sudden pain in her lumbar region. How should the nurse follow up this event?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Make an appointment with a physician and document the injury if there are significant results.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Have a trusted colleague perform a musculoskeletal assessment and monitor the nurse's range of motion for the remainder of the shift.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Go home immediately and take enough sick time to allow her back to recover completely before returning to work.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Document the event as soon as possible using the hospital's designated forms.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A nurse who suspects an injury should report the event promptly using the appropriate paperwork. A common error is to delay reporting in the belief that you should report something only if you know it will be serious or require medical care. It is insufficient to leave work without documenting the event or to rely on a colleague's assessment and care."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "88",
        "Question": "Three times in the past several weeks a physician has commented on a nurse's body and each comment has been more explicit and sexually suggestive than the last. How should the nurse first respond to this form of sexual harassment?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Avoid contact with the physician except in locations where there are colleagues or other witnesses.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Ignore the physician if more comments are made in the future.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Confront the physician directly and explain that such comments are unacceptable and unwanted.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Document the events in detail and inform the state medical board.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Individuals should take steps to stop sexual harassment by giving clear, direct verbal messages indicating that the behavior in question is unwanted, unpleasant, and must stop. Sometimes this action alone stops inappropriate behavior. If clear, direct messages are not successful, the individual then should report the matter in writing to an immediate supervisor. Simply avoiding the offender or attempting to manage the behavior by reducing opportunities are not sufficient responses."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "89",
        "Question": "Despite being seen as a safe environment where victims of violence are treated, hospitals are the site of a large number of assaults. Which of the following care environments is associated with the greatest risk of physical violence?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Psychiatric mental health",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Geriatrics and gerontology",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Critical care and acute medicine",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Labor and delivery",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The majority of client assaults occur in psychiatric mental health settings."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "90",
        "Question": "A string of recent assaults perpetrated on nurses by clients has prompted the hospital administrators to address this disturbing trend. What action should the administrators prioritize in an effort to reduce the incidence of workplace violence?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Ensure that at least one male nurse is present at all times on each nursing unit.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Teach self-defense techniques to all the nurses who provide care in high-risk settings.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Train nurses how to effectively manage the behavior of aggressive patients and clients.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Withhold care from patients and clients who have a history of aggression.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  One form of violence prevention is to train employees in the management of hostile and violent behavior. Ways of identifying hostile and assaultive clients should be developed so that staff can be warned to take extra personal safety precautions. This is different from teaching self-defense techniques, which are normally physical in nature. It is not normally possible to withhold care from an individual, even if the person has a history of violence or aggression. The presence of male nurses is not an adequate measure in the prevention of violence."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: EMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 15: Valuing the Political Process1.  A nurse practicing in Alabama accepts a position in Connecticut. Which of the following would be the best resource to consult for a legal definition of nursing in that state?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  American Association of Nurses",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nurse Practice Act",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The American Journal of Nursing",
        "Choice 4": "D)  National League for Nursing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  All of the philosophic discussions about the role of the nurse must return to the reality of the nurse's role as legally defined in the state's practice act. Nurse practice acts define the specific legal parameters for nursing practice in a state. The AAN, NLN, and nursing journals do not make these determinants.",
        "Test Number": "91"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "92",
        "Question": "A nurse attempts to become more involved in the political process. Which of the following statements accurately describes the political arena in which this nurse may become involved?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Nurses can be involved in the political process as individuals, but they are far more effective when working in groups.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Most traditional nursing organizations are government-mandated groups and therefore are deeply involved in political activity.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Political action committees are nonprofit organizations that are registered as political action groups and are free to try to affect the political process.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nurses who testify for decision-making bodies must do so as an official representative of a nursing organization.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Legislators consider the views of individual constituents when making political decisions. However, the views of organized groups are more likely to influence a policymaker. Most traditional nursing organizations are nonprofit groups and therefore are limited in their political activity. PACs are registered as political action groups and are free to try to affect the political process. Nurses may testify as individuals."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "93",
        "Question": "Which of the following is an accurate representation of politics at the local level?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Once budgeted funds are allocated to an objective, more funds are made available for other projects.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Local budgets are generally mandated by federal agencies.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Support for community services may depend on whether knowledgeable nurses voice their advocacy.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Local political decision-making sessions are usually closed to the public.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In many communities, decisions about the allocation of federal money are made at the local level. Support for health-related community services may depend on whether those who are knowledgeable about the benefits of these services are willing to voice their advocacy in local decision-making bodies. When funds are allocated they are no longer available for other purposes and projects. The local political decision-making process is normally open to the public."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "94",
        "Question": "A nurse decides to become a member of NANDA-International (NANDA–I). Which of the following areas of the nursing process is he or she most likely interested in developing?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Assessment",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Diagnosis",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Implementation",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Evaluation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The purpose of NANDA-I is to work toward uniform terminology and definitions to be used in nursing diagnosis and to share ideas and information regarding this topic."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "95",
        "Question": "What is the main purpose of the National Council of State Boards of Nursing (NCSBN)?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Provide accreditation of baccalaureate and higher degree programs",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Recognize those with superior ability and leadership potential, and those who have made important contributions to nursing",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Provide a forum for the legal regulatory bodies to act together in the regulation of nursing practice for the protection of the public",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Unite the interests of nursing with those of the community in support of excellence in nursing education",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The purpose of the NCSBN is to provide a forum for the legal regulatory bodies (whatever their particular state titles might be) of all states, the District of Columbia, and the US territories to act together in the regulation of nursing practice for the protection of the public. It does not perform accreditation or leadership in education programs or acknowledge influential nurses."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "96",
        "Question": "A nurse has expressed her intention to draft a letter to her state senator but the nurse's colleagues have characterized this effort as “a waste of time and energy”. Which of the following statements provides the most accurate rationale for nurses' involvement in the political process?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Involvement in the political process can lead to the effective allocation of resources.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Political action increases the status and influence of the nursing profession as a whole.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Involvement in the political process demonstrates responsibility and accountability by nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Political involvement by nurses increases the influence of women in society and in government.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  With many voices competing to be heard in the decision-making circles of any nation, the person who understands power and politics, and who participates in this process, is the one most likely to obtain the resources needed to accomplish desired ends. Political involvement is not primarily motivated by the desire to increase the status of nurses and/or women and it is not simply an activity performed out of obligation or responsibility."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "97",
        "Question": "A nurse has become aware of sweeping changes that are proposed for the state budget which may have ramifications for the funding of the inner-city clinic where the nurse provides care. In order to influence the decision-making process the nurse should first",
        "Choice 1": "A)  tell clients of the clinic that their healthcare is in jeopardy.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  clearly communicate her views on the matter to the appropriate legislators.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  examine the systems and processes at the clinic to see where efficiency could be improved.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  approach the media with examples of the way that funding changes will hurt patient and client outcomes.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  One of the most basic, and important, ways to influence the political process is to explicitly communicate one's views to the government leaders who determine policy. Examining the efficiency of the clinic is a useful exercise but not one that is likely to influence political decisions. It is likely premature and alarmist to go to the media or begin telling clients that their care is in jeopardy."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Multiple Selection8.  The federal government operates in the healthcare field in complex ways that involve dozens of agencies. Which of the following groups are examples of the involvement of the federal government in healthcare? (Select all that apply.)",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC)",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Department of Health and Human Services (HHS)",
        "Choice 3": "C)  National Institutes of Health (NIH)",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Center for Medical & Medicare Services (CMS)",
        "Choice 5": "E)  National League of Nursing (NLN)",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 2, 3, 4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) is a cabinet-level administrative unit of the federal government with four major service divisions and many different sections. The Public Health Service includes the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). The National Institutes of Health (NIH), the Food and Drug Administration, the Health Resources Administration, and the Center for Medical & Medicare Services (CMS) are all part of HHS. The NLN is not a department or agency affiliated with the federal government.",
        "Test Number": "98"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "99",
        "Question": "A group of nurses have organized with the purpose of promoting an amendment to the nurse practice act that governs the profession. This group should direct their efforts toward what level of government?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Local",
        "Choice 2": "B)  State",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Federal",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Regional",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Nurse practice acts are pieces of legislation that exist at the state level."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "100",
        "Question": "A nurse has initiated a letter-writing campaign in an effort to increase the funding for school nursing programs in local high schools. A colleague of the nurse, however, has pointed out that the monies for such programs originate with the federal government. Which of the following statements best describes the relationship between federal funding and local healthcare programs?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Federal funding is made available only in cases where the local tax base is insufficient to fund programs.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Local contributions to health promotion programs are matched by the Department of Health and Human Services.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Decisions around the allocation for federal funding are often made at the local level.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Federal representatives control budgets at a local level but are obliged to consider input from local residents.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In many communities, decisions about the allocation of federal money are made at the local level. Recent congressional actions have leaned toward enhancing state and local control through creating large block grants where priorities would be decided locally. Federal funding is not dependent on a lack of local funding and the DHHS does not normally match local funding. Local budgets are not normally under the direction of federal officials."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "101",
        "Question": "In 2010, the Quality and Affordable Care Act was passed, beginning the process of providing health coverage for all legal residents of the United States. This legislation has numerous ramifications for nurses, including",
        "Choice 1": "A)  the replacement of most general practice physicians with nurse practitioners.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  the creation of incentives for advanced practice nursing education.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  the creation of a common scope of practice for practical (vocational) nurses and registered nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  the establishment of mandatory overtime for nurses in acute care settings.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The Quality and Affordable Care Act creates incentives for nurses to seek advanced education. This legislation does not create a uniform scope of practice for PNs and RNs or advocate the elimination of general practice physicians. As well, the act does not establish mandatory overtime for nurses."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "102",
        "Question": "A nursing student has expressed exasperation at the bewildering number and variety of nursing organizations that exist in the United States. Why are there so many nursing organizations?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The nursing profession itself is large, diverse, and complex.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nursing has long been defined by competing political interests.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Nursing is governed by a combination of local, state, and federal laws.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The nursing profession has traditionally been influenced by the interests of other political organizations.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The existence of a large number of diverse organizations for nurses is, in many ways, a reflection of nursing itself. The profession offers a wide variety of employment opportunities to its members, with distinct and varied contributions and interests in healthcare. When nurses become committed to a particular specialty group, they have a tendency to want to advance the purposes and interests of the people working in that area. This variety and diversity is reflected in the number of nursing organizations. It is not necessarily a result of competition, outside influences, or the variety of legislation that affects nursing practice."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "103",
        "Question": "After many years of providing bedside care in a variety of settings, a nurse has become involved in the leadership of the American Nurses Foundation (ANF). In this role, the nurse will be primarily involved in",
        "Choice 1": "A)  supporting nursing research.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  enhancing the public perception of the nursing profession.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  advancing the scope of practice for registered nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  lobbying for improved wages and benefits.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The ANF is a tax-exempt, nonprofit corporation that exists for the purpose of supporting research related to nursing. It is not primarily involved in promoting the image of nursing, lobbying for wages and benefits, or determining the scope of practice."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "104",
        "Question": "During his baccalaureate program in nursing, Mark became passionate about excellence in nursing education. Now that he has graduated and begun acting as a preceptor for nursing students, he wishes to become politically involved in issues relating to nursing education. What nursing organization should Mark most likely join?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  American Nurses Foundation (ANF)",
        "Choice 2": "B)  National Council of State Boards of Nursing, Inc. (NCSBN)",
        "Choice 3": "C)  NANDA-International (NANDA-I)",
        "Choice 4": "D)  National League for Nursing (NLN)",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The NLN seeks to unite the interests of nursing with those of the community in support of excellence in nursing education. The NCSBN, ANF, and NANDA-I are not primarily focused on matters relating to nursing education."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "105",
        "Question": "The Quality and Affordable Care Act of 2010 addresses a large variety of issues and policies related to the provision of healthcare in the United States. Which of the following situations is most likely to be affected by the provisions of this act?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A new resident of a small town has been unable to find a family physician who is accepting new patients.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A citizen has been falsifying documents and tax returns in order to qualify for Medicare.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A man is engaged in a dispute with his health maintenance organization (HMO) over reimbursement for an emergency procedure.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A woman is unsure where to bring her daughter for an annual influenza vaccination.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The Quality and Affordable Care Act addresses the Medicare and Medicaid programs, aiming to increase availability and eliminate waste and fraud. The act does not directly address the functioning of HMOs or the availability of specific aspects of care."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: EMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 16: Applying Research and Technology to Nursing Practice1.  A nurse has conducted a literature review in an effort to identify the effect of handwashing on the incidence of nosocomial (hospital-acquired) infections in acute care settings. An article presented findings at a level of significance of <0.01. This indicates that",
        "Choice 1": "A)  the control group and the experimental group were more than 99% similar.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  the findings of the study have less than 1% chance of being attributable to chance.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  the effects of the intervention were nearly zero.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  the clinical significance of the findings was less than 1:100.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The level of significance is the level at which the researcher believes that the study results most likely represent a nonchance event. A level of significance of <0.01 indicates that there is less than 1% probability that the result is due to chance.",
        "Test Number": "106"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "107",
        "Question": "A nurse has read a qualitative research study in order to understand the lived experience of parents who have a neonatal loss. Which of the following questions should the nurse prioritize when appraising the results of this study?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  “How well did the authors capture the personal experiences of these parents?”",
        "Choice 2": "B)  “How well did the authors control for confounding variables that may have affected the findings?”",
        "Choice 3": "C)  “Did the authors use statistical measures that were appropriate to the phenomenon in question?”",
        "Choice 4": "D)  “Were the instruments that the researchers used statistically valid and reliable?”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Qualitative studies are judged on the basis of how well they capture and convey the subjective experiences of individuals. Statistical measures and variables are not dimensions of a qualitative methodology."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "108",
        "Question": "A nurse has expressed skepticism to a colleague about the value of nursing research, claiming that nursing research has little relevance to practice. How can the nurse's colleague best defend the importance of nursing research?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  “The existence of nursing research means that nurses are now able to access federal grant money, something that didn't use to be the case.”",
        "Choice 2": "B)  “Nursing research has allowed the development of masters and doctoral programs and has greatly increased the credibility of the profession.”",
        "Choice 3": "C)  “The growth of nursing research has caused nursing to be viewed as a true profession, rather than simply as a trade or a skill.”",
        "Choice 4": "D)  “The application of nursing research has the potential to improve nursing practice and patient outcomes.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The greatest value of nursing research lies in the potential to improve practice and, ultimately, to improve patient outcomes. This supersedes the contributions of nursing research to education programs, grant funding, or the public view of the profession."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "109",
        "Question": "Tracy is a nurse with a baccalaureate degree who works in the labor and delivery unit of a busy urban hospital. She has noticed that many new mothers abandon breast-feeding their babies when they experience early challenges and wonders what could be done to encourage more women to continue breast-feeding. What role is Tracy most likely to play in a research project that tests an intervention aimed at promoting breast-feeding?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Applying for grant funding for the research project",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Posing the clinical problem to one or more nursing researchers",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Planning the methodology of the research project",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Carrying out the intervention and submitting the results for publication",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A major role for staff nurses is to identify questions or problems for research. Grant applications, methodological planning, and publication submission are normally carried out by nurses who have advanced degrees in nursing."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "110",
        "Question": "A patient signed the informed consent form for a drug trial that was explained to patient by a research assistant. Later, the patient admitted to his nurse that he did not understand the research assistant's explanation or his own role in the study. How should this patient's nurse respond to this revelation?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Explain the research process to the patient in greater detail.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Describe the details of a randomized controlled trial for the patient.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Inform the research assistant that the patient's consent is likely invalid.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Explain to the patient that his written consent is now legally binding.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Just as the staff nurse is not responsible for medical consent, the staff nurse is not responsible for research consent. If patients who have agreed to participate exhibit ambivalence or uncertainty about participating, do not try to convince them to participate. Ask the person from the research team who is managing consents to speak with concerned patients about the study, even after a patient has signed the consent forms."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Multiple Selection6.  A nurse leader is attempting to increase the awareness of evidence-based practice (EBP) among the nurses on a unit. A nurse who is implementing EBP integrates which of the following? (Select all that apply.)",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Interdisciplinary consensus",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nursing tradition",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Research studies",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Patient preferences and values",
        "Choice 5": "E)  Clinical expertise",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "3, 4, 5",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Fineout-Overholt, Melnyk, Stillwell, and Williamson define EBP as a problem-solving approach to the delivery of healthcare that integrates the best evidence from studies and patient care data with clinician expertise and patient preferences and values.",
        "Test Number": "111"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "112",
        "Question": "Mrs. Mayes is a 73-year-old woman who has a diabetic foot ulcer that has been extremely slow to heal and which now poses a threat of osteomyelitis. The wound care nurse who has been working with Mrs. Mayes applies evidence-based practice (EBP) whenever possible and has proposed the use of maggot therapy to debride necrotic tissue. Mrs. Mayes, however, finds the suggestion repugnant and adamantly opposes this treatment despite the sizable body of evidence supporting it. How should the nurse reconcile Mrs. Mayes' views with the principles of EBP?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The nurse should explain that reliable and valid research evidence overrides the patient's opinion.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The nurse should explain the evidence to the patient in greater detail.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The nurse should integrate the patient's preferences into the plan of care.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The nurse should involve the patient's family members in the decision-making process.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Patient preferences should be integrated into EBP and considered alongside research evidence and the nurse's clinical expertise; evidence does not trump the patient's preferences. The family should be involved, but this is not an explicit dimension of EBP. Similarly, explaining the evidence in more detail is not a demonstration of EBP."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "113",
        "Question": "The administrators of a long-term care facility are considered the use of specialized, pressure-reducing mattresses in order to reduce the incidence of pressure ulcers among residents. They have sought input from the nurses on the unit, all of whom are aware of the need to implement the principles of evidence-based practice (EBP) in this decision. Which of the following evidence sources should the nurses prioritize?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A qualitative study that explores the experience of living with a pressure ulcer",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A case study that describes the measures that nurses on a geriatric unit took to reduce pressure ulcers among patients",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Testimonials from experienced clinicians about the effectiveness of the mattress in question",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A randomized controlled trial that compared the pressure-reducing mattress with standard mattresses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The most reliable evidence is considered RCTs. Qualitative studies, case studies, and expert opinion are low on the hierarchy of evidence."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "114",
        "Question": "Hospital administrators are applying the principles of evidence-based practice (EBP) in their attempt to ascertain the most efficient and effective way to communicate between nurses who are on different units, a project that will consider many types of evidence. Which of the following information sources should the administrators prioritize?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A systematic review about communication in nursing contexts",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nurses' ideas about communication methods",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The results of a chart review",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The hospital's accreditation status",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Systematic reviews are assigned a high value in EBP. Reviews would be prioritized over nurses' ideas or a chart review, though both are potential considerations. The hospital's accreditation status is not a relevant consideration."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "115",
        "Question": "A nurse has resolved to apply the evidence-based practice (EBP) process to the way that admission assessments are conducted and documented on a unit. How should the nurse begin the process of establishing EBP?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Gather evidence showing the shortcomings of current practices",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Formulate a clear and concise question to be addressed",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Elicit support from the nurses who are most often responsible for admissions",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Search the literature for evidence that is potentially relevant to the practice need",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The first step in applying EBP is to ask a clear, focused question. This should precede a search of the literature or the recruitment of participants. An assessment of the shortcomings of the current system is not an explicit component of the EBP process."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "116",
        "Question": "Which of the following questions best exemplifies the PICOT format for asking evidence-based questions?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  What affect does parents' alcohol use have on the alcohol use of their teenage children?",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Among postsurgical patients, what role does meditation rather than benzodiazepines have on anxiety levels during the 48 hours following surgery?",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Among high school students, what is the effectiveness of a sexual health campaign undertaken during the first 4 weeks of the fall semester as measured by incidence of new sexually transmitted infections?",
        "Choice 4": "D)  In children aged 6–8, is the effectiveness of a descriptive pain scale superior to a numeric rating scale in the emergency room context?",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The correct answer includes a population (postsurgical patients), intervention (meditation), comparison (benzodiazepines), outcome (anxiety levels), and a time frame (48 hours). No other option contains each of the five elements of a PICOT question."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "117",
        "Question": "A nurse has made plans to implement the University of North Carolina (UNC) model of “5 As” during the process of applying evidence-based practice (EBP) to a practice problem. What is the final step that the nurse will take in applying this model?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Analyze the results of the EBP process",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Advocate for others to embrace the identified change",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Adopt the changes identified in the review process",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Assess the outcomes of the new practice",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The final step in the UNC rubric is to “Assess” the change using the quality improvement process in place in the institution."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "118",
        "Question": "A nurse has been asked to make a presentation to a group of high school students on the subject of sexual health. However, the nurse does not have a background in this practice area and requires rapid access to evidence-based guidelines. Which of the following strategies is most likely to provide the nurse with valid and reliable evidence in a time-efficient manner?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Search the Cochrane Library of Systematic Reviews",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Google search terms such as “sexual health teens” and “sexual education”",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Search Medline using PubMed and order relevant articles",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Scan the most recent issues of nursing journals that address this area of practice",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  For some problems, a systematic review may be available from a source such as the Cochrane Library. Often this review is done by an expert panel providing excellent information on which to base decisions. This approach is more likely to produce valid and reliable results than a Google search and is more efficient than searching journal manually or ordering articles through PubMed."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "119",
        "Question": "The nurses at a university hospital have been informed that a computerized record system will be implemented over the next 12 months. The nurses should be aware that such as system presents particular challenges in the area of",
        "Choice 1": "A)  vulnerability to errors in charting and the inability to make changes.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  patient privacy and confidentiality of records.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  enforcing compliance with the system on the part of nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  ensuring compatibility with different computer operating systems.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Concerns about privacy become magnified when information is available to many people in many sites far removed from where the patient is located, a situation that exists when computerized records are used. This is usually considered a more important concern than issues of compliance, compatibility, or vulnerability to errors."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "120",
        "Question": "A nurse is nervous about the impeding introduction of computerized nursing care records at the hospital because he does not consider himself to be technologically adept. How should this nurse best respond to this situation?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Take courses in advanced practice nursing to build his knowledge.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Explore employment opportunities in settings that use written documentation systems.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Advocate for a delay in the introduction of the proposed system.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Seek out opportunities to learn the relevant knowledge and practice the necessary skills.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A nurse who lacks technological knowledge or skills should seek out opportunities to expand these. This is preferable to finding a job elsewhere, studying advanced practice nursing, or attempting to delay the change."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: EMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 2: Educational Preparation for Nursing1.  Manuel has a baccalaureate degree in biology and wishes to make a career change to eventually become an advanced practice RN. Which of the following courses of study would be the most time-efficient choice to meet his educational goals?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Master's degree in nursing",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Baccalaureate degree in nursing",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Doctoral degree in nursing",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Associate degree in nursing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Students may be admitted to master's programs in nursing with a baccalaureate degree in another discipline and are granted a master's degree in nursing after completing an established 2-year program of study that prepares them for RN licensure. However, people who already possess baccalaureate or higher degrees in other fields sometimes seek admission to an associate degree program, often because it can be completed in a shorter period of time than would be needed to earn another baccalaureate degree (though accelerated baccalaureate programs are becoming more common).",
        "Test Number": "121"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "122",
        "Question": "Which nursing report recommended that nursing education move away from the system of apprenticeship that predominated at the time and move toward a planned program of education similar to that offered by other professions?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The Surgeon General's Consultant Group Report on Nursing",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The Brown Report",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The American Nurses Association Position Paper",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The Pew Health Profession Commission Study",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In Nursing for the Future, Brown (1948) recommended that nursing education move away from the system of apprenticeship that predominated at the time and move toward a planned program of education similar to that offered by other professions. This predated the Surgeon General's Consultant Group Report on Nursing, the American Nurses Association Position Paper, and the Pew Health Profession Commission Study."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "123",
        "Question": "Which of the following accurately states a major position of the ANA Position Paper on Educational Preparation?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The education of those who are licensed to practice nursing should take place in hospitals.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Minimum preparation for beginning professional nursing practice at the present time should be an associate degree in nursing.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Minimum preparation for beginning technical nursing practice at the present time should be a baccalaureate degree in nursing.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Education for assistants in health service occupations should be short, intensive preservice programs in vocational educational institutions.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  One of the four major positions of the ANA Position Paper on Educational Preparation is that education for assistants in the health service occupations should be short, intensive preservice programs in vocational education institutions, rather than on-the-job training programs. It also states that the education of all those who are licensed to practice nursing should take place in institutions of higher education, not in hospitals. The paper specifies an associate degree as the minimum for technical nursing and a baccalaureate degree for professional nursing."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "124",
        "Question": "Sister Calista Roy identified an adaptation model that characterizes the individual as being in constant interaction with a changing environment, therefore requiring adaptation. Which of the following identifies an adaptive mode listed in her theory?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Role function",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nutrition",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Spirituality",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Genetic makeup",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Roy identifies four adaptive modes, or ways in which a person adapts through: (1) physiologic needs, (2) self-concept, (3) role function, and (4) interdependence relations. Nutrition, spirituality, and genetic makeup are not discrete concepts within this theory."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "125",
        "Question": "Mr. Van is a 79-year-old widower who is being transferred to a long-term facility following hip replacement surgery. The nurse in charge of his care hopes to provide holistic nursing care for him based on his response to the interaction between his internal and external environment. This approach represents the model of care proposed by which of the following theorists?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Dorothy Johnson",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Madeleine Leininger",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Dorothea Orem",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Myra Levine",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Levine supports a holistic approach to nursing based on recognition of the total response of the person to the interaction between the internal and the external environment. This approach is not specified by Johnson, Leininger, or Orem."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Multiple Selection6.  A college sophomore has become disillusioned with her current field of studies and has begun exploring careers in nursing. To her surprise, she is unable to identify any hospital-based programs of study in her home state. Which of the following factors have contributed to the demise of hospital-based diploma programs? (Select all that apply.)",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Increased patient acuity in hospitals",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Increased popularity of college- and university-based nursing programs",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The growth of managed care and its influence on hospital management",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Increased costs to hospitals for maintaining nursing programs",
        "Choice 5": "E)  The emergence of the baccalaureate degree as the entry to technical nursing practice",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "2, 4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The elimination of hospital-based programs occurred because hospitals could not sustain the costs of supporting the programs and because students became more attracted to programs located in colleges and universities. Patient acuity and managed care have not been identified as causative factors. The baccalaureate degree has been proposed as the entry to professional nursing practice, not technical nursing.",
        "Test Number": "126"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "127",
        "Question": "Kirsten is a 22-year-old woman who has just been granted admission to an associate degree program at a local college. During her course of study, Kirsten should expect to complete",
        "Choice 1": "A)  the National Council Licensure Examination (NCLEX®).",
        "Choice 2": "B)  a preceptorship under the direction of a licensed practical (vocational) nurse.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  a major, original research project immediately prior to graduation.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  numerous nonnursing courses in a variety of disciplines.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In a typical ADN program, approximately 40% of the credits needed for the associate degree must be fulfilled by general education courses such as English, anatomy, physiology, speech, psychology, and sociology; the rest are to be fulfilled by nursing courses. Original research is not a component of undergraduate nursing education, and preceptorships are normally completely under the direction of an RN. The NCLEX® is written after graduation."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "128",
        "Question": "Ben is a 30-year-old man who has applied for an accelerated baccalaureate program at a university because the 15-month program of study will allow him to accommodate his family and financial responsibilities. In order to be granted admission, what will Ben most likely require?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A varied work history that demonstrates initiative and responsibility",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A baccalaureate degree in another field",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A mentor or sponsor within the nursing field",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Volunteer experience in a health-related setting",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Building on previous learning experiences, accelerated programs are designed to transition adults with baccalaureate and graduate degrees in other fields into nursing. A strong work history, volunteer experience, and an available mentor in the field are all assets for success, but these are less likely to be absolutely required for admission."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "129",
        "Question": "Julia has just graduated with her Bachelor of Science in Nursing degree from her state university and has begun seeking employment. However, she is anxious about her level of clinical competence due to the fact that she completed far fewer clinical hours than many practicing nurses. Which of the following has the potential to ease Julia's transition to practice?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Completing a residency or internship at the hospital where she will be employed",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Auditing courses in a nonnursing, health-related discipline",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Working for several months as a nursing assistant in order to gain confidence",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Taking online courses in advanced nursing practice",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Internships and residencies for new graduates have been instituted by hospitals to ease the transition from the role of student to that of staff by providing the opportunity to increase clinical skills and knowledge as well as self-confidence. Taking more academic courses and/or working as a nursing assistant are unlikely to increase Julia's confidence and competence in her clinical nursing role."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "130",
        "Question": "According to the ANA Position Paper on Educational Preparation, which of the following four individuals is adequately prepared to provide care?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A nursing assistant who has just completed an on-the-job training program in a local hospital",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A nurse who graduated from a hospital-based diploma program",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A nurse in a high-acuity setting who possesses an associate degree in nursing (ADN) degree",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A nursing assistant who graduated from the training program at a community college",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The ANA Position Paper specifies that education for assistants in the health service occupations should be short, intensive preservice programs in vocational education institutions, rather than on-the-job training programs. The Paper also specifies a minimum of an ADN degree for all nursing practice and a baccalaureate degree for professional nursing (e.g., in high-acuity settings)."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "131",
        "Question": "Nurse. L. provides care in a state that has mandatory continuing education requirements for nurses. What are the consequences of this policy for Nurse L.?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Nurse L. must demonstrate a commitment to making practice improvements.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nurse L. must have a baccalaureate degree in order to provide professional nursing care.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Nurse L. is obliged to update her diploma to an associate degree.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nurse L. must demonstrate continuing education for license renewal.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Mandatory continuing education affects licensure, meaning that any nurse renewing a license in a state requiring (mandating) continuing education will have to satisfy that requirement. However, this does not necessarily mean that a nurse must update his or her degree or diploma or undertake practice improvements."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "132",
        "Question": "The administrators of a large, university hospital have expressed a commitment to differentiated nursing practice. Which of the following most clearly exemplifies differentiated practice?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Each nurse performs a role that is commensurate with his or her education and experience level.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Each nurse in the hospital is expected to provide competent care in a variety of different settings.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Nurses demonstrate evidence of continuing education in two or more different specialties.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Each nurse in the hospital possesses an ADN or baccalaureate degree in nursing.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Differentiated nursing practice can be defined as the practice of structuring nursing roles on the basis of education, experience, and competence. It does not necessarily specify the provision of care in diverse settings, evidence of continuing education, or the possession of a nursing degree."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "133",
        "Question": "A nurse manager who oversees the provision of community-based care to a large number of clients has been mandated to implement differentiated care over the next year. In order to carry out this directive, the nurse manager must be able to",
        "Choice 1": "A)  teach each nurse to become a “generalist” rather than a “specialist.”",
        "Choice 2": "B)  identify the evidence that underlies the nursing care that is provided.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  clearly identify the specific roles and tasks that these nurses perform.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  hire more licensed practical (vocational) nurses.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Differentiated practice requires that the specific roles that are performed in the provision of care be clearly identified and delineated. This is necessary in order to appropriately match individual care providers to particular tasks and functions. Nurses do not need to become “generalists” nor are more practical nurses necessarily required. Evidence underlying nursing care should be identified, but this is not necessary for differentiated care."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "134",
        "Question": "Pressure from students and the healthcare industry has prompted the nursing educators at a college to implement new technology into the nursing education that they provide. Which of the following statements is true of technological change and nursing education?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Technology is typically high in colleges and universities but low in hospitals and other care settings.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Many of the purported educational benefits of technology have not been demonstrated in the nursing literature.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Computer literacy is high among students but most nursing educators lack computer skills.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The costs of integrating new technology into nursing education can be prohibitive.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  High-technology equipment is often expensive, a fact that often presents a challenge to educational institutions. The benefits of technology in learning have been demonstrated and computer literacy is nearly universal. Hospitals are high-technology work environments."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "135",
        "Question": "The faculty members of a college-based school of nursing have taken action to increase the teaching and clinical time in the curriculum that is devoted to community-based nursing. Which of the following phenomena provides the most valid rationale for this change?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Public mistrust of hospitals is increasing and many individuals prefer to remain at home.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The number of patients who qualify for Medicare and Medicaid is increasing.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Patients are typically discharged from the hospital much earlier than in the past.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Evidence demonstrates that students learn more in the community than in the hospital.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Earlier hospital discharge to the home and an increasing emphasis on prevention has created new demands on nursing in the community. This shift is not rooted in mistrust of hospitals, a lack of learning in hospitals, or trends in Medicare and Medicaid."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: EMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 3: Credentials for Healthcare Providers1.  What is the major advantage of “sunset laws”?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Nurses can modify their standards of practice on a daily basis.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  They guarantee that the legislature will review and evaluate agencies and programs.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The legislature can close facilities that do not meet governmental requirements.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Facilities must renew their accreditation in a specified amount of time.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Because sunset laws are set to expire at a specified point in time, legislatures are obligated to review and evaluate them prior to expiry. Sunset laws do not directly influence the nurses' standards of practice, the quality of healthcare facilities, or the accreditation process.",
        "Test Number": "136"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "137",
        "Question": "A nurse who is licensed to practice in Pennsylvania decides to seek a nursing position in Florida. This nurse would obtain this license by which of the following methods?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Licensure by endorsement",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Licensure by examination",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Licensure by renewal",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Reciprocal licensure",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The method of obtaining a license when the nurse is already licensed in another jurisdiction is called licensure by endorsement; this is an alternative to license by examination. This transfer is not termed reciprocal licensure or licensure by renewal."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "138",
        "Question": "A nursing board asks the court to stop a nurse from practicing until it investigates allegations that the nurse was providing care while under the influence of alcohol. What is the name of the process that allows this action?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Revocation",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Suspension",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Injunctive relief",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Court investigation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A board of nursing may be authorized to ask a court to halt a specific practice that it believes is contrary to the law until a full hearing can be held. This is called injunctive relief. This term refers to the court order called an injunction that requires an individual or organization to stop a particular activity, such as practicing nursing. The investigation is performed by the board, not the court. Revocation involves the removal of a license, and suspension does not typically involve the courts."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "139",
        "Question": "Which of the following is a recommendation of the Institute of Medicine report Health Profession Education: A Bridge to Quality (2003)?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Developing separate core competencies to regulate each health profession",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Revising the processes of accreditation bodies to require outcomes related to core competencies",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Allowing each profession to educate, practice, and dialogue within its own boundaries",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Changing healthcare workforce regulations based on what is termed a “safe” focus",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The IOM report recommended that both licensing bodies and specialty certification bodies require health professionals to demonstrate in some way their continued competence in the previously determined core competencies. The report does not advocate the development of separate core competencies, the isolation of each profession, or changes to workforce regulations."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "140",
        "Question": "A nurse administers insulin to a diabetic patient via an insulin pump. Based on the NCLEX® examination, this action would fall under which of the categories of client needs?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Safe effective care environment",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Health promotion and maintenance",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Psychosocial integrity",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Physiological integrity",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The client needs category of physiological integrity encompasses nursing actions that address a client's physical needs and the treatment of illness. Administration of medication is not normally considered a health promotion activity, an aspect of psychosocial integrity, or a demonstration of safety measures."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "141",
        "Question": "A nurse who has provided care in acute settings for several years has begun the process of gaining additional credentials. Which of the following statements best describes credentials?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Credentials indicate that an individual has demonstrated a continuing commitment to competence.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Credentials recognize an individual's professional superiority to his or her peers.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Credentials indicate that an individual has met specific criteria and standards.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Credentials indicate that an individual has the authority to direct practice in a particular care setting.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Credentials indicate that an individual (or organization) has met specific standards that are important to fulfilling a professional mandate. This is not necessarily synonymous with a “continued commitment,” though such a commitment may help facilitate the attainment of credentials. Individual credentials do not necessarily indicate superiority or leadership potential."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "142",
        "Question": "After completing an associate degree in nursing and passing the NCLEX-RN® examination, a nurse has been granted a license to practice. A license to practice provides the nurse with",
        "Choice 1": "A)  formal recognition of the nurse's graduation from an accredited school of nursing.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  legal permission to practice the nursing profession.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  the authority to practice nursing in any state.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  recognition of advanced learning and competence in a particular care setting.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A license is a legal credential awarded by an individual state that grants permission to that individual to practice a given profession. A license is normally specific to a particular jurisdiction. It does not denote advanced learning in a specific setting. Graduation from a school of nursing is required for licensure, but a license does not explicitly document this education."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "143",
        "Question": "The students and faculty of a school of nursing are pleased that the school has recently been granted a renewal of its current accreditation. Accreditation of a school of nursing is based primarily on which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The proportion of graduates who pass the NCLEX-RN®",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The academic credentials of faculty members",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The findings of an external review committee",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The overall contribution of the school to the body of nursing knowledge",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Accreditation of a school of nursing is primarily based on the findings of nursing experts who visit the institution and appraise the education that is provided. Other factors may be considered, such as the success of graduates, the credentials of instructors, or the research that is conducted, but the findings of external reviewers are paramount."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "144",
        "Question": "A state board of nursing is legally empowered to carry out the provisions of the Nurse Practice Act. Which of the following activities best demonstrates the mandate and jurisdiction of a state board of nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Advocating for nurses during labor negotiations",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Organizing information campaigns to enhance the public perception of the nursing profession",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Specifying the way that nursing care is organized in public hospitals",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Establishing the standards that nurses must meet in order to be licensed",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  State boards of nursing perform multiple functions, including examination and licensure of nurses. Participation in labor negotiations, advertising to increase awareness of the profession, and specifying the way that care is provided are activities that are normally beyond the purview of a state board of nursing."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "145",
        "Question": "A registered nurse who completed her education in the Philippines and who is in the process of immigrating in the United States is attempting to obtain a license to practice in New Jersey, her intended state of residence. In order to obtain a license, the nurse will primarily be in contact with",
        "Choice 1": "A)  the New Jersey Board of Nursing.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  the American Nurses Association (ANA).",
        "Choice 3": "C)  one of the accredited schools of nursing in New Jersey.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  the National Council of State Boards of Nursing, Inc. (NCSBN).",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Licensure is one of the main responsibilities of state boards of nursing, and a nurse seeking a license to practice in a particular state must obtain a license from that state's board of nursing. Schools of nursing, the ANA, and the NCSBN do not directly grant licensure."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Multiple Selection11.  Amanda is a nurse who currently works in a community clinic in a city near state lines. She is exploring employment possibilities in a neighboring state and hopes to obtain a license through mutual recognition of licensure. Which of the following conditions must be met in order for Amanda to obtain a nursing license in this manner? (Select all that apply.)",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Amanda's home state must be party to the Nurse Licensure Compact.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Amanda must obtain a nursing license in the intended state as well as in her home state.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Amanda must meet the standards for licensure in the state where she intends to practice.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The state in which Amanda wishes to practice must belong to the Nurse Licensure Compact.",
        "Choice 5": "E)  Amanda must possess an ADN or baccalaureate degree in nursing.",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 3, 4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Obtaining a license through mutual recognition of licensure requires that an individual's home state and the intended state of practice be party states. As well, an applicant must qualify for licensure in the intended state. A diploma in nursing does not preclude transfer of licensure, and an individual may not possess licenses in both states simultaneously.",
        "Test Number": "146"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "147",
        "Question": "Under the provisions of the Nurse Licensure Compact (NLC), a nurse who is licensed in Arizona has been practicing for the past year in New Mexico. The nurse is alleged to have become involved in an inappropriate relationship with a patient in New Mexico and grounds for disciplinary action appear to exist. How will the discipline of this nurse most likely proceed?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The New Mexico Board of Nursing may withdraw the nurse's license if this is deemed necessary.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The nurse's discipline is referred to the American Nurses Association because two state boards of nursing have interest in the matter.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The New Mexico Board of Nursing will undertake investigation, but the Arizona State Board of Nursing will implement appropriate discipline.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The New Mexico Board of Nursing will be unable to change the Arizona licensure status of the nurse.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A major concern with mutual recognition is the disciplinary process. Although the board of nursing can investigate nursing practices and enforce its own standards in the state, it cannot change the licensure status of the person whose licensure originates in a different state. The ANA does not participate in disciplinary matters, and a state would not normally undertake discipline based on an investigation in another party state."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "148",
        "Question": "Nurse T. has been notified by her state board of nursing that a complaint has been lodged regarding her practice. How should Nurse T. best respond to this news?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Retain the services of an attorney.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Organize a private meeting between her and the complainant.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Have colleagues write statements attesting to her competence.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Explore practice opportunities in other states.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The individual being investigated for any violation of the Nurse Practice Act should have an attorney who is knowledgeable about professional disciplinary issues from the time of notification of the complaint. This is an important action, whether or not there are grounds for the accusation. A meeting with the complainant would be inappropriate, and enlisting support from colleagues would be a secondary concern compared with hiring an attorney. It would be premature, and likely inappropriate, to explore options out-of-state at this early stage."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "149",
        "Question": "A nurse has been working in pediatrics for 6 years since graduating from an accredited nursing school. The nurse is now interested in pursuing American Nurses Credentialing Center certification as a pediatric Clinical Nurse Specialist. What factor will primarily determine whether the nurse obtains this ANCC certification?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Enrollment in a PhD, DNS, or DNP degree program",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A review of the nurse's marks from nursing school and interviews with managers and colleagues",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Completion of an original research project related to pediatric nursing",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The demonstration of knowledge and skills in beyond those required for licensure as an RN",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  ANCC certification is a method of recognizing nurses who have special expertise. Applicants must demonstrate current practice and knowledge beyond that required for licensure as an RN. Enrollment in a doctoral program is not necessary. Marks from nursing school, the opinions of supervisors, and the completion of research do not form the basis for certification."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "150",
        "Question": "The Institute of Medicine (IOM) report Health Profession Education: A Bridge to Quality (2003) came to several conclusions around the issues confronting health professions education. Which of the following issues was addressed in the report?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The tendency of each health discipline to educate and practice independently of the other disciplines",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The lack of recognition of credentials and the credentialing process outside of the field of nursing",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The trend toward managed care and the inability of nursing educators to adapt to this change",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The historical animosity between nursing and medicine and the failure to bridge this gap",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The IOM noted that each health profession tends to educate, practice, and dialogue within a “silo.” These narrowly constructed walls make it difficult for interdisciplinary collaboration to occur. The report does not focus on the relationship between medicine and nursing, the trend toward managed care, or the lack of recognition of credentials."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: DMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 4: Making Professional Goals a Reality1.  Which organization developed the most definitive statements on the competencies needed by the newly licensed practical nurse (PN) and the RN?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  National Council of State Boards of Nursing (NCSBN)",
        "Choice 2": "B)  American Association of Nurses (ANA)",
        "Choice 3": "C)  National League for Nursing (NLN)",
        "Choice 4": "D)  American Association of Colleges of Nursing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The most definitive statements on the competencies needed by the newly licensed practical nurse (PN) and the RN have been developed by the NCSBN based on its job analysis studies, which serve as the basis for the NCLEX-RN® and NCLEX-PN®.",
        "Test Number": "151"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "152",
        "Question": "In what type of healthcare setting are the most RNs currently employed?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Ambulatory care centers",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Doctor's offices",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Acute care hospitals",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Long-term care facilities",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  As of 2008, over 89% of nurses worked in hospital settings, 4.8% worked in long-term care, and 4.3% worked in community-based or ambulatory care settings. Only 1.7% of nurses indicated that they worked in “other” settings."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "153",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements accurately reflects what employers generally should expect when hiring a newly graduated RN?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The RN should be proficient with the documentation system used by the institution.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The RN should be able to perform all nursing skills, enabling him or her to work independently.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The RN should function with speed comparable to that of the other nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The RN should be able to develop plans of care and follow plans developed by the agency.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  New graduates should be able to develop plans of care and follow plans, such as care pathways, that have been developed by the agency. Proficiency, speed, and complete independence are developed over time and with increased experience and orientation."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "154",
        "Question": "A nurse decides to apply for a position in a hospital in her hometown. Which of the following statements provides good advice for her job quest?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  She should call the human resources department and speak to the person who is in charge of hiring nurses.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  She should include a cover letter with her résumé that is no more than two pages long and briefly reiterates the information found in the résumé.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  She should invest in a professionally prepared résumé to make a better impression on potential employers.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  She should focus her résumé on accomplishments and use active verbs to describe her skills.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In a résumé, it is best to focus on accomplishments and use active verbs to describe skills. Professional preparation of a résumé is not necessary, and telephone communication is generally discouraged. A cover letter should ideally not exceed one page in length."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "155",
        "Question": "Which of the following is a recommended guideline when resigning a position?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Provide the employer with 2 weeks to seek a replacement.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Clearly state the details if you wish to be compensated for any vacation or holiday time accrued.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  If resigning because of problems in the work setting, it is a good idea to put the reason in the resignation letter.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Place comments regarding positive factors experienced in the workplace in a separate correspondence from the resignation letter.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  If you have accrued vacation or holiday time and want to take the time off or be paid for it when resigning, clearly state that. A month's notice is ideal, and a resignation letter should not go into detail regarding the contributing problems in the workplace. Positive factors experienced in the workplace may be included in the resignation letter."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "156",
        "Question": "A student nurse is scheduled to graduate in a few weeks and is preparing to begin searching for employment. Which of the following statements best conveys an aspect of the current job market for nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Most nursing graduates are expected to perform in the role of a nursing assistant or practical (vocational) nurse after graduation.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The majority of nursing opportunities for new graduates are in international settings.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Job openings in acute care have decreased in many places but long-term care openings continue to grow.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The increasing severity of the nursing shortage means that job opportunities for nursing graduates are greater than ever.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Positions for new graduate RNs have recently decreased. This is due in part to the effects of the economic recession. Although hospital vacancies have decreased in many places, those in long-term care continue to increase. Some, but not most, graduates may find work in other roles, and a minority of positions are in international settings."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "157",
        "Question": "A recent nursing graduate is attempting demonstrate the competencies that she learned as a nursing students and to reconcile the expectations of her new colleagues and employer with her own abilities. Which of the following tasks is the most important and most frequently performed?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Helping patients and families navigate the healthcare environment",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Applying the principles of infection control and standard precautions",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Initiating vascular access and maintaining peripheral and/or central IV access",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Liaising with members of other health disciplines to ensure safe and continuous care",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Apply principles of infection control (e.g., hand hygiene, room assignment, isolation, aseptic/sterile technique, universal/standard precautions) is among the most common, and most important, nursing actions as identified by nursing organizations. Patient advocacy, interdisciplinary cooperation, and IV therapy are all important, but none is performed as frequently as infection control measures."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "158",
        "Question": "Healthcare institutions expect that nursing graduates will be able to apply their theoretic knowledge for safe client care. Which of the following actions best demonstrates this?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Creating a nursing care plan for a newly admitted patient",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Responding appropriately to a patient complaining of chest pain",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Advocating for a patient's interests with members of other disciplines",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Conducting a thorough and thoughtful search for nursing employment",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Responding appropriately to an emergent health threat is a demonstration of safe care and the appropriate application of knowledge. Patient advocacy and creating care plans are functions that are less closely related to patient safety. Searching for a job is not linked to safe client care."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "159",
        "Question": "The expected competencies of new nursing graduates are not standardized and can vary between institutions and organizations. Most nursing and healthcare organizations, however, agree that recent graduates should be able to use the nursing process in a systematic way. Which of the following nursing activities best exemplifies this competency?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The nurse identifies a nursing diagnosis of Impaired Skin Integrity based on an assessment and plans to reposition the patient.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The nurse administers an ACE inhibitor to a patient with high blood pressure.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The nurse makes a referral to occupational therapy for a patient with a neurological deficit.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The nurse attends an inservice on pain control that is conducted by a nurse educator.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The nursing process includes assessment, analysis, planning, intervention, and evaluation. Identifying a nursing diagnosis on the basis of an assessment exemplifies the early stages of this process. Learning about pain management, administering a medication, and making a referral to another discipline may also exist within the framework of the nursing process, but the steps of this process are not as clearly evident in these examples."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "160",
        "Question": "A patient has just been transferred to the acute medicine unit from the intensive care unit and the patient's arterial line has not yet been discontinued. The nurse on the acute medicine unit is a recent graduate and does not have experience in caring for an arterial line. As a result, the nurse is unsure how to safely address this aspect of the patient's care. How should the nurse best respond?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Look up arterial lines in the policy and procedures manual on the unit.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Inform the unit manager that this patient assignment is inappropriate.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Enlist the help of a more senior nurse on the unit.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Have the patient transferred back to the intensive care unit.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  To provide safe care, the nurse must identify when a situation requires greater expertise or knowledge and when assistance is needed. Asking a colleague for assistance is an appropriate demonstration of this competency. Looking up a procedure in a policy manual is an appropriate action but does not show a willingness to ask others for help. It would likely be premature to refuse the care of this patient or to have him or her transferred."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "161",
        "Question": "After several months of working on an acute care for elders (ACE) unit following her graduation, Theresa has decided to focus her nursing career on working with older adults. What action is most likely to help Theresa meet this career goal?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Cultivating a passion for the health of the older adult population",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Networking with prominent older adults in the community",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Performing original research that adds to the knowledge of this population's needs",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Working toward certification in gerontological nursing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Certification in a particular nursing specialty has the potential to increase a nurse's opportunities in that field. Passion, networking, and research may all be of some benefit, but certification is more likely to create tangible career opportunities."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "162",
        "Question": "After identifying a job posting in his or her field of specialty, a diabetes nurse has submitted a letter of application and a résumé. What is the primary function of a letter of application?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  To introduce the applicant to the employer in a personal way",
        "Choice 2": "B)  To state why the nurse left his most recent position",
        "Choice 3": "C)  To demonstrate the nurse's work ethic",
        "Choice 4": "D)  To summarize the content of the résumé in a succinct way",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A letter of application provides the opportunity for a nurse to reveal a bit of his or her personality and connects his or her experience to the position's requirements. The purpose is not primarily to summarize the résumé or demonstrate a work ethic. It is inappropriate to state reasons for leaving previous positions in a cover letter."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "163",
        "Question": "During her final clinical placement, a nursing student worked with two of her fellow students to plan a health fair that took place in a local community center. How should she best characterize this activity on her résumé?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  “I was a member of the steering committee for a community health fair.”",
        "Choice 2": "B)  “Organized a community health fair.”",
        "Choice 3": "C)  “I have strong organizational skills.”",
        "Choice 4": "D)  “Assisted with the organization of a community health fair.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Option B provides the most succinct and action-oriented description of the activity. Option A lacks an action verb, while option C is imprecise and not descriptive. Option D is less direct and less action oriented than option B."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "164",
        "Question": "A nursing student who has held a variety of nonnursing positions is scheduled to graduate in a few weeks and is searching for a nursing job. The student has responded to a posting at a local hospital that asks for two references. Which of the following individuals would be the best choices for these two references?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A trusted coworker and a nurse who supervised the student during a preceptorship",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A family friend who knows the student well and the associate dean of the nursing school",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The two work supervisors with whom the student has the strongest rapport",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A nursing instructor and the supervisor of the student's latest job",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A primary reference should be an instructor from your basic educational program. This person would be able to affirm your ability in the nursing field. Another reference should be someone who has employed you and who can describe your work habits and effectiveness as an employee. Coworkers and family friends are not normally appropriate references."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "165",
        "Question": "In response to her recent job application, a nurse has been contacted by a member of the hospital's human resources (HR) department in order to schedule an interview. The nurse should",
        "Choice 1": "A)  bring several copies of her résumé to the interview.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  ask the HR representative how she should dress for the interview.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  do research so that she can avoid asking questions during the interview.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  ask the interviewers about their work history and areas of career interest.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Take several copies of your résumé with you to the interview. You may want to refer to it, or you may find it appropriate to leave a copy with someone. It is best to dress formally rather than asking for direction in this matter. It is appropriate to ask questions during an interview, but these should not focus on the work of the interviewers."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: DMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 5: The World of Healthcare Employment1.  What is the basic tenet of “shared governance”?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  It allows nursing staff and management to be involved in decision-making.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  It establishes the control of the institution over the actions of the nursing staff.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  It allows the administrative decision area to be controlled by management.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  It supports the traditional role of the supervisor as one who hires, evaluates, promotes, and fires.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Shared governance may be viewed as a system in which nurses have organizational autonomy as reflected in control over their practice, and have input into decision relating to patient care. It is a professional practice model in which both the nursing staff and the nursing management are involved in decision-making, as opposed to the administrative decision area being controlled by management. In this way, it is an alternative to traditional supervision models and hierarchies.",
        "Test Number": "166"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "167",
        "Question": "A nurse is assigned for the care of each patient from the time the patient is admitted to the hospital until that patient's discharge. What system of care delivery is most likely in place?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Functional care",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Primary care",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Modular care",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Team care",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In a pattern of primary care, one nurse was assigned the responsibility for the care of each patient from patient admission until that patient's discharge. The primary nurse was responsible for initiating and updating the nursing care plan, patient teaching, and discharge planning. An associate nurse worked with this same patient on other shifts and on the primary nurse's day off, carrying out the plan of care developed by the primary nurse."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "168",
        "Question": "Nurses working in a hospital initiate a negotiating session in which they offer to take a pay cut to allow management to provide job security and to hire more nurses to alleviate understaffing. What is the term for this type of session?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Interest-based bargaining",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Collective action bargaining",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Concession bargaining",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Good faith bargaining",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Concession bargaining is a process in which there is an explicit exchange of reduced labor costs for improvements in job security. This specific tradeoff is not a characteristic of interest-based bargaining, collective action bargaining, or good faith bargaining."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "169",
        "Question": "Nurses decide to go on strike to try to force improvement in the quality of patient care in their facility. Once the strike is resolved, what are their options for being rehired by the facility under the “reinstatement privilege” that is in effect in their contract?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  They will be rehired after the strike whether or not it is decided that the strike was lawful.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  They will be rehired after the strike as positions become available provided they have not engaged in unfair labor practices.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  They will be rehired to replace nurses hired during the strike who were hired to replace them.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  They will be rehired at their former job as soon as the strike is resolved.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A reinstatement privilege is a guarantee offered to striking employees that they will be rehired after the strike as positions become available, provided that they have not engaged in any unfair labor practices during the strike, and provided that the strike itself is lawful."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "170",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements accurately reflects the general use of the grievance process by nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Grievances usually are related to interpretations of a contract or to policies and procedures.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Although either the management or an employee can file grievances, in most instances it is management that initiates the case.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A grievance involves informal talk between the management and the employee until the issue is resolved.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Employees may have grievances about the contract negotiation process itself.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A grievance is a circumstance or action believed to be in violation of a contract (or of policies of an institution if a contract is not in place). Grievances usually are related to interpretations of a contract or policies and procedures and they are usually initiated by employees. Although resolution may begin with an informal talk, this proceeds to a formal process if resolution is not achieved."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "171",
        "Question": "As part of the development of a new inner-city clinic, a group of nurses and members of other health disciplines have drafted a mission statement for the clinic. This statement will most likely specify",
        "Choice 1": "A)  the priorities for the health of the identified population.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  the main goals and functions that the organizers envision for the clinic.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  the philosophies and beliefs that underlie the existence and functioning of the clinic.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  the health outcomes that the organizers see as currently lacking in the community.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The purpose of an organization is often expressed in the form of a mission statement, which outlines what the organization plans to accomplish, including its goals and function. This may or may not identify the philosophy of the organization, specific health outcomes, or priorities for the health of residents."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "172",
        "Question": "Which of the following conditions must be met in order to ensure the efficient and effective operation of a healthcare organization?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Span of control must be kept as narrow as possible.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The chain of command must be explicitly and clearly delineated.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The formal organizational structure must closely mimic the informal relationships that exist (the “grapevine”).",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Registered nurses must occupy positions in employee, middle management, and executive roles.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The effective operation of a healthcare organization requires a detailed and clear chain of command. A narrow span of control is not always preferable to broader spans of control and formal structure does not necessarily have to replicate informal structures, though each should be acknowledged and recognized. It is certainly possible, and potentially beneficial, for nurses to occupy a variety of roles in the organizational hierarchy but this is not a precondition for successful organization."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "173",
        "Question": "A nurse has concerns about some of the practices on the hospital unit and met with the unit manager to explain these concerns. After the meeting, the nurse felt misunderstood and rebuffed by the manager. How should the nurse determine who in the organization to meet with next?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Consult with the hospital bureaucracy",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Enlist the help of a union representative",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Ask colleagues about who is most influential in the organization",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Refer to the hospital's chain of command",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The chain of command represents the path of authority and accountability from individuals at the top of the organization to those at the base of the organization. The nurse should most likely meet with the person who is above the manager in the chain of command. The hospital bureaucracy, the union, and the persons who are informally influential are less likely to help the nurse identify the appropriate person with whom to meet."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "174",
        "Question": "There is general agreement on a postsurgical unit that the admission assessment template that is used is lengthy, unwieldy, and includes many parameters that are not relevant to the care of the patient population on the unit. Which of following aspects of amending the assessment template best exemplifies the concept of shared governance?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Managers and nurses cooperatively make a change and share accountability for the outcomes.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The unit manager consults with nurses and members of other disciplines prior to changing the document.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The decision-making process reflects the chain of command that exists at the hospital.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nurses collectively present the change in practice to the manager, who is then accountable for the outcomes of the change.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Shared governance encompasses a collaborative model of decision-making and shared accountability for the outcomes of these decisions. It does not involve nurses announcing an independent change to management or management being solely accountable for the decisions of others. Shared governance is not necessarily linked to the chain of command in an organization."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "175",
        "Question": "The staff, the administrators, and the executives of a large, urban hospital are currently celebrating the fact that the hospital has recently been granted Magnet Recognition by the American Nurses Credentialing Center (ANCC). This designation suggests that the hospital",
        "Choice 1": "A)  pays nurses higher wages than the national median.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  has lower staff turnover than most hospitals.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  integrates the principles of evidence-based practice into care.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  has a committed and responsive bureaucracy.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  While all of the given options may underlie or contribute to a hospital's Magnet designation, low staff turnover is one of the key attributes of such a hospital. Magnet Recognition is not explicitly based on high wages, effective bureaucracy, or evidence-based practice."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "176",
        "Question": "A nurse who has a baccalaureate degree in nursing has begun working at a hospital in which the principles of primary care nursing are used to organize care. Which of the following actions should the nurse anticipate?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Performing the most complex nursing tasks on the unit for all of the patients",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Taking action to ensure that neither too much nor too little care is provided for each patient",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Directing a team of practical (vocational) nurses and unlicensed care providers",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Being responsible for specific patients from the time of their admission to the time of discharge",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In a pattern of primary care, one nurse is assigned the responsibility for the care of each patient from patient admission until that patient's discharge. Patient care is not fragmented according to complexity, as in functional nursing. Collaboration of a group of RNs, PNs. and UAPs is characteristic of team nursing. Tight control of the amount of care a patient receives is a key characteristic of case management."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "177",
        "Question": "Collective bargaining has a long history in nursing. Which of the following milestones in the history of collective bargaining resulted from the 1974 amendment of the Taft-Hartley Act (Labor Management Relations Act)?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Nurses were granted the right to form unions and engage in collective bargaining.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The maximum length of a work week and the minimum nursing wage were established.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Nursing was formally recognized as a professional occupation.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nonprofit hospitals were obliged to bargain with nurses around wages and working conditions.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Under the 1974 amendment of the Taft-Hartley Act, nonprofit hospitals were required to bargain with nurses for better salaries and working conditions. The formation of unions and the recognition of nursing as a profession predated this act. The 1974 amendment did not specify wages and hours of work."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "178",
        "Question": "Contracts are essential to the maintenance of high quality care in healthcare institutions. As well, they are necessary to protect the interests of nurses who provide this care. Which of the following issues is most likely to be addressed in a contract for nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The process that should be followed when distributing overtime work",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The obligation of nurses to participate in nursing research",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The details of the organizational structure of a hospital",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The relationships among nurses, physicians and members of other health disciplines",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Contracts commonly address such issues as overtime work. Relationships between care providers, participation in research, and organizational structure of a hospital are issues that are normally outside the purview of a nursing contract."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "179",
        "Question": "Despite the long history of collective bargaining in the nursing profession, many nurses have concerns regarding membership in a collective bargaining unit. Which of the following statements by nurses best conveys one of the primary concerns that are prevalent among nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  “I think that physicians recognize our value and sufficiently advocate for our best interests.”",
        "Choice 2": "B)  “I think that a collaborative model results in higher wages than a confrontational model such as collective bargaining.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  “I'm not sure that joining a union is congruent with the philosophy of the nursing profession.”",
        "Choice 4": "D)  “In the end, I think that the costs of being in bargaining unit outweigh the potential benefits.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Among the major issues of collective bargaining that affect the nursing profession is the fact that some nurses see collective bargaining as unprofessional. The other most common concerns involve the matter of which bargaining group will represent nursing when nurses participate in collective bargaining, the question of whether to join a union when one exists, and the issue of the role of the supervisor."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "180",
        "Question": "Nurses, as well as individuals outside the profession, have sometimes expressed concern around the involvement of state nurses associations in collective bargaining. What factor most often underlies such concerns?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  State nurses associations lack the legal authority to engage in bargaining though this has been their traditional role.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  State nurses associations tend to be unaware of many of the issues that nurses face when providing care.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  It can be difficult to reconcile the professional obligations of nurses associations with their role in bargaining.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Few practicing nurses participate in the activities of state nurses associations.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Some individuals contend that it is not realistic for state nurses associations to work with the professionalism aspect of nursing as well as with the issues of wages, benefits, and working conditions. State nurses associations do not lack the legal right to bargain and participation of nurses in the operations of state nurses associations does not directly affect their right or ability to bargain."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: EMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 6: Understanding the Healthcare Environment and Its Financing1.  Which of the following clients would be a good candidate to receive care in an assisted-living facility?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A 30-year-old victim of a car accident who has been in a coma for the past 2 months.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A 78-year-old widower who is living independently but needs help with preparing meals, doing laundry, and remembering to take his medications.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A husband and wife approaching retirement age who have no difficulty with ADLs but desire to “age in place.”",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A 72-year-old woman diagnosed with Alzheimer disease who is described by her daughter as having “good days and bad days.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The assisted-living facility provides care for those needing help with up to three ADLs. In an assisted-living arrangement, the resident can maintain maximum independence and use a shared decision-making model to decide when additional help or support is needed. A patient in a coma, an individual with significant cognitive deficits, and a couple with no difficulty in achieving ADLs would not be appropriate for assisted-living.",
        "Test Number": "181"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "182",
        "Question": "Mr. Kline is a construction worker who is recovering from surgery on his dominant hand that he injured on the job. Which member of the healthcare team would the nurse contact to help Mr. Kline learn how to feed himself using modified utensils?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Registered physical therapist",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Doctor of osteopathy",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Registered dietitian",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Occupational therapist",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Occupational Therapists are educated in the assessment and management of ADLs, especially when assistive devices are required. A physical therapist focuses primarily on mobility and would not introduce assistive devices aimed at achieving ADLs. Osteopaths and dietitians would not manage the use of assistive devices."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "183",
        "Question": "Which of the following is a current trend related to the education and scope of practice of healthcare providers within the healthcare system?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The Flexner Report limited the involvement of hospitals in research and education of medical students, resulting in a decrease in internships and residencies.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Pressure from insurers has mandated an increased use of specialty physicians over general practice physicians.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  There is a short supply of qualified individuals in most health occupations, including nursing.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  As the healthcare system has grown more and more complex, it is imperative for one individual educated to a specific role, to manage all aspects of care.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Nurses are not the only healthcare workers in short supply. There are predicted shortages in almost all areas of healthcare over the next 15 years. As the population ages and more people enter the system due to expansion of healthcare insurance coverage, the shortages are likely to persist. The Flexner Report increased the involvement of hospitals in research and education of medical students. There is pressure to increase the involvement of general practice physicians. As the healthcare system grows more complex, it is clear that it is impossible for one individual educated to a specific role, to manage all aspects of care."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "184",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements is an accurate representation of the nature of healthcare coverage available worldwide?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  In the United States, healthcare is seen as a right or entitlement of every citizen.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  In developing nations, healthcare is adequately provided by governmental agencies and nonprofit organizations, such as the World Health Organization.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The US healthcare system has been simplified by the existence of standards for funding and controlling healthcare.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  In most of the industrialized world, governmental healthcare systems are in place to accomplish overall health outcomes.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In most of the industrialized world healthcare is seen as a right, or an entitlement, of every citizen. This stands in contrast the views of many in the United States. Developing nations often lack basic healthcare and the US healthcare has increased in complexity over the years."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "185",
        "Question": "Mr. Gomez is a patient on Medicare receiving care in a hospital following cardiac surgery. What method would be used to determine payment for the services provided for this client?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Resource utilization groups",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Minimum data sets",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Capitation",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Diagnosis-related groups",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Diagnosis-related groups (DRGs) are used to determine the payment for each Medicare client admitted to the hospital. Payment is not determined using resource allocation groups, minimum data sets, or capitation."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "186",
        "Question": "A nurse provides care in a hospital that is owned and operated by the Roman Catholic Church. According the classification system of healthcare organizations that is based on ownership, how would this hospital be classified?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Proprietary corporation",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Sole proprietorship",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Nonprofit organization",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Community organization",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Healthcare institutions that are operated by religious organizations are normally categorized as nonprofit. They are not proprietorships or community organizations."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Multiple Selection7.  The number and importance of hospitals increased greatly during the development of the American healthcare system. Which of the following phenomena have contributed to this trend? (Select all that apply.)",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Increased health literacy of the American public",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The development of more sophisticated medical technology",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Increased incidence and prevalence of chronic diseases",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The development of professional nursing",
        "Choice 5": "E)  The growth of the health insurance industry",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 2, 4, 5",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The growth of the hospital as a primary healthcare institution was the result of numerous factors, including the medical technology, the growth of professional nursing, and the emergence of the health insurance industry. This trend has not been closely linked to changes in health literacy and chronic diseases.",
        "Test Number": "187"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "188",
        "Question": "Historically, health insurance was for hospital care and related services only. What effect did this characteristic have on the health behaviors of individuals enrolled in such plans?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Some individuals neglected health promotion measures.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Many individuals began to pay out-of-pocket for superior care.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Individuals avoided hospitals because of the association of hospitals with illness.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Some individuals who qualified for Medicare did not enroll in the program.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Insurance coverage for inpatient treatment created a disincentive towards preventative measures and health promotion activities since these were nor insured benefits. The focus on inpatient care did not prevent participation in Medicare or dissuade people from visiting hospitals."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "189",
        "Question": "In 2010 the US Congress passed the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act, commonly referred to as the Healthcare Reform. This Act aims to change the provision of healthcare in the United States by",
        "Choice 1": "A)  bringing the health insurance industry under the umbrella of the federal government.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  increasing the number of nonprofit and public hospitals.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  placing limits on healthcare costs and limits on the growth of health maintenance organizations (HMOs).",
        "Choice 4": "D)  requiring every American to be enrolled in some type of health insurance plan.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Healthcare Reform set up a process through which the United States would move toward healthcare coverage for all by requiring everyone to be enrolled in some type of health plan. This goal of universal coverage is not being sought through taking control of the insurance industry, building public hospitals, or limiting the role of HMOs."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "190",
        "Question": "A 63-year-old man has qualified for Medicaid. His qualification for Medicaid will be based primarily on what factor?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  His medical history and present health status",
        "Choice 2": "B)  His income",
        "Choice 3": "C)  His employment history",
        "Choice 4": "D)  His military service",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Medicaid provides funds for healthcare for those dependent on public assistance and certain other low-income individuals. Qualification is not based on work history, health status, or military service."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "191",
        "Question": "A hospital is currently undergoing scrutiny in terms of a number of hospital healthcare outcomes. Which of the following would be considered an outcome?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The ratio of care providers to managers and administrators in the hospital",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The incidence of nosocomial infections in the hospital",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The demographics of the population that the hospital serves",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The major sources of revenue for the hospital",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Outcome measures are specific, measurable aspects of healthcare that show the effectiveness of the system as a whole. An example of an important outcome measure is the incidence of nosocomial infections in a care setting. The staffing mix, the demographics of the community, and the revenue sources of the hospital may be important data but they are not considered to be outcomes."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "192",
        "Question": "Historically nurses have had limited power in the healthcare system. How can a nurse best exercise power to move the provision of healthcare in a positive direction?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  By participating in shared governance",
        "Choice 2": "B)  By providing evidence-based care",
        "Choice 3": "C)  By establishing collaborative relationships with physicians",
        "Choice 4": "D)  By becoming accredited in a specialty area",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  One of the most effective ways for nurses to effect change in the healthcare system is by taking advantage of opportunities to participate in shared governance. Accreditation, collaboration, and high-quality care are all positive actions, but they are less directly related to the exercise of power and influence."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "193",
        "Question": "There has been a great increase in the sophistication of healthcare technology in recent decades. What effect has increased technology primarily had on the provision of healthcare?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Health technologies have made healthcare more accessible to larger numbers of Americans.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  High-technology equipment requires a large capital investment in the short-term but reduces healthcare costs in the long-term.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Health technologies improve patient care and provide an incentive for innovative people to enter the healthcare field.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Sophisticated health technologies can improve patient outcomes but increase healthcare costs greatly.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Health-related technologies often have the potential to improve patient outcomes but they typically increase costs to healthcare institutions and, ultimately, to healthcare consumers. They do not normally result in decreased costs in the longer term and their ability to directly attract innovators to the healthcare industry has not been proven."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "194",
        "Question": "Many consumers and advocacy groups in the United States have raised concerns around the practices of the pharmaceutical industry. These concerns are most often motivated by the fact that",
        "Choice 1": "A)  drug research and development is conducted overseas but most drugs are sold domestically.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  residents of other industrialized countries have better availability of drugs.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  drug costs are higher in the US than in many other industrialized countries.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  pharmaceutical companies have shown an unwillingness to develop new drugs.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Drug companies often sell identical drugs in other countries for far less money than what they charge consumers in the United States, a fact that contributes to the high cost of healthcare in the United States. Overseas research and development is not a contentious issue and drug companies are continually active in the development of new drugs. Despite the high costs, the availability of drugs in the United States is unmatched."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "195",
        "Question": "Nurse T. has been providing care for Mr. James for the past several days during his admission to hospital for the exacerbation of his chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD). How can Nurse T. best help Mr. James, and other patients, navigate the healthcare system effectively and efficiently?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Encourage Mr. James to take ownership of his health and be proactive with prevention measures.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Teach patients how to use technology to minimize their reliance on care providers.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Educate patients about the varied roles that nurses can play in the provision of healthcare.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Become familiar with the organization of healthcare and apply this knowledge to patient teaching.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Nurses should become familiar with the complexities of healthcare and use this knowledge to help patients and families navigate the system. Technology and the roles of nurses of not topics that are likely to benefits patients in a tangible way. Prevention measures are important for health but they do not necessarily aid in navigating the system."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: DMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 7: Legal Responsibilities for Practice1.  Which of the following statements accurately reflects an element of the crisis surrounding liability insurance in the United States?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Professional liability insurance does not provide coverage when the nurse assists in an emergency.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Malpractice insurance premiums are not affordable for nurses in independent advanced practice and traditional nursing roles.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Laws in some states are being amended to restrict the monetary liability of any party according to the percentage of responsibility.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nurses are being named in fewer lawsuits, but the judgments being awarded are larger.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Laws in some states are being amended to restrict the monetary liability of any party according to the percentage of responsibility. Liability laws continue to be a major concern for nurses, because nurses are being named in an increasing number of suits, although the total number is still low. Nursing liability insurance tends not to be expensive and it provides coverage in emergency situations.",
        "Test Number": "196"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "197",
        "Question": "The law requires that a person give voluntary and informed consent for medical treatment. Which of the following statements accurately describes this legal obligation?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  It is the responsibility of the nurse to obtain informed consent.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Informed consent must be obtained in the form of written documentation.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A blanket consent for “any procedures deemed necessary” is usually considered adequate consent for specific procedures.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The courts do not accept the client's medical condition alone as a valid reason for withholding information when seeking consent.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Courts do not accept the patient's medical condition alone as a valid reason for withholding complete and accurate information when seeking consent. Obtaining consent is not normally a nursing responsibility. Verbal consent and implied consent may have legal standing and “blanket consent” is insufficient to cover any and every procedure."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "198",
        "Question": "A nurse working in a hospital setting is accused of malpractice. Which statement accurately represents a legal element of this type of negligence?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Malpractice is present only if a breach of duty was the cause of the harm.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  When the harm is not clear and needs to be proved in court, the legal term res ipsa loquitur is used.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Breach of duty is clearly defined as the expression of malicious intent.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A breach of duty is a failure to act as a prudent professional according to standards of care designated by the federal government.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  One of the essential elements of malpractice is a breach of duty by the professional. When the harm is so clear and the responsibility for the harm so straightforward that it does not need to be proved in court, the legal term res ipsa loquitur is used. Breach of duty is not synonymous with malicious intent. The standards by which breach of duty is evaluated are not defined by the federal government."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "199",
        "Question": "An attorney representing a client in a malpractice case attends a deposition. What might occur in this proceeding?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A sworn, verbatim record is made by a court reporter.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A settlement is made out of court.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A legal proceeding presided over by a judge takes place in a courtroom.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Damages are awarded to the plaintiff.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A deposition is a formal proceeding in which each attorney has an opportunity to question a witness outside of court, and a sworn verbatim record is made by a court reporter. A deposition is not the usual venue for a settlement or the awarding damages. A trial, not a deposition, is a legal proceeding presided over by a judge that takes place in a courtroom."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "200",
        "Question": "A nurse is called to testify as an expert witness in a malpractice suit. Which of the following guidelines contains prudent advice for this nurse?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Volunteer as much information as possible when explaining medical procedure.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Use medical jargon as appropriate to describe the treatment provided by the defendant.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Pause during the testimony to allow your attorney to object if appropriate.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Discuss your testimony with the opposing attorney before the court date.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A nurse who is testifying should listen carefully to the entire question before answering and pause to let your attorney object if appropriate. The nurse should not offer additional information voluntarily or use medical jargon unless it is necessary. Testimony is not discussed with the opposing attorney prior to a court date."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "201",
        "Question": "A nurse is aware that the nurse practice act in her state provides the legal framework for her scope of practice. A nurse practice act is an example of",
        "Choice 1": "A)  common law.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  constitutional law.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  enacted law.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  judicial law.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Enacted law includes all bills passed by legislative bodies; nurse practice acts in the various states are examples of enacted law at the state level. A nurse practice act is not an example of constitutional law or common law. Judicial law consists of decrees or judgments from the courts."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "202",
        "Question": "The federal Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) of 1996 addresses patient rights within the healthcare system. Which of the following actions may constitute a violation of HIPAA?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A nurse identifies a patient whom he recently cared for on his Facebook page.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A nurse completes a charting entry without providing her initials after the entry.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A nurse inserts a central venous catheter without the consent of the patient.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A nurse makes a crude comment to a patient while providing morning hygiene.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  HIPAA specifically addresses matters related to patient privacy and confidentiality. Identification of a patient by a nurse would be considered a violation of confidentiality. Failing to sign documentation is not a contravention of HIPAA. Making inappropriate comments and performing interventions without consent are both serious violations of professionalism, but these are less likely to be addressed by HIPAA."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "203",
        "Question": "The risk manager at a large, university hospital has become aware that there may be a discrepancy between a longstanding protocol on one of the hospital units and the nurse practice act of the state. Which of the following statements regarding the legal standing of institutional policies is most accurate?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Institutional policies do not have legal standing.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Institutional policies supersede enacted law but do not supersede common law.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Established policies may be considered common law by a court",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Discrepancies between policies and legislation are usually resolved by professional associations such as a board of nursing.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Established agency policies may be considered the standard of practice for that agency and, therefore, common usage (common law) by the court, and may become important as a basis for legal decisions. However, policies do not normally have the power to supersede enacted laws. Discrepancies are ultimately the jurisdiction of the courts, not professional associations."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "204",
        "Question": "Nursing practice is subject to a wide variety of laws and regulations. Which of the following actions is the clearest violation of criminal law?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A nurse left a patient's bed in a raised position and the patient subsequently fell.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A nurse withheld opioids from a patient and then sold them.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A nurse left the unit before her replacement had arrived.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A nurse applied restraints to a patient in alcohol withdrawal without first obtaining an order.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Thefts and the sale of controlled substances are not only violations of professional standards but also crimes. Abandoning patients, performing interventions without orders, or committing an action that leads to injury are most often violations of civil law."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "205",
        "Question": "On a night shift, a nurse who provides care in an inpatient psychiatric setting admitted a patient with a recent history of violence but placed the patient in a two-bed room. The patient subsequently attacked and injured the other patient in the room. Which of the following principles will be considered in the court's determination of liability?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The nurse may be held liable if institutional factors are not noted to have contributed to the situation.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The nurse is exempt from liability if institutional protocols specify that room allocation is a nursing responsibility.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The nurse may be held liable provided the action was a crime.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The nurse may be held liable if the action constituted a violation of the standard of care.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A violation of the standard of care is likely to create a situation of legal liability for a nurse. The violation need not be a crime, however. Institutional factors and protocols do not negate the nurse's potential liability"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "206",
        "Question": "Mrs. Howe, age 59, had a bilateral mastectomy with axillary node dissection and was discharged home 2 days later with drains in situ. Contrary to the nurses' predischarge teaching, Mrs. Howe attempted to remove one of her drains independently once output ceased, resulting in pain, tissue trauma, and bleeding. Mrs. Howe claims that her injuries were the result of negligence by the nurses on the unit. How would the court apply the principle of comparative negligence in this case?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The court would determine what proportion of the patient's injuries was the result of her own actions.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The court would compare Mrs. Howe's actions with those of a reasonable person.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The court would determine whether it was medically appropriate to discharge Mrs. Howe with her drains still in situ.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The court would decide if the nurses on the postsurgical unit are legally obliged to teach patients.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In the application of comparative negligence, the courts determine what percentage of injury resulted from a patient's negligence and what part rested with the nurse, and reduce the damage award accordingly. The court would also likely examine the patient's actions in light of those of a reasonable person, but this is not a direct application of the concept of comparative negligence. The court would not likely focus on the appropriateness of the patient's discharge or the nurses' abilities to teach patients."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "207",
        "Question": "Mr. Yamata was recently admitted to the hospital after a fall in which he suffered a fracture of his femoral head. Over the past 2 days, he has begun to refuse care. Which of the following factors is most significant in the determination of Mr. Yamata's legal competence to refuse care?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Mr. Yamata was recently diagnosed with early-stage Alzheimer disease.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Mr. Yamata defers most of his important decisions to his oldest son.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Mr. Yamata has previously expressed a preference for complementary and alternative therapies.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Mr. Yamata attempted to transfer to the commode independently, despite the nurse's instructions to the contrary.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Cognitive ability is an important consideration in the determination of competence. The patient's preference of alternative therapies, his previous reckless behaviors, and his deference to his son are not factors that would significantly affect his legal competence."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "208",
        "Question": "An 80-year-old woman has been admitted to the emergency department after a sudden loss of consciousness and computed tomography indicates a serious ischemic stroke. The patient's son is adamant that the patient would not want thrombolytic therapy. The son would have the right to refuse this treatment on his mother's behalf if",
        "Choice 1": "A)  there is a reasonable belief that such a treatment would not result in improved outcomes for the patient.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  a durable power of attorney for healthcare names the son as a healthcare proxy.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  the son is able to show evidence that his mother was legally incompetent prior to her stroke.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  there is unanimity among other immediate family members.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A durable power of attorney for healthcare (DPOA-Healthcare) is a document that legally designates a substitutionary decision maker, should the person be incapacitated. This document may also be referred to as designating a healthcare proxy. Previous disabilities, the agreement of other family members and a low likelihood of benefit are not factors that confer legal rights for surrogate decision-making."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "209",
        "Question": "A nurse who works in the emergency department of a large, urban hospital often provides care for patients who must be temporarily restrained for their own protection. Which of the following measures lessens the chance that the nurse will be faced with a false imprisonment suit?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Utilize physical restraints whenever possible and chemical restraints only as a last resort.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Use the least restrictive means possible to restrain patients.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Delegate the management of confused and aggressive patients to unlicensed care personnel.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Have all patients sign “blanket consent” when admitted.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Any time patients pose a danger to themselves or others, the law requires that the least restrictive means available be used to protect patients and others. Physical restraints are not usually preferable to chemical restraints and neither method exempts the nurse from potential liability. It would be inappropriate to delegate the care of patients who pose a danger and “blanket consent” does not have legal standing."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "210",
        "Question": "Despite the fact that all nurses face the potential risk of being named in a lawsuit there are measures that nurses can take to significantly reduce this risk. Which of the following measures has the greatest potential to prevent a malpractice claim?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Complete continuing competence requirements on time",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Carry adequate liability insurance that provides comprehensive coverage",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Avoid interacting with clients or patients without a witness",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Maintain a high-quality standard of nursing care",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  There are many actions that nurses can take to prevent lawsuits. Paramount among these is maintaining a high standard of care. Insurance does not necessarily prevent claims, but rather mitigates the consequences of these claims. It is normally unnecessary to avoid one-on-one interaction with patients and clients and continuing competence requirements do not necessarily prevent lawsuits."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: DMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 8: Ethical Concerns in Nursing Practice1.  A mother and a daughter are taken to the emergency room for injuries suffered in a car accident. When the mother is taken to surgery, the nurse tells her that her daughter will be fine, even though she does not know the exact extent of the daughter's injuries. This nurse's actions may have been guided by which of the following ethical theories?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Social equity and justice",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Natural law",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Deontology",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Utilitarianism",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A central premise of utilitarianism is that an act is right when it is useful in bringing about a desirable or good end. In this case, instilling hope in the mother may alleviate her stress before surgery. A deontological view would condemn the nurse's actions, since deontology proposes that ethical decision-making is based on moral rules and unchanging principles (i.e. that lying is categorically wrong). Social equity and natural law are not reflected in the nurse's decision to temporarily deceive the patient.",
        "Test Number": "211"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "212",
        "Question": "A client has advance directives for a DNR code (do not resuscitate). When the nurse is caring for this client, the client's wife asks him to “do everything in your power to keep my husband alive.” This nurse is most likely to experience which of the following moral challenges?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Values clarification",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Ethical dilemma",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Values conflict",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Nonmaleficence",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  An ethical dilemma is any situation in which guiding moral principles cannot determine which course of action is right or wrong. In this case, there is a conflict between the client's wishes and that of his wife, a situation that causes duress for the nurse. Values clarification, values conflict, and nonmaleficence are not at the root of the situation the nurse faces."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "213",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements accurately reflects one of the primary provisions of the ANA Code for Nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The administrators of the healthcare facility are responsible and accountable for individual nursing practice.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The physician determines the appropriate delegation of tasks consistent with the nurse's obligation to provide optimum patient care.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The nurse's primary commitment is to the employing agency.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The nurse owes the same duties to self as to others.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The nurse owes the same duties to self as to others, including the responsibility to preserve integrity and safety, to maintain competence, and to continue personal and professional growth. The Code does not place primary ethical responsibility with administrators or physicians nor does it claim that the nurse's main commitment is to the employer."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "214",
        "Question": "A nurse helps a client work through an ethical dilemma by using an ethical decision-making framework. Which of the following statements describes a component of this process?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The steps of this process are distinctly different from those of the nursing process.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Most ethical problems have one possible solution.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The nurse uses the framework of his or her own values to assist the clients to make a decision.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The facts of a situation make a difference in the options that are possible.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  When attempting to make ethical decisions, it is important to have as much information about the unique situation as possible because the facts of the situation make a difference in what options are possible. The steps in ethical decision-making mimic those of the nursing process. The nurse should not impose his or her values on clients and most ethical problems have more than one potential solution."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "215",
        "Question": "Which of the following is an accurate guideline for reporting the chemical dependency of a colleague?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Confront the person you suspect, and offer assistance in obtaining treatment.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Be sure beyond any doubt that a problem exists.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Rely on an informed supervisor to assume responsibility for the problem.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Be aware that help and rehabilitation are only offered to the person need it following disciplinary proceedings.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Usually, once you have notified your supervisor, he or she will assume responsibility for the problem. When planning to report, you do not have to be sure beyond any doubt that a problem exists. Confrontation is often ill-advised and rehabilitation may accompany or precede discipline."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "216",
        "Question": "A nurse on a palliative care unit has attended an educational inservice on ethics. Which of the following statements most accurately describes the concept of ethics?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Ethics offers a process that can be used to guide behavior.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Ethics is the expression of social and culture values, priorities, and norms.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Ethics is the basis for evaluating personal character.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Ethics is the tangible application of religious and spiritual truths.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Ethics offers a formal process for answering the question about what one ought to do in a given situation. Ethics is not considered to be simply an expression of cultural or religious principles and it does not specify criteria for evaluating an individual's character."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "217",
        "Question": "Nursing involves close interaction between nurses and patients, a situation which can create the potential for boundary violations. Which of the following situations most clearly constitutes a boundaries violation?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A community health nurse continues weekly visits to a former client despite the fact that the client is no longer receiving care.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  A nurse states that she is willing to advocate to the patient's employer than the patient was genuinely ill and not feigning health complaints to gain time off work.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A nurse attends a family meeting at the hospital in which the patient and his family discuss the patient's code status.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A nurse contacts a social worker without the patient's knowledge because of admissions the patient has made about her substandard living conditions.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Continuing contact with a patient outside of the domain of care is a boundaries violation. Informing an employer that a patient was ill is not likely a boundaries violation, since the nurse is reporting facts with the patient's permission. Nurses often participate in family meetings and referrals made without a patient's knowledge are not a violation of boundaries."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "218",
        "Question": "A few weeks ago, a nurse worked a shift with a colleague during which three oxycodone tablets went missing from the narcotic cupboard. As well, the nurse has noted that the colleague has sometimes documented the administration of oxycodone to patients only to have the patients continue to complain of pain. The nurse suspects that the colleague is taking the oxycodone from the unit for personal use. How should the nurse best follow up these suspicions?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Organize coworkers and the colleague's family members to carry out an intervention",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Contact representatives from the state board of nursing",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Report these suspicions to the unit supervisor",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Confront the colleague with these suspicions",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Reasonable suspicions of chemical abuse should be reported to a nurse's immediate supervisor. Confrontation, either face-to-face or in a group setting, should normally be avoided. It would be premature to contact the state board of nursing."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "219",
        "Question": "Mr. Bains is a 70-year-old man who has been recently diagnosed with colon cancer. Mr. Bains is adamant that he does not want to undergo chemotherapy or radiotherapy, citing the unpleasant side effects and the absence of a guaranteed cure. His wife, however, is distraught that he would “give up so quickly” and begs the nurse to convince him to pursue treatment. Which of the following ethical principles would underlie the nurse's decision to respect Mr. Bains' informed choice?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Beneficence",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Nonmaleficence",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Fidelity",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Autonomy",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Autonomy involves the right of self-determination or choice, independence, and freedom. As such, an expression of autonomy would involve respecting the patient's wishes even if they are unusual or opposed by family members. Beneficence and nonmaleficence denote doing good and avoiding harm. Fidelity refers to the obligation to be faithful to the agreements and commitments."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "220",
        "Question": "An obstetrical-gynecological nurse has moved to a new region and is seeking employment. The nurse opposes the ethics of elective abortion and refuses to participate in the procedures. However, the only hospital in the immediate area is the site of numerous elective abortions. How should the nurse account for this fact when seeking employment?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Ask the hospital administrators to exempt her from participating in any aspect of abortion.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Consider applying for a nursing position that will not involve abortion.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Begin working at the hospital and attempt to change the hospital politically.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Accept a position at the hospital and then make her position known to supervisors.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Nurses have a responsibility to avoid situations that they know would be personally problematic for ethical reasons. It would be unreasonable to accept a position and expect special treatment. As well, it would be disingenuous for the nurse to accept a position without disclosing her stance or to accept a position with the intent of enacting a change."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "221",
        "Question": "A patient with a long-standing diagnosis of renal failure has declared her intention to stop hemodialysis. Because of the ethical ramifications of this, the care team has begun the process of making an ethical decision. This process should begin by",
        "Choice 1": "A)  eliciting input from impartial individuals from outside the hospital setting.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  explaining the major concepts of ethics to the patient and her family.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  clearly identifying the essential elements of the ethical problem.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  confirming the patient's cultural and religious background.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A process for ethical decision-making begins with the clear identification of the situation at hand. This should precede the involvement of other individuals or an exploration of the patient's culture and religion. It would not likely be helpful to explain ethical concepts to the patient."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "222",
        "Question": "The care providers and administrators of a hospital have struggled to find an appropriate response to a patient who has a long history of being admitted to hospital and then leaving against medical advice. Under the direction of the hospital ethics committee, a plan was created and implemented. What action should the care providers and the ethics committee take after the plan has been implemented?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Continue to implement the plan when necessary",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Assess the outcomes of applying the plan",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Seek input from the hospital's risk manager",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Report to the state board of nursing about the manner in which the situation was handled",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Implementation of an ethical decision should always be followed by evaluation and appraisal of the course of action that was chosen. Involvement of the hospital's risk manager should take place during the planning phase. It would not normally be necessary to involve the state board of nursing in this decision-making process."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "223",
        "Question": "A nurse is working a shift with a colleague who has a nursing student participating in the care of the colleague's patients. The nurse notices that the colleague has spent much of the morning on the computer at the nurse's station and is allowing the student to perform every aspect of the patients' care. How should the nurse best respond to this colleague?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Speak directly to the colleague about these observations.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Ask the nursing student if she feels like the colleague's patients are receiving good care.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Report the colleague to the supervisor of the unit.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Create a written report recording the facts of the morning.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Lapses in the quality of care are best addressed by speaking directly and privately to the person involved. The individual's response to this discussion would determine whether involvement by supervisors is necessary. It would be inappropriate to involve the nursing student in this matter, given the power differential that exists between the nurse and the student."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "224",
        "Question": "Tom is a nurse who provides care on a busy medical unit. One of Tom's colleagues has just confided in him that she erroneously gave her patient 16 mg of immediate-release hydromorphone instead of 16 mg of extended-release hydromorphone. She tells Tom that she does not want to report the incident and so she plans to simply monitor the patient's level of consciousness and respiratory status closely for the next several hours. Which of the following statements best describes Tom's required response to this situation?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Tom has a professional and legal responsibility to report this.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Tom should strongly encourage his colleague to document this error.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Tom is obliged to assist his colleague with follow-up assessments.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Tom has no legal obligation to respond, but he should take advantage of this teaching opportunity.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Incidents that have the potential for patient harm create a legal and moral obligation for the nurse to report. Simply encouraging the colleague to document this matter or helping with assessments are insufficient responses."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "225",
        "Question": "After working for several months on a geriatric subacute medicine unit, a nurse has come to the conclusion that substandard care has become accepted as the norm by the majority of nurses as well as their immediate supervisors. The nurse's attempts to discuss and address some significant and persistent lapses in care have been rebuffed by nurses and supervisors alike. What should the nurse do next?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Enlist the support of current and previous patients",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Resign from the unit",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Contact media outlets",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Further discuss the benefits of practice improvements with the nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A final alternative to a workplace problem may be to resign. It is normally inappropriate to involve patients. Further discussions with the nurses are unlikely to be beneficial, given the systemic nature of problems on this unit. Contacting the media is rare and appropriate response."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Base Settings: Brownstone DefaultInformation Field: Client NeedsInformation Field: Cognitive LevelInformation Field: DifficultyInformation Field: Integrated ProcessInformation Field: ObjectiveInformation Field: Page and HeaderHighest Answer Letter: DMultiple Keywords in Same Paragraph: NoChapter: Chapter 9: Bioethical Issues in Healthcare1.  A doctor performs an abortion on a woman who is unable to carry a fetus to term because of a severe risk to her health. What is the term for this type of abortion?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Spontaneous abortion",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Elective abortion",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Therapeutic abortion",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Legal abortion",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A therapeutic abortion is performed for medical reasons while elective abortion is undertaken for personal reasons. Both are legal under legally appropriate circumstances. A spontaneous abortion results from natural causes.",
        "Test Number": "226"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "227",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements accurately describes a characteristic of the stem cell?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Stem cells are not able to renew themselves.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Stem cells give way to specialized cells.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Stem cells are committed to conduct a specific function.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Pluripotent stem cells are derived from the patient's own DNA.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A stem cell is a special kind of cell that is able to renew itself and give rise to specialized cell types. These cells, unlike most other cells in the body, such as those of the heart or skin, are not committed to conduct a specific function. The cell remains uncommitted until it receives a signal to develop into a specialized cell. Pluripotent cells have the ability to differentiate into any type of cell found in the body; they are not directly derived from DNA."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "228",
        "Question": "A nurse is asked to obtain informed consent for a procedure to be performed on a patient who has not yet been told her cancer is terminal. Which of the following is an issue surrounding guidelines to the amount of information that should be given to this patient?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Under a paternalistic model of care, the locus of decision-making resides with the patient's family, who are responsible for informing the patient.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Physicians basically agree on the amount and nature of the information that should be provided to the patient, but disagree on its delivery.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  It is the responsibility of the nurse to inform the patient of matters that have not been discussed with the physician.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  In some cultures, both physicians and families strongly believe that those who are ill should be protected from bad news.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In some cultures, both physicians and families strongly believe that those who are ill should be protected from bad news. A paternalistic model of care denigrates the role of the patient's family. The nurse is not always obliged to compensate for missing information and there is controversy surrounding the appropriate nature of information to provide to patients and/or families."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "229",
        "Question": "Which of the following guidelines supports current practice when using behavior control on a client?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Methods of influence that decrease a person's ability to think rationally should only be used when a client is not acting in his or her own best interest.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  In many cases, the use of psychosurgery to effect a permanent change is recommended over drug therapy.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Methods of influence that keep relevant facts from a client should only be used with the consent of the client's significant others.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Methods that work through the cognitive and affective structure of a person are preferred treatment.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Although there are widely varying opinions regarding the appropriate application of behavior control in clients with mental illness, it is generally agreed that nonsurgical options are preferred over surgical interventions. Family consent does not necessarily warrant the withholding of information from clients. Interventions do not have the goal of reducing a person's ability to think rationally."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "230",
        "Question": "Which of the following best describes the term rationing of healthcare?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Providing healthcare only to those who can afford it.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  Providing a planned approach to the use of limited resources.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Asking consumers to prioritize their use of healthcare resources.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Requiring consumers to carry private insurance to cover healthcare not covered by the public sector.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Most consider rationing to be a planned, thoughtful approach to a limited supply. This does not involve mandatory insurance or restricting care to those who can afford it. Individual preferences should be considered, but the philosophy of rationing does not require consumers to prioritize their own use of resources."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "231",
        "Question": "During the various clinical placements that a nursing student has had during a baccalaureate program, the student has become increasingly aware of how significant bioethical issues are in the delivery of healthcare. Which of the following factors has contributed most significantly to the importance of bioethical issues in healthcare?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Increased health literacy among healthcare consumers",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The development of new healthcare technologies",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The politics of proposed universal healthcare in the United States",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Increased incidence and prevalence of chronic health problems",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Bioethical issues have always been present, but their importance has grown alongside changes in technology. The phenomena of increased health literacy, chronic diseases, and politics are not among the primary factors that have increased the visibility of bioethics."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "232",
        "Question": "The history of family planning in the United States has been characterized by controversies, many of which continue to the present day. Which of the following statements most accurately conveys an aspect of these controversies?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  Protestant Christianity advocates a careful and deliberate control of the size of a population.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints (Mormons) teach that only nonhormonal contraceptive methods may be used.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The Roman Catholic church states that the purpose of all sexual activity is the creation of new life.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  Judaism teaches that family planning should be the exclusive domain of wives.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The Roman Catholic Church has strongly advocated that the natural purpose of sexual activity is to create new life and nothing should try to interfere with that potential. The members of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints (Mormons) do not differentiate between the hormonal and nonhormonal methods of contraception. Some conservative Protestant Christians and conservative Muslims also advocate allowing God to plan families and do not use birth control methods. Judaism does not explicitly teach about family planning."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "233",
        "Question": "In vitro fertilization (IVF) is an example of assisted reproductive technology (ART) that has become more common in recent decades. However, IVF is not without controversy. Which of the following aspects of IVF is most often contentious?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The number of fertilized ova normally exceeds the number of children that a woman desires.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The success or failure of IVF rests on the genetic characteristics of sperm that comes from a man unknown to the woman undergoing the procedure.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  IVF is most common among women who have a history of elective abortion.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  IVF is often undertaken without the consent of a woman's partner.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  In IVF, several fertilized ova are usually returned to the uterus to ensure that at least one will survive. If more than one implants successfully, it is possible for the mother to have multiple births. The alternative to this potential is the abortion of one of more of the implanted ova, a practice that is controversial. IVF may or may not use sperm from an anonymous donor and is not normally performed without the awareness or consent of the woman's partner. IVF is not normally necessitated by prior elective abortions."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "234",
        "Question": "The advent of technology has made it increasingly difficult to define the exact point at which death occurs. Which of the following is currently the most commonly-accepted criterion for death?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The cessation of blood circulation",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The inability to perform respiration spontaneously",
        "Choice 3": "C)  Persistent lack of interaction with outside stimuli",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The cessation of brain activity",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Brain activity, with few exceptions, is said to be nonexistent when flat electroencephalographic tracings are obtained over a given period, often 48 hours. After this point, the person may be considered dead, although machines may be supporting the vital functions of respiration and circulation. Many institutions now accept this definition of cerebral death and use it as a basis for turning off respirators and stopping other treatments. It is also used as a basis for determining death when there is a desire to recover organs from the patient."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "235",
        "Question": "After several rounds of unsuccessful in vitro fertilization (IVF), a couple has chosen to explore the use of a surrogate mother. In most states, this would involve",
        "Choice 1": "A)  a civil court case in which a judge grants permission for the couple to proceed with surrogacy.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  the use of a surrogate who is selected from a state-recognized list of approved surrogates.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  the drafting of a detailed contract between the surrogate mother and the couple.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  a covert and illegal arrangement between the couple and the potential surrogate mother.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  A formal, contractual relationship is usually established. The couple who wishes to have the child agrees to pay all expenses associated with the pregnancy, and to pay the surrogate mother an agreed sum for her time and involvement In a few states, however, such arrangements are illegal. A court case is not required and approval of a particular surrogate mother is not the jurisdiction of the state."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "236",
        "Question": "A nurse is aware that there are numerous bioethical issues involved in the practice or euthanasia. Which of the following events most clearly constitutes active euthanasia?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A woman chooses not to phone 911 when her elderly husband become unconscious in the home.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  At his and his wife's request, a doctor provides a man with a fatal dose of phenytoin.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A nurse withholds cardiopulmonary resuscitation (CPR) from a patient in light of the patient's DNR order.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A family decides against treating their mother's sepsis because of her low potential for recovery.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Negative, or passive, euthanasia refers to a situation in which no extraordinary or heroic measures are undertaken to sustain life. This includes applying DNR orders, opting not to phone 911, or choosing to withhold treatment of an acute illness. Active euthanasia, however, occurs in a situation in which the physician prescribes, supplies, or administers an agent that results in death."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "237",
        "Question": "There are differing viewpoints surrounding the withholding and withdrawal of treatment. Which of the following situations constitutes the most acceptable application of the withholding and/or withdrawal of treatment?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  A competent patient expresses a desire that hydration and nutrition be discontinued.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The potential benefits of a patient's antibiotic therapy exceed the likely risks.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  A patient's family will be forced to pay out-of-pocket for the patient's life support due to a lack of insurance coverage.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  A patient's children wish to discontinue the patient's treatment because they have lost faith in the care team.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Most healthcare organizations and institutions agree that a competent patient has the right to withdraw or withhold treatment, especially when such treatment is unlikely to result in positive outcomes. When benefits exceed risks, treatment is normally undertaken. Financial concerns and interpersonal disputes should ideally not form the basis of such life-and-death decisions."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "238",
        "Question": "The practice or organ transplantation is associated with several important bioethical issues. The ethics of transplantation primarily surround the fact that",
        "Choice 1": "A)  organ transplantation does not guarantee positive outcomes.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  only a small number of the organs in the body are amenable to transplantation.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  transplantation is a treatment of last resort.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  the demand for organs greatly exceeds the available supply.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Ethical issues in organ transplantation most often surround the fact that there is a very finite supply of available organs and a larger number of potential recipients. As a result, difficult decisions must be made around the allocation of a valuable and scarce resource. The fact that transplantation is a measure of last resort is less salient. The facts that transplantation does not guarantee recovery and that only certain organs may be transplanted are not central to these difficult decisions."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "239",
        "Question": "The Human Genome Project (HGP) has been the subject of extensive attention, both in the healthcare community and in the public at large. Which of the following bioethical issues is most applicable to the HGP?",
        "Choice 1": "A)  The HGP was conducted with little participation from developing countries.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  The HGP did not result in the number or quality of medical applications that were originally hoped.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  The HGP provides information that has the potential to influence the selection of behavioral attributes.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  The HGP calls into question many of the practices that have been accepted in Western medicine.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  The ethical and bioethical concerns that can evolve from the HGP are many and varied. Among them are the issues of access to and use of new genetic information and technology to improve health, the research that would involve human participants, and the implications of the discovery of genetic contributions related to diseases, non-disease attributes, and various behavioral traits such as cognition, mental illness, diurnal rhythms, and aging for how we understand health and illness. The project did not discount common medical practices or fail to produce useful applications. The Western focus of the project was not widely criticized."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "240",
        "Question": "Gene therapy has been touted as one of the most promising therapies for healthcare in the 21st century. At present, gene therapy is primarily limited by",
        "Choice 1": "A)  the dynamic nature of the human genome.",
        "Choice 2": "B)  objections to gene therapy that are posed by religious groups.",
        "Choice 3": "C)  the difficulty in producing safe, consistent therapeutic results.",
        "Choice 4": "D)  the fact that only around a dozen known human diseases have a genetic basis.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Explanation": "Feedback:  Although gene therapy is a promising treatment option for a number of diseases (including inherited disorders, some types of cancer, and certain viral infections), the technique remains risky and is still under study to ensure its safety and effectiveness. The human genome is essentially consistent between individuals. Hundreds of diseases have a genetic basis and opposition from organized groups has not been the primary brake on the development of gene therapy."
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When describing the NCLEX examination, which of the following would the instructor include?",
        "Choice 1": "Includes content standardized for baccalaureate education in nursing",
        "Choice 2": "Measures minimum technical competencies for safe entry into basic nursing practice",
        "Choice 3": "Tests content determined appropriate for practice entry by the American Nurses Association",
        "Choice 4": "Requires different passing scores for RNs educated at the ADN level than at the BSN level",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Test Number": "241"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "242",
        "Question": "Which of the following would a prospective student expect to find when examining a typical associate degree in nursing (ADN) program?",
        "Choice 1": "A maximum requirement for 120 semester hours or 180 quarter units",
        "Choice 2": "Similar curricular content as BSN programs, with greater clinical hours",
        "Choice 3": "Completion possible within 18 months to 2 years",
        "Choice 4": "Additional coursework for preparation to practice in multiple settings",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "243",
        "Question": "Raising the educational level for entry into professional nursing",
        "Choice 1": "Should be relatively easy due to unanimous support",
        "Choice 2": "Is likely to have a short-term effect of reducing the current nursing shortage",
        "Choice 3": "May increase recruitment to and retention in the field in the long run",
        "Choice 4": "May destabilize the nursing workforce due to increased job satisfaction for ADNs",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "244",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects most of the RNs working in the United States today?",
        "Choice 1": "They have received an associate degree in nursing (ADN).",
        "Choice 2": "They have adequate educational preparation for roles in leadership and management.",
        "Choice 3": "There are significant differences in care provided by ADN- and BSN-prepared nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "Separate NCLEX examinations are supported for BSN- and ADN-educated nurses.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "245",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is teaching a group of students about “grandfathering” that may result if the entry level to nursing practice is raised. The instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students describe it as which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "A way to allow an individual to continue to practice his or her profession or occupation after new qualifications has been enacted into law",
        "Choice 2": "A mandate for nurses with greater education and knowledge levels to be responsible for supervising those prepared at lower levels",
        "Choice 3": "A necessary requirement by state and federal laws when educational entry requirements change",
        "Choice 4": "A concept that is not supported by most professional nursing associations that support raising the entry level for professional nursing practice",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "246",
        "Question": "Transitioning from a predominantly ADN educational model of nursing education to a baccalaureate model",
        "Choice 1": "Is already occurring in a seamless, integrated manner that maximizes the use of educational resources",
        "Choice 2": "Will be relatively inexpensive, given that adequate institutions of higher learning already exist to meet this need",
        "Choice 3": "Will require the development of alternative pathways for RN education for learners who may not otherwise be able to pursue additional nursing education",
        "Choice 4": "Is primarily limited to nursing education in the United States",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "247",
        "Question": "Which of the following would a nurse identify as a positive force for raising the educational entry level in professional nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "There is often little if any difference in pay between BSN- and ADN-educated nurses.",
        "Choice 2": "Patient outcomes are better when ADN representation in the staffing mix is high.",
        "Choice 3": "Consumers generally have no understanding of the entry-to-practice issue in nursing.",
        "Choice 4": "The entry level in nursing is significantly lower than for other health professions.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "248",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing for a test on levels of preparation for nurses. Which of the following if stated by the students as reflecting Mildred Montag's view of associate degree educational programs indicates that the students have understood the information?",
        "Choice 1": "Preparation for beginning, technical practitioners who would provide direct, safe nursing care under the supervision of the professional nurse in an acute-care setting",
        "Choice 2": "Preparation of advanced professional nurses capable of the independent judgment and autonomy required to successfully function as RNs in the 21st century",
        "Choice 3": "Preparation of professional registered nurses who could function safely in a variety of health care settings including acute care, home care, and public health",
        "Choice 4": "Preparation of broadly educated registered nurses with an understanding of cultural, political, economic, and social issues affecting patients and health care delivery",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "249",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the suggestions of the 1965 position paper by the American Nurses Association for nursing education?",
        "Choice 1": "The education of all those who are licensed to practice nursing should take place ininstitutions of higher education.",
        "Choice 2": "Minimum preparation for beginning professional nursing practice should be the associate degree in nursing.",
        "Choice 3": "Minimum preparation for beginning technical practice should be the baccalaureate degree in nursing.",
        "Choice 4": "There was no need for assistant nurses in the health care occupations.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "250",
        "Question": "When reviewing the demographics related to ADN and BSN programs, which of the following would be an expected finding?",
        "Choice 1": "ADN program graduates tend to be younger than graduates of baccalaureate programs.",
        "Choice 2": "ADN program graduates tend to be more diverse in race, gender, and age than baccalaureate-prepared nurses.",
        "Choice 3": "ADN program graduates are more likely to be single or divorced than baccalaureate graduates.",
        "Choice 4": "ADN program graduates typically have at least twice as many children as nurses educated in baccalaureate programs.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "251",
        "Question": "Which of the following was the most likely cause fueling the debate about entry to practice?",
        "Choice 1": "Brown's publication of Nursing for the Future",
        "Choice 2": "Mildred Montag's dissertation",
        "Choice 3": "ANA's 1965 position paper",
        "Choice 4": "The Veterans Administration's requirement for BSN",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "252",
        "Question": "A nurse is presenting a discussion to a group of local high school students about nursing and the various types of educational programs available. One of the students asks, “What's the difference between a nurse with an associate's degree and one with a baccalaureate degree?” Which response would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "“Both can be licensed as registered nurses, but an associate's degree education requires morenursing coursework units.”",
        "Choice 2": "“Both take the same test for licensure, but a nurse with a baccalaureate degree must get a higher score to pass.”",
        "Choice 3": "“Employers have routinely paid baccalaureate degree nurses a higher starting salary than associate's degree nurses.”",
        "Choice 4": "“The outcomes for patients cared for by baccalaureate-prepared nurses appear to be better than those for associate's degree nurses.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "253",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be considered an important factor related to changes in health care that would emphasize the need for a BSN degree for entry to practice?",
        "Choice 1": "Shift from community settings to acute care",
        "Choice 2": "Rapid advances in health care technology and complexity",
        "Choice 3": "The need to work as a dependent member of the team",
        "Choice 4": "Dramatic increase in curative care",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "254",
        "Question": "After reviewing different health professions and their required entry-level degree, a student identifies which profession as requiring the lowest degree level?",
        "Choice 1": "Pharmacy",
        "Choice 2": "Social work",
        "Choice 3": "Speech pathology",
        "Choice 4": "Nursing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "255",
        "Question": "Which of the following organizations recommends that the nursing profession have multiple entry points?",
        "Choice 1": "American Nurses Association (ANA)",
        "Choice 2": "National League for Nursing (NLN)",
        "Choice 3": "Nurse Alliance of Service Employees International Union (SEIU)",
        "Choice 4": "American Nephrology Nurses' Association (ANNA)",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "256",
        "Question": "When reviewing the factors involved with obtaining advanced education, which of the following would a nurse expect as being the chief obstacle?",
        "Choice 1": "Cost",
        "Choice 2": "Age of the nurse",
        "Choice 3": "Gender",
        "Choice 4": "Ethnic minority status",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "257",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about the two levels of preparation for registered nurses, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which of the following as a characteristic of technical nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "Four-year program of education in a college or university",
        "Choice 2": "Achievement of a baccalaureate degree",
        "Choice 3": "In-depth coverage of nursing research",
        "Choice 4": "Ability to provide care in acute-care settings",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "258",
        "Question": "A group of students are reviewing material about the proliferation of ADN education in preparation for a quiz the next day. The students demonstrate understanding of the material when they identify which of the following as a characteristic of the 1960s?",
        "Choice 1": "Associate's degree programs were just beginning.",
        "Choice 2": "Diploma education was on the decline.",
        "Choice 3": "The majority of nurses were educated in colleges and universities.",
        "Choice 4": "Enrollment in baccalaureate programs was decreasing.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "259",
        "Question": "A nurse manager who is preparing a presentation for a group of staff nurses about educational opportunities for returning to school will be integrating research information about incentives for doing so. Which of the following would the nurse include?",
        "Choice 1": "Equality of treatment",
        "Choice 2": "Lack of recognition for past education",
        "Choice 3": "Creation of a credible professional identity",
        "Choice 4": "Working within a structured format",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "260",
        "Question": "Which of the following effects has been identified as reflective of the education gap between nursing and other professions?",
        "Choice 1": "The perspective that nursing is elitist due to lack of entry standards",
        "Choice 2": "Increased appeal of nursing as an emerging workforce",
        "Choice 3": "View of nurses as second-class citizens in health care",
        "Choice 4": "Licensure not equating with professional status",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "A group of nursing students are reviewing information about transition to practice programs. Which of the following if identified by the group as a program indicates the need for additional review?",
        "Choice 1": "Residencies",
        "Choice 2": "Externships",
        "Choice 3": "Internships",
        "Choice 4": "Orderlies",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Test Number": "261"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "262",
        "Question": "Based on research studies and recommendations of organizations, transition to practice programs would least likely focus on which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Basic patient care skills",
        "Choice 2": "Work organization",
        "Choice 3": "Priority setting",
        "Choice 4": "Emergency response",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "263",
        "Question": "Which of the following would typically characterize an employer-based nurse residency program?",
        "Choice 1": "Emphasis on teaching specialty-specific skills",
        "Choice 2": "Open to new graduates entering critical care",
        "Choice 3": "Focus on building critical thinking skills",
        "Choice 4": "Inclusion of nurses returning to the workforce",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "264",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about the movement to provide transition to practice programs, the instructor determines that additional teaching is needed when the students identify which organization as being most involved?",
        "Choice 1": "Versant",
        "Choice 2": "American Nurses Association",
        "Choice 3": "National Council of State Boards of Nursing",
        "Choice 4": "Advisory Board Company",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "265",
        "Question": "Which of the following recommendations were cited by Benner and colleagues in conjunction with their work for the Carnegie Foundation related to transition to practice programs?",
        "Choice 1": "Need for structured postgraduate programs for skill building in the real clinical setting.",
        "Choice 2": "Requirement of completion of a one year residency for in-depth knowledge development in a clinical specialty area.",
        "Choice 3": "Sponsorship of residencies for baccalaureate-prepared nurses in academic medical centers",
        "Choice 4": "Development of transition to practice programs outside of the acute care setting to that of community-based settings.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "266",
        "Question": "When describing the impact of the nation's economic recession on the hiring of new graduates, which of the following would most likely be included?",
        "Choice 1": "Greater numbers of patients opting for elective surgeries",
        "Choice 2": "Decrease in the hours worked by experienced nurses",
        "Choice 3": "Delay in retirement by many older nurses",
        "Choice 4": "Increase in hospital days and revenue",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "267",
        "Question": "A group of nursing students are developing a presentation for their class on QSEN competencies. Which of the following would the group expect to include? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Communication",
        "Choice 2": "Teamwork",
        "Choice 3": "Safety",
        "Choice 4": "Nursing process",
        "Choice 5": "Informatics",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "2, 3, 5"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "268",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be considered a common component for all school-based transition to practice programs? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Course duration of 12 to 18 weeks",
        "Choice 2": "Training for program preceptors",
        "Choice 3": "Awarding of a certification of completion",
        "Choice 4": "Opportunities to sit for NCLEX examination",
        "Choice 5": "Service partners providing liability coverage",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 2, 3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "269",
        "Question": "A group of students are preparing for a class discussion on comparing school-based transition to practice programs with those of employer-based residencies. Which of the following would the group identify as specific to the school-based programs?",
        "Choice 1": "Need for clinical sites to hire participants before attending the program",
        "Choice 2": "Implementation of a service-partner completion certificate",
        "Choice 3": "Designed intention to take the place of employer-based residency programs",
        "Choice 4": "Requirement of academia and service partnership for design and implementation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "270",
        "Question": "When evaluating the areas that may affect the sustainability of transition to practice programs, which of the following would apply?",
        "Choice 1": "Limited numbers of preceptors that clinical sites can supply",
        "Choice 2": "Increase in the numbers of clinical sites available for use",
        "Choice 3": "Decrease in workload for the school and clinical site partners",
        "Choice 4": "Wide ranging sources available for funding program costs",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "271",
        "Question": "Which of the following would most likely support the need for transition to practice programs?",
        "Choice 1": "The diminishing complexity of patient care",
        "Choice 2": "Increased focus on communication",
        "Choice 3": "Stabilization of technology",
        "Choice 4": "Patient safety as a priority",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "272",
        "Question": "The gap between the expectations of education and practice requires which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Academia to improve their curriculum objectives",
        "Choice 2": "Employers to change their expectations",
        "Choice 3": "Academic and practice shared solution strategies",
        "Choice 4": "Extension of orientation programs for new graduates",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "273",
        "Question": "Nursing, unlike other professions, does not require standardized internships. This is most likely the result of which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "The superiority of the nursing educational system across all program types",
        "Choice 2": "Need for filling vacancies due to the long-term nature of the nursing shortage",
        "Choice 3": "Employment occurring most often in the clinical facility used during schooling",
        "Choice 4": "Traditional education system as being grounded in apprenticeship like programs",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "274",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be least likely to occur as a result of a well-designed transition to practice program?",
        "Choice 1": "Ability to meet the demands of patient care",
        "Choice 2": "Decrease in onboarding",
        "Choice 3": "Decrease in staff turnover",
        "Choice 4": "Improved competencies",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "275",
        "Question": "A new graduate is preparing to participate in a transition to practice program. Which of the following would the new graduate expect to work on? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Priority setting",
        "Choice 2": "Assessment skills",
        "Choice 3": "Communication with families",
        "Choice 4": "Delegating",
        "Choice 5": "Advanced life support skills",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 3, 4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "276",
        "Question": "During a presentation about transition to practice programs, an attendee asks, “What is onboarding?” Which response by the presenter would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "“It refers to the actual number of new graduates who are being employed by the facility.”",
        "Choice 2": "“It's when a new graduate is integrated into staffing the unit for direct patient care.”",
        "Choice 3": "“It means that the new graduate has been through the routine orientation for the facility.”",
        "Choice 4": "“It involves the process of hiring a new graduate who then turns around and leaves the facility.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "277",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the concept of QSEN competencies?",
        "Choice 1": "They are the basis for determining licensure for a new graduate.",
        "Choice 2": "They allow facilities to evaluate the “employability” of a new graduate.",
        "Choice 3": "They provide a foundation for developing plans for nurses in bridging the gap to practice.",
        "Choice 4": "They are important for nursing education but are of little significance for the clinical service area.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "278",
        "Question": "In reviewing possible evaluation tools for transition to practice programs, which of the following would be considered the most important?",
        "Choice 1": "First Employer Survey",
        "Choice 2": "QSEN-based competency tool",
        "Choice 3": "NCLEX examination",
        "Choice 4": "Workplace safety checklist",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "279",
        "Question": "After a discussion about transition to practice programs, the instructor determines the need for additional clarification when the students identify which of the following as characteristic of these programs?",
        "Choice 1": "Guided intensive clinical experience is integrated with prior educational learning.",
        "Choice 2": "The cost of the program for many clinical sites is justified by the increased nurse retention.",
        "Choice 3": "Programs are standardized so that all participants received the same core training.",
        "Choice 4": "The program is intended to repeat that which was taught in nursing school.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "280",
        "Question": "The nurse is reviewing the recommendations of the Institute of Medicine's (IOM) report on the Future of Nursing. Which of the following would the nurse expect to find? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Nurse participation in transition to practice program after completing an advanced practice degree program",
        "Choice 2": "Program development focusing on other settings in addition to the acute care setting.",
        "Choice 3": "The emphasis on the need for nurses to participate in lifelong learning.",
        "Choice 4": "Limiting partnerships with physicians when redesigning health care in the United States.",
        "Choice 5": "Redirecting of graduate medical education funding programs from diploma nursing programs to support the implementation of residencies.",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 2, 3, 5"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When reviewing information about mandatory staffing, which of the following would best reflect the current status?",
        "Choice 1": "Many of the states in the United States have moved toward imposing mandatory licensed staffing requirements.",
        "Choice 2": "Texas has already enacted legislation requiring mandatory staffing ratios affecting hospitals and long-term care facilities.",
        "Choice 3": "Research suggests that the average number of patients assigned to RNs for care in acute-care facilities has actually decreased in the past decade, but patients are much sicker.",
        "Choice 4": "Consumers and legislators, not nurses, have urged implementation of mandatory staffing ratios because most nurses feel current staffing levels are minimum but adequate.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Test Number": "281"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "282",
        "Question": "Benchmark research completed by Aiken and colleagues in 2002 found",
        "Choice 1": "There was no significant difference in patient outcomes when staffing at six patients per nurse rather than four.",
        "Choice 2": "There was no rise in patient morbidity until patient-to-nurse ratios exceed eight to one.",
        "Choice 3": "There is no direct, provable link between nurse-to-patient ratios and mortality rates from preventable complications.",
        "Choice 4": "In hospitals with higher patient-to-nurse ratios, the likelihood of dying within 30 days of admission and mortality complications were increased.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "283",
        "Question": "When evaluating the pros and cons of mandatory regulation of RN-to-patient ratios, which statement most accurately reflects the beliefs of the critics?",
        "Choice 1": "Such ratios protect the most basic elements of the public health care consumers take for granted.",
        "Choice 2": "Implementing ratios will improve the nursing shortage, at least temporarily over the short term.",
        "Choice 3": "Mandatory staffing will lead to a reduction in hospital services and increased expenses due to the need to pay overtime.",
        "Choice 4": "Mandatory staffing ratios create significant opportunity costs that encourage employers and payers to respond to market forces.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "284",
        "Question": "Developing draft regulations for minimum staffing ratios was challenging for the California Department of Health Services (CDHS) because",
        "Choice 1": "Although standardized patient classification system data were available, hospitals were unwilling to submit the data.",
        "Choice 2": "Hospitals had not been required to use patient classification systems prior to the passage of staffing-ratio legislation and had no data.",
        "Choice 3": "California Healthcare Association and the California Nurses Association agreed on the minimum ratios, but consumer advocate groups pressed for lower patient-to-nurse ratios.",
        "Choice 4": "Proposals received by CDHS suggested a wide range of minimum staffing ratios and even more widely differing estimates of implementation costs.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "285",
        "Question": "Implementing the ratio legislation in California proved to be difficult because",
        "Choice 1": "Nursing unions balked when courts ruled that both LVNs and RNs could be used to meet minimum staffing ratios.",
        "Choice 2": "The current nursing shortage made it impossible to meet the mandated ratios.",
        "Choice 3": "Legislation was introduced to delay implementation of the minimum 1:5 nurse-to-patient staffing ratio on medical-surgical units.",
        "Choice 4": "A significant number of hospitals in the state had to close their doors due to the cost of implementing staffing ratios.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "286",
        "Question": "When reviewing the California legislation, legal clarification became necessary due to the “at-all-times” clause, which referred to which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Maintaining minimum staffing ratios throughout the day including during breaks and lunches",
        "Choice 2": "Having at least one registered nurse on duty at all times",
        "Choice 3": "Ensuring no more than a 1:4 nurse-to-patient ratio on any unit in acute-care hospitals",
        "Choice 4": "Having to keep emergency departments open 24 hours a day",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "287",
        "Question": "Which of the following best describes waivers to the mandatory staffing ratios that were part of the California legislation?",
        "Choice 1": "Were typically not allowed for any institution",
        "Choice 2": "Were sought by many of the larger hospitals because of the financial costs",
        "Choice 3": "Were routinely granted if patient safety was not being compromised",
        "Choice 4": "Were allowed but only to rural hospitals under very strict conditions",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "288",
        "Question": "An instructor is describing compliance oversight by the California Department of Health Services in acute-care hospitals to a group of students. Which of the following would most likely occur if a hospital was found to be out of compliance with the mandatory minimum staffing ratios?",
        "Choice 1": "The hospital would be forced immediately to close its doors until it could demonstrate compliance.",
        "Choice 2": "The facility is given 48 hours to correct the deficiency after being fined substantially.",
        "Choice 3": "The hospital must discharge or transfer patients within 24 hours to reach a level of compliance.",
        "Choice 4": "There is no penalty or monetary fine for a violation unless serious injury or death occurs.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "289",
        "Question": "Which of the following is suggested based on the initial research findings as to the effectiveness of mandated staffing-ratio implementation in California?",
        "Choice 1": "Staffing ratios remained essentially unchanged.",
        "Choice 2": "Staffing ratios increased the number of worked nursing hours per patient day in hospitals.",
        "Choice 3": "Hospitals had less difficulty meeting ratio requirements than originally anticipated.",
        "Choice 4": "The “at-all-times” clause was not a significant hardship.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "290",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the position taken by the Joint Commission on mandated staffing ratios?",
        "Choice 1": "Supportive, arguing that more states should follow California's model",
        "Choice 2": "Criticism that ratios as not flexible enough due to failure to address diversity of U.S. hospitals",
        "Choice 3": "Watchful waiting by other states until California's experience can be fully evaluated",
        "Choice 4": "Direct opposition to the implementation because of the current nursing shortage",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "291",
        "Question": "When reviewing the various alternatives to legislated minimum staffing ratios, which of the following would a nurse expect to find as the position of the American Nurses Association?",
        "Choice 1": "A workload system that encompasses existing variables for safe staffing",
        "Choice 2": "Use of Continuous Quality Improvement to ensure adequate staffing",
        "Choice 3": "Use of market-based incentives for hospitals to maximize nurse staffing",
        "Choice 4": "Evaluation of number, competency, and skill mix of staff related to needed services",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "292",
        "Question": "A nursing administration is using the legislation in California as a guide to implement appropriate minimum registered nurse staffing ratios for the labor and delivery area. Which of the following ratios would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "1:1",
        "Choice 2": "1:2",
        "Choice 3": "1:4",
        "Choice 4": "1:6",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "293",
        "Question": "Various studies have examined the link between staffing mix and patient outcomes. Which of the following best describes the most common finding associated with this research?",
        "Choice 1": "Inadequate numbers of RNs has little effect on patient outcomes.",
        "Choice 2": "Mortality dropped with increased staffing numbers of nurse aides.",
        "Choice 3": "Increased numbers of RNs in staffing mix led to improved patient outcomes.",
        "Choice 4": "A decreased prevalence of infections was found with less staffing.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "294",
        "Question": "After describing the arguments for and against mandated minimum staffing, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which of the following as a major argument by critics?",
        "Choice 1": "Patient safety is unrelated to the staffing ratios.",
        "Choice 2": "Workload of nurses is difficult to translate into numbers.",
        "Choice 3": "Standardized ratios do not provide consistency in approach.",
        "Choice 4": "Overall cost of care would increase exponentially.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "295",
        "Question": "A nurse is reviewing the events leading up to implementing the California legislation. In addition to identifying ratios for safe staffing, the legislation also addressed which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Use of LPNs/LVNs as part of the staff mix",
        "Choice 2": "Possible cost incentives",
        "Choice 3": "Restrictions for procedures of unlicensed personnel",
        "Choice 4": "Patient classification systems",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "296",
        "Question": "A nursing student is reading a journal article about mandatory staffing ratios and states that have implemented legislation related to staffing. Which state would the student be least likely to read about?",
        "Choice 1": "Ohio",
        "Choice 2": "Alabama",
        "Choice 3": "Connecticut",
        "Choice 4": "Nevada",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "297",
        "Question": "As student is reviewing the recommendations of the ANA to maintain sufficient staffing. The student demonstrates a need for additional study when the student identifies which of the following as a recommendation?",
        "Choice 1": "Creation of staffing plans by administrative personnel",
        "Choice 2": "Legislative mandates for regulation of nurse to patient ratios",
        "Choice 3": "Staffing plans that reflect the needs of the patient population",
        "Choice 4": "Disclosure of staffing levels to a regulatory body",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "298",
        "Question": "As part of the Hospital Patient Protection Act (2008), which nurse-to-patient ratio would be appropriate for pediatrics?",
        "Choice 1": "1:2",
        "Choice 2": "1:3",
        "Choice 3": "1:4",
        "Choice 4": "1:5",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "299",
        "Question": "A student is reviewing research in preparation for a debate on minimum mandatory staffing relies on the study by Aiken et al. (2002) as a basis for arguing in support of this issue. Which of the following best describes the student's use of this study?",
        "Choice 1": "It is considered the seminal work for supporting legislation of minimum staffing ratios.",
        "Choice 2": "It provided the most comprehensive study on costs, staffing, and use of unlicensed personnel.",
        "Choice 3": "It supported findings from research performed by the Agency for Healthcare Quality and Research.",
        "Choice 4": "It reinforced what was already known about the need for mandatory staffing ratios in acute-care facilities.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "300",
        "Question": "Which of the following would a nurse identify as the primary driving force in dictating changes in the RN skill mix in hospitals?",
        "Choice 1": "Rise in use of unlicensed assistive personnel",
        "Choice 2": "Growing nursing shortage",
        "Choice 3": "Patient outcomes",
        "Choice 4": "Economics",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Which of the following would a nurse manager use to describe mandatory overtime to a group of new nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "Any hours worked over 40 hours per week",
        "Choice 2": "A problem unique to nursing as a result of its repetitive shortages",
        "Choice 3": "Forced requirement to work more hours than are standard",
        "Choice 4": "Prohibited by the Fair Labor Standards Act (FLSA) of 1938",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Test Number": "301"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "302",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing information about the Fair Labor Standards Act. Which of the following would they identify as a component?",
        "Choice 1": "The time standard for the health care industry is the same as for other industries.",
        "Choice 2": "Each state can determine the amount of overtime and appropriate compensation.",
        "Choice 3": "Amount of overtime is limited to four hours per day",
        "Choice 4": "Overtime pay should be at least one and one-half times the regular rate of pay",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "303",
        "Question": "When reviewing the literature related to legislation to restrict mandatory overtime for nurses, which of the following would be an expected finding?",
        "Choice 1": "Every state has defeated it since it has been introduced.",
        "Choice 2": "The majority of states have passed restriction legislation.",
        "Choice 3": "The state of California, so far, is the only state with legislation in effect.",
        "Choice 4": "Fourteen states have enacted legislation with 16 states having restrictions.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "304",
        "Question": "After teaching a class on mandatory overtime, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which practice area as most commonly having more mandatory overtime?",
        "Choice 1": "Labor and delivery",
        "Choice 2": "Operating room",
        "Choice 3": "Medical/surgical unit",
        "Choice 4": "Pediatrics",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "305",
        "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about mandatory overtime in nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "When overtime is mandated by an employer, the employee typically has little or no planned notice, often experiencing high levels of fatigue and increased errors.",
        "Choice 2": "The risk of making an error as a result of working mandatory overtime does not increase until the nurse has worked at least 16 consecutive hours.",
        "Choice 3": "Although nurses often work 12-hour shifts, double shifts (16 hours) are most commonly confined to rare emergencies.",
        "Choice 4": "Mandatory overtime has been shown to reduce nurse dissatisfaction and turnover because pay rewards are so great.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "306",
        "Question": "Which of the following best describes the risk for the charge of patient abandonment with overtime?",
        "Choice 1": "Can be filed in all states of the United States if the nurse refuses to work mandatory overtime",
        "Choice 2": "Is an “empty threat” by employers because nurses are protected if they identify a concern for patient safety as their reason for declining mandatory overtime",
        "Choice 3": "Are more likely to be valid if the nurse accepts an assignment (mandatory overtime) and then changes his or her mind and decides to leave",
        "Choice 4": "Cannot result in termination of a nurse's employment, as specified by the National Labor Relations Act",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "307",
        "Question": "When describing a nurse's professional duty, which of the following would be included?",
        "Choice 1": "Placing patient needs above one's own, even if nurse is now at increased personal risk",
        "Choice 2": "Placing employer's needs above one's own, even if it places patients at risk",
        "Choice 3": "Ensuring the nurse is mentally and physically able to provide minimum safe care",
        "Choice 4": "Demonstrating a service orientation that entails altruism",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "308",
        "Question": "During a class discussion, a student asks, “How do most collective bargaining agents view mandatory overtime?” Which of the following would an instructor need to integrate into the response?",
        "Choice 1": "It is allowed, but employees should receive at least double pay when it happens.",
        "Choice 2": "Mandatory overtime is something that should be eliminated entirely.",
        "Choice 3": "Typically, guidelines are left to the employer's discretion if reviewed with each collective bargaining contract renewal.",
        "Choice 4": "Mandatory overtime is an unavoidable alternative during severe nursing shortages.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "309",
        "Question": "While reviewing a journal article about mandatory overtime and nurses, a student reads that many of the nurses report working more than how many hours when mandatory overtime is involved?",
        "Choice 1": "6",
        "Choice 2": "8",
        "Choice 3": "10",
        "Choice 4": "12",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "310",
        "Question": "A group of nursing students are reviewing information about state legislation and restrictions on the use of mandatory overtime for nurses. The students demonstrate a need for additional review when they identify which state as have enacted legislation?",
        "Choice 1": "Alaska",
        "Choice 2": "Maryland",
        "Choice 3": "West Virginia",
        "Choice 4": "California",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "311",
        "Question": "After teaching a class about the Fair Labor Standards Act (FLSA) of 1938, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students state which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "There is a ceiling limit as to the amount of overtime hours that can be worked by any one individual.",
        "Choice 2": "Individuals cannot be dismissed from their job if they decide to decline to work overtime.",
        "Choice 3": "For each hour worked over 40 hours, payroll employees must be paid time and a half the regular pay rate.",
        "Choice 4": "Persons refusing to work overtime can receive sanctions from the employer.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "312",
        "Question": "When reviewing the literature about mandatory overtime in nursing, which of the following most likely would be noted?",
        "Choice 1": "It has become the standard operating procedure in many agencies.",
        "Choice 2": "Use of mandatory overtime is fairly standardized among institutions.",
        "Choice 3": "Overtime work generally involves work greater than 30 hours per week.",
        "Choice 4": "The reliance on mandatory overtime is gradually decreasing.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "313",
        "Question": "Which of the following employees would least likely be exempted under the most recent changes to federal overtime rules?",
        "Choice 1": "Those with the authority to hire or fire employees",
        "Choice 2": "Those whose primary duties required advanced knowledge",
        "Choice 3": "Those who are considered “learned professionals”",
        "Choice 4": "Those who provide care as hourly employees",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "314",
        "Question": "Which of the following is cited as the most common reason for nurses working mandatory overtime?",
        "Choice 1": "Increased income",
        "Choice 2": "Higher self-esteem",
        "Choice 3": "Possible patient abandonment",
        "Choice 4": "Staff allegiance",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "315",
        "Question": "The majority of research on mandatory overtime and its effects focuses primarily on working shifts of which time duration?",
        "Choice 1": "8 hours",
        "Choice 2": "10 hours",
        "Choice 3": "12 hours",
        "Choice 4": "14 hours",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "316",
        "Question": "Which of the following is necessary for a charge of patient abandonment?",
        "Choice 1": "A provider-patient relationship was established.",
        "Choice 2": "The patient was unaware of an expectation for care.",
        "Choice 3": "The provider carried out the obligation.",
        "Choice 4": "The patient remained free of injury.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "317",
        "Question": "Students are preparing for a test about mandatory overtime in nursing. The students demonstrate a need for additional study when they identify which of the following as an effect?",
        "Choice 1": "Cost reduction",
        "Choice 2": "Increased risk for errors",
        "Choice 3": "Lower productivity",
        "Choice 4": "Longer patient stays",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "318",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the current status of the use of mandatory overtime?",
        "Choice 1": "It is used fairly consistently from institution to institution.",
        "Choice 2": "It is often used as a last resort for staffing shortages.",
        "Choice 3": "Magnet hospitals required its use much less often.",
        "Choice 4": "It is a relatively new concept for nurses.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "319",
        "Question": "A perioperative nurse manager is using the AORN Position Statement for safe work and on-call practices as a guide for staffing. Which of the following would apply?",
        "Choice 1": "Direct patient care should be limited to 10 hours or less during a 24-hour period.",
        "Choice 2": "The nurse should work no more than 60 hours in a 7-day period.",
        "Choice 3": "Time off duty should allow for a maximum of 4 hours of uninterrupted sleep.",
        "Choice 4": "On-call duty hours are not included in determining the total number of hours worked.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "320",
        "Question": "After teaching a class about mandatory overtime, the instructor determines that the students have understood the concept when they identify which of the following as another term used?",
        "Choice 1": "Employment abandonment",
        "Choice 2": "Compulsory overtime",
        "Choice 3": "Mentoring",
        "Choice 4": "Socialization",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When describing workplace violence to a group of students, which of the following would the instructor include in the discussion?",
        "Choice 1": "A new phenomenon with most recent occurrences over the past decade",
        "Choice 2": "Relatively rare in health care with the potential to affect workers in all sectors",
        "Choice 3": "Directed at all health care professionals with nurses being at high risk",
        "Choice 4": "Primarily involves verbal abuse rather than physical harm in health care settings",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Test Number": "321"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "322",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be identified as a common reason for the underreporting of workplace violence?",
        "Choice 1": "Many individuals fail to recognize violence in the workplace as violence.",
        "Choice 2": "Such violence rarely results in serious or long-term injury.",
        "Choice 3": "Most individuals do not know to whom to report such violence.",
        "Choice 4": "Subordinates are afraid of repercussions because many perpetrators are management staff.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "323",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about violence in nursing, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which of the following as third-party violence?",
        "Choice 1": "Is perpetrated by outside persons entering the workplace with criminal intent, such as armed robbery for drugs or gang reprisals in emergency departments",
        "Choice 2": "Refers to the effect of violence on those witnessing violence such as family members and colleagues",
        "Choice 3": "Occurs when nurses are violent toward those in their professional care",
        "Choice 4": "Focuses on nurses' experiences in times of extreme emergencies such as biochemical/terrorist attacks",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "324",
        "Question": "A nurse manager is preparing a presentation for a group of staff nurses related to violence against female nurses. Which of the following would the nurse manager expect to include?",
        "Choice 1": "Occurs more often than against male nurses",
        "Choice 2": "Occurs less often than against male nurses",
        "Choice 3": "Occurs with the same frequency as against male nurses",
        "Choice 4": "Is almost always perpetrated by other female nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "325",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the organizational approach to violence in nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "Developing broad policies and procedures to address this problem",
        "Choice 2": "Immediately informing law enforcement of the issue",
        "Choice 3": "Developing a culture that does not condone the behavior",
        "Choice 4": "Instituting disciplinary action as deemed by the statutory organization",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "326",
        "Question": "After teaching a class on workplace violence and global approaches, the instructor determines that the students have understood the material when they identify which term as being the preferred term when referring to this issue?",
        "Choice 1": "Mobbing",
        "Choice 2": "Incivility",
        "Choice 3": "Bullying",
        "Choice 4": "Social undermining",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "327",
        "Question": "When describing the concept of violence in nursing, which of the following would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "The act of violence is the most important aspect.",
        "Choice 2": "Abuse of power often is not considered violence.",
        "Choice 3": "Statistics related to violence in nursing are highly specific.",
        "Choice 4": "The nonphysical effects are often ignored.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "328",
        "Question": "A student is reviewing information about nonphysical workplace behaviors involving nurses. Which of the following if identified by the student indicates a need for additional study about this topic?",
        "Choice 1": "Limited to patients with dementia",
        "Choice 2": "Occurs more often with male nurses",
        "Choice 3": "Is similar to incidents involving nonphysical violence",
        "Choice 4": "Occurs mainly in specialized care areas",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "329",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is describing violence in nursing. Which of the following would the instructor include in the discussion?",
        "Choice 1": "Workplace violence occurs primarily in acute care settings.",
        "Choice 2": "Most persons view workplace violence in the same way.",
        "Choice 3": "Each person's experience with violence is unique.",
        "Choice 4": "Categorizing the types of violence experienced is difficult.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "330",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be least likely to be involved with third-party violence?",
        "Choice 1": "Colleague",
        "Choice 2": "Family member",
        "Choice 3": "Significant other",
        "Choice 4": "Health care agency",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "331",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about legislative approaches to workplace violence, the instructor determines that the teaching has been successful when the students identify which country as referring to workplace violence as inappropriate behavior?",
        "Choice 1": "United States",
        "Choice 2": "Australia",
        "Choice 3": "Canada",
        "Choice 4": "United Kingdom",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "332",
        "Question": "A nurse bullies another nurse colleague. This would be categorized as which type of violence",
        "Choice 1": "Horizontal violence",
        "Choice 2": "Vertical violence",
        "Choice 3": "Third-party violence",
        "Choice 4": "External perpetrator violence",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "333",
        "Question": "A nurse is reading an article on workplace violence from several years ago that describes incidents occurring in Europe. Which term would the nurse most likely see used in the article?",
        "Choice 1": "Horizontal violence",
        "Choice 2": "Mobbing",
        "Choice 3": "Bullying",
        "Choice 4": "Workplace violence",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "334",
        "Question": "When describing violence against male nurses, which of the following most likely would be included?",
        "Choice 1": "It arises from the same forces as that for female nurses.",
        "Choice 2": "Males are often the major perpetrators of internal violence in nursing.",
        "Choice 3": "More male nurses are victims of violence than female nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "More research is needed to evaluate violence against male nurses.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "335",
        "Question": "After teaching a class of students about different types of physical and nonphysical workplace violence, the instructor determines that the students have understood the material when they identify which of the following as an example of physical violence?",
        "Choice 1": "Rudeness",
        "Choice 2": "Rumors",
        "Choice 3": "Pinching",
        "Choice 4": "Uncooperativeness",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "336",
        "Question": "As part of a presentation on workplace violence, a nurse explains that physical violence is more commonly associated with which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Nurse-to-nurse violence",
        "Choice 2": "Patient-to-nurse violence",
        "Choice 3": "Organization-to-nurse violence",
        "Choice 4": "Third-party violence",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "337",
        "Question": "A nurse who is walking from the parking lot to the health care agency is attacked and robbed at gunpoint. The nurse is a victim of which type of violence?",
        "Choice 1": "External-perpetrator violence",
        "Choice 2": "Organization-to-nurse violence",
        "Choice 3": "Patient-to-nurse violence",
        "Choice 4": "Nurse-to-nurse violence",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "338",
        "Question": "A group of nursing students are preparing a class presentation about legislation and workplace violence. Which of the following would the group include as specific to the United States?",
        "Choice 1": "Occupational Health, Safety and Welfare (Industrial Manslaughter) Amendment Bill",
        "Choice 2": "Universal Declaration of Human Rights",
        "Choice 3": "Occupational Safety and Health Act",
        "Choice 4": "International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "339",
        "Question": "A nurse is reviewing research studies related to the organizational approach to workplace violence. Which of the following would the nurse find as the main theme?",
        "Choice 1": "Inadequate working conditions",
        "Choice 2": "Trust and mistrust",
        "Choice 3": "Disciplinary shortfalls",
        "Choice 4": "Burden of staffing shortages",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When describing the impact of technology in health care, which of the following would be the major driving force?",
        "Choice 1": "Cost-savings benefit",
        "Choice 2": "Improved quality of patient care",
        "Choice 3": "Enrichment of a nurse's work life",
        "Choice 4": "Global growth",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Test Number": "340"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "341",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements best reflects robotics in contemporary health care?",
        "Choice 1": "Usually able to perform surgery without assistance from surgeons",
        "Choice 2": "Can replace the caring part of nursing practice",
        "Choice 3": "Frequently provide care that should be completed only by licensed practitioners",
        "Choice 4": "Typically serve as an adjunct to professional health care staff",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "342",
        "Question": "When describing biometrics to a group of students, which of the following would the instructor include?",
        "Choice 1": "Information chips implanted in patients are the most common type of biometrics in health care.",
        "Choice 2": "Biometrics likely will become less commonplace in the near future due to the inability of health care providers to afford the high implementation costs.",
        "Choice 3": "Biometrics reduces the confidentiality of patient information because it is often transmitted electronically.",
        "Choice 4": "One type of biometrics currently beginning to make inroads into health care is facial geometry.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "343",
        "Question": "In point-of-care (POC) testing, which of the following is true?",
        "Choice 1": "Caregivers can gather and test specimens near the patient or at the bedside and then download results via the Internet to a central clinical lab.",
        "Choice 2": "Manual documentation of test results occurs in a patient's chart and then is transmitted electronically to the nurse caring for that patient.",
        "Choice 3": "Consumers perform the test under the direct supervision of licensed health care workers.",
        "Choice 4": "This type of testing currently represents the majority of most clinical laboratories' total testing volume.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "344",
        "Question": "A nurse manager is preparing an in-service program for the unit nursing staff about using a bar coding system. Which of the following would the nurse need to integrate into the discussion?",
        "Choice 1": "Although it is beneficial to patient care, it is the most expensive method of electronic patient labeling.",
        "Choice 2": "The nurse matches his or her nametag, the bar code on the patient's identification band, and the medication to be given.",
        "Choice 3": "Few hospitals have implemented the system, but these numbers are beginning to increase gradually.",
        "Choice 4": "It is a highly efficient means for labeling and storing drugs for easy retrieval but holds little promise for reducing medication errors.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "345",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements best reflects computerized physician/prescriber order entry (CPOE)?",
        "Choice 1": "Designation as one of three key patient-safety initiatives by the Leapfrog Group, a conglomeration of non–health care Fortune 500 company leaders",
        "Choice 2": "A clinical software application designed specifically to help providers communicate electronically with all members of the health care team",
        "Choice 3": "Saving of ordering time for providers but more likely to result in medication errors than orders written on paper because so many providers have poor typing skills",
        "Choice 4": "A commonplace occurrence in contemporary urban hospitals and health care agencies",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "346",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about technology in health care, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students describe “smart” objects as which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Relatively small, portable computers for patient access to health care information at home",
        "Choice 2": "Everyday objects with easy-to-use software inserted for some degree of intelligence",
        "Choice 3": "Advanced robots designed to mimic the behavior and voice of a human being",
        "Choice 4": "Highly sophisticated computer technologies with virtually unlimited intelligence",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "347",
        "Question": "When describing the benefits of the electronic health record (EHR), which of the following would be included?",
        "Choice 1": "Has safeguards to assure patient health information confidentiality and security",
        "Choice 2": "Generally can be implemented with minimal cost",
        "Choice 3": "Allows workers to access quality-improvement information",
        "Choice 4": "Is easy to integrate in contemporary health care organizations",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "348",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects telehealth?",
        "Choice 1": "Only a small percentage of home care in the United States is suitable for telehealth of some form.",
        "Choice 2": "Telehealth has resulted in decreased flexibility and, more often, less personalized care for patients.",
        "Choice 3": "Telehealth may provide greater opportunities for nurse–patient encounters, particularly for homebound, isolated individuals.",
        "Choice 4": "The practice of telephone nursing involves use of multiple standardized tools to assess outcomes.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "349",
        "Question": "While preparing a presentation for a local community group about the impact of technology on health care, a nurse is planning to describe “expert patients.” Which of the following would the nurse integrate into the discussion?",
        "Choice 1": "The term refers to patients who have the confidence, skills, information, and knowledge to play a central role in the management of their own health care.",
        "Choice 2": "They are typically relegated to a somewhat passive and dependent role in their health care decision making.",
        "Choice 3": "It refers to patients who think they are well informed about health care matters but are not.",
        "Choice 4": "This patient needs less guidance from his or her health care provider due to access to expert opinions and information from the Internet.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "350",
        "Question": "After teaching an in-service to a group of staff nurses about point-of-care bar coding, the presenter determines that the group has understood the material when they state which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "“Bar codes can become unreadable if they become smudged and wet.”",
        "Choice 2": "“The risk of encountering wireless dead spots is virtually eliminated.”",
        "Choice 3": "“The bar-coding safeguards are extremely difficult to circumvent.”",
        "Choice 4": "“The nurse becomes the first line of defense in preventing errors with this system.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "351",
        "Question": "A health care provider using CPOE enters an order for a test and receives a message that this test is contraindicated for the particular patient. This is an example of which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Personal digital assistant",
        "Choice 2": "Wireless local area networking",
        "Choice 3": "Bluetooth technology",
        "Choice 4": "Clinical decision support",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "352",
        "Question": "Which of the following is considered to be the most significant variable impacting the adoption of the electronic health record?",
        "Choice 1": "Financial burden",
        "Choice 2": "Resistance to change",
        "Choice 3": "Communicability among computers",
        "Choice 4": "Ownership of information",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "353",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the views of critics on the use of technology in health care?",
        "Choice 1": "Technology is more expensive in the initial set-up period, making it cost prohibitive.",
        "Choice 2": "Agencies that adopt more technology are more likely to have less desirable outcomes.",
        "Choice 3": "Most nurses aren't consulted because their health care technology knowledge is limited.",
        "Choice 4": "The education needed to be truly competent in the use of all technology is never ending.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "354",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about patients' use of the Internet for access to medical information, the instructor determines that the students need additional teaching when they state which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "There are concerns about the accuracy of the information patients obtain.",
        "Choice 2": "Most patients typically understand the information available to them.",
        "Choice 3": "Patients may tend to self-diagnose themselves inappropriately.",
        "Choice 4": "The opportunities for being better informed have increased significantly.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "355",
        "Question": "A nurse is investigating the specialty of nursing informatics. Which of the following would the nurse expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Standardized set of courses to obtain a doctoral degree",
        "Choice 2": "Long history of educational requirements to become specialized",
        "Choice 3": "Integration of nursing, computer, and information sciences",
        "Choice 4": "Primary function focusing on implementing electronic health records",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "356",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is describing biomechatronics. Which of the following would the instructor include in the description?",
        "Choice 1": "Devices that mimic how the body works",
        "Choice 2": "Robots that perform minor medical procedures",
        "Choice 3": "Use of physical characteristics for identification",
        "Choice 4": "Credit card-sized devices with a chip containing a person's clinical history",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "357",
        "Question": "After describing the field of biometrics to a group of students, the instructor determines the need for additional teaching when the group identifies which of the following as an example?",
        "Choice 1": "Fingerprints",
        "Choice 2": "Retinal scans",
        "Choice 3": "Voice recognition",
        "Choice 4": "Passwords",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "358",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be a characteristic of a mental service robot used as a direct care provider?",
        "Choice 1": "Ability to assist with patient hygiene",
        "Choice 2": "Ability to change behavior based on how it is treated",
        "Choice 3": "Ability to help elderly patients move around",
        "Choice 4": "Ability to provide care in remote areas",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "359",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about electronic and wireless communication, the instructor determines a need for additional teaching when the students identify which of the following as an example?",
        "Choice 1": "PDA",
        "Choice 2": "WLAN",
        "Choice 3": "Bluetooth",
        "Choice 4": "Clinical decision support",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When describing the issue of medical errors in health care, which of the following would most likely be included?",
        "Choice 1": "Medical errors received national attention with the passage of Medicare in 1965.",
        "Choice 2": "Medication errors are the leading cause of adverse events in patients.",
        "Choice 3": "The overwhelming majority of medical errors are the result of provider negligence.",
        "Choice 4": "Most medical errors are the result of organization, system, or process failures.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Test Number": "360"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "361",
        "Question": "A student is reviewing the literature involving benchmark studies related to medical errors. Which of the following would the student expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Thomas, Studdert, Newhouse, et al., found that the more than one half of adverse events found could not be prevented.",
        "Choice 2": "“To Err Is Human” reported that the elderly were at greatest risk for medication errors, experiencing harmful medication errors three times more often than children.",
        "Choice 3": "“To Err Is Human” found that deaths due to medical errors in the United States could be considered the eighth leading cause of death in 1999.",
        "Choice 4": "The July 2004 HealthGrades study found that medical-error statistics published by the Institute of Medicine (IOM) had overestimated the problem by as much as 50%.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "362",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is discussing the impact of the IOM's report, “To Err Is Human.” Which of the following would the instructor most likely include in the discussion?",
        "Choice 1": "Received little press at the time it was published but became the seminal work on medical errors by the year 2005",
        "Choice 2": "Resulted in U.S. Senate and House hearings on the issue within weeks of the report's release",
        "Choice 3": "Garnered immediate national attention but was fairly ineffective as a catalyst for promoting long-term change",
        "Choice 4": "Was of limited value to consumers because it was written at a level appropriate only for the scientific and academic communities of interest",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "363",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing for an examination on medical errors in health care. The students demonstrate understanding of the information when they identify which of the following as part of the IOM's four-pronged approach to reducing medical errors?",
        "Choice 1": "Progressive disciplinary consequences for employees who made errors",
        "Choice 2": "Decreasing the responsibility of oversight organizations, group purchasers, and professional groups and transferring it to health care organizations themselves",
        "Choice 3": "Identifying and learning from medical errors through both mandatory and voluntary reporting systems",
        "Choice 4": "Closing hospitals and health care practices that had more than twice the average number of medical errors",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "364",
        "Question": "A health care institution is reviewing process performance using a Six Sigma approach for safety management. The process having which sigma would show the best performance?",
        "Choice 1": "2",
        "Choice 2": "3",
        "Choice 3": "4",
        "Choice 4": "5",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "365",
        "Question": "A nurse is reviewing research related to the effects of fully disclosing a medical error. Which of the following would the nurse be most likely to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Reduced likelihood of a lawsuit",
        "Choice 2": "Increase in change in physician",
        "Choice 3": "Decreased patient satisfaction",
        "Choice 4": "Decreased physician trust",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "366",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the actions of most health care providers related to medical errors?",
        "Choice 1": "Report all of the medical errors they make or are aware of to their employer but not to the patients or families involved",
        "Choice 2": "Report all of the medical errors they make or are aware of to the patients or families involved in accordance with professional ethical guidelines",
        "Choice 3": "Are reluctant to report errors to their employer, patients, or families for fear of legal liability and/or disciplinary action",
        "Choice 4": "Appropriately hide medical errors from patients and families to reduce the legal liability of their employer",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "367",
        "Question": "To move from a “culture of blame” to one of “safety management” will require",
        "Choice 1": "Legal protections for medical error reporting to prevent voluntarily shared information from being subpoenaed or used in legal discovery.",
        "Choice 2": "Increasingly severe disciplinary penalties for employees who commit errors that harm patients.",
        "Choice 3": "That each employee keep a portfolio documenting errors he or she has made for review at his or her annual performance appraisal.",
        "Choice 4": "That organizations keep their quality-control data confidential so as not to unduly alarm consumers.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "368",
        "Question": "An in-service instructor is preparing a presentation for a group of staff nurses about reducing medical errors. The instructor is planning to describe The Leapfrog Group. Which of the following would the instructor expect to include?",
        "Choice 1": "Is the leading producer of software products in the United States directed at reducing the incidence of medical errors",
        "Choice 2": "Has endorsed the use of computerized physician/provider order entry to assist in reducing medical errors",
        "Choice 3": "Has suggested that quality of care in hospital intensive care units would improve if patients were cared for by their own personal physician",
        "Choice 4": "Is an elite group of hospitals who have made safety management organization-wide, comprehensive, pervasive, and visible",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "369",
        "Question": "Which of the following strategies would likely be most proactive in reducing the number of medical errors in an organization?",
        "Choice 1": "Development of a systems approach to medical errors that examines all causes of failure, including components, subsystems, processes, interactions, and functions",
        "Choice 2": "Development of a standardized form for all employees to use in reporting medical errors and mandate its use for all types of errors",
        "Choice 3": "Hiring of a quality-management team to investigate errors that are made and educate staff regarding how to avoid repeating those same errors",
        "Choice 4": "Purchasing of the latest technology available to complete patient care tasks and train staff how to use that technology",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "370",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing information in preparation for a test on the various national committees and groups formed to address the IOM's goals. The students demonstrate understanding of the information when they identify which of the following as being responsible for creating a list of serious reportable events?",
        "Choice 1": "Floyd D. Spence National Defense Authorization Act of 2001",
        "Choice 2": "National Quality Forum",
        "Choice 3": "Quality Interagency Coordination Task Force",
        "Choice 4": "The National Patient Safety Foundation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "371",
        "Question": "Which of the following terms would be used to identify an injury occurring to a patient resulting from treatment?",
        "Choice 1": "Medical error",
        "Choice 2": "Medication error",
        "Choice 3": "Adverse event",
        "Choice 4": "Sentinel event",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "372",
        "Question": "A review of the results of the study of medical errors by HealthGrades in 2004 would reveal which of the following as least commonly associated with patient safety incidents (PSIs)?",
        "Choice 1": "Failure to rescue",
        "Choice 2": "Pressure ulcer",
        "Choice 3": "Postoperative sepsis",
        "Choice 4": "Accidental needle stick",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "373",
        "Question": "Which of the following would a hospital's interdisciplinary team most likely use to identify steps in the care process that might lead to error?",
        "Choice 1": "Failure mode and effects analysis",
        "Choice 2": "Root-cause analysis",
        "Choice 3": "Sentinel-event reporting",
        "Choice 4": "Quality-based purchasing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "374",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of nursing students about the National Patient Safety Goals for Hospitals, the instructor determines that the students need additional teaching when they identify which of the following as a goal?",
        "Choice 1": "Improved patient-identification accuracy",
        "Choice 2": "Reduced risk of health care–associated infections",
        "Choice 3": "Increased patient passivity in own care",
        "Choice 4": "Reduced risk of harm due to falls",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "375",
        "Question": "Based on the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services (CMS), Medicare will no longer reimburse for care related to which of the following if acquired in a hospital?",
        "Choice 1": "Myocardial infarction due to coronary artery disease",
        "Choice 2": "Urinary tract infection from a catheter",
        "Choice 3": "Peritonitis from a ruptured appendix",
        "Choice 4": "Fracture due to motor vehicle accident",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "376",
        "Question": "When describing the use of mandatory report cards, which of the following would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "They are fairly standard in the way that information is reported.",
        "Choice 2": "Most provide information about the quality of care by specific groups.",
        "Choice 3": "Similar data ratings are received regardless of the type of report card used.",
        "Choice 4": "Most focus on the use of service data and patient satisfaction ratings.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "377",
        "Question": "When describing the Patient Safety and Quality Improvement Act of 2005, which of the following would be most appropriate to include?",
        "Choice 1": "It was the first legislation passed to require bar-coding technology for patient identification and medication administration.",
        "Choice 2": "The act provided legal protections for medical-error reporting including confidential treatment of information.",
        "Choice 3": "It mandated the necessity for evidence-based hospital referrals for patients with high-risk conditions.",
        "Choice 4": "It required that patients in intensive-care units receive care by individuals called intensivists who are familiar with ICU complications.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "378",
        "Question": "A nurse is working on a hospital committee to reduce medical errors. The committee is planning to implement the concept of a “just culture.” Which of the following would be necessary to include?",
        "Choice 1": "Use of negative feedback",
        "Choice 2": "Judgmental assessment of events",
        "Choice 3": "Rewards for error reporting",
        "Choice 4": "Simplistic view of the situation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "379",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects a basic belief of the National Patient Safety Foundation?",
        "Choice 1": "The system of health care is infallible.",
        "Choice 2": "Patient safety is central to quality health care.",
        "Choice 3": "Limited patient involvement in learning is required.",
        "Choice 4": "Closed communication leads to continued improvement.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When describing whistle-blowing to a group of students, which of the following would the instructor include?",
        "Choice 1": "Must primarily be external before an organization will take adequate action to resolve serious problems",
        "Choice 2": "Occurs internally only if inadequate action has been taken by the media to address a whistle-blower's concerns",
        "Choice 3": "Becomes external in some cases in an effort to embarrass an organization publicly or to seek financial redress",
        "Choice 4": "Removes the need for an employee to report concerns up the chain of command within an organization hopefully to resolve the problem internally",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Test Number": "380"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "381",
        "Question": "Which of the following best describes a whistle-blower?",
        "Choice 1": "Typically a disgruntled employee with poor work history",
        "Choice 2": "A need to do “good” as the primary motivation",
        "Choice 3": "Great courage and self-conviction to avoid groupthink",
        "Choice 4": "Typically a reward for willingness to come forward",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "382",
        "Question": "When it comes to whistle-blowing in organizations, which statement about management would be most accurate?",
        "Choice 1": "Have a lack of awareness that a problem exists until external whistle-blowing occurs",
        "Choice 2": "Provide support for their whistle-blowers after they learn there is a problem",
        "Choice 3": "Encourage external whistle-blowing for lack of appropriate supervisor redress",
        "Choice 4": "Aware of problem but ignore it until crisis-precipitating event or whistle-blowing occurs",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "383",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about whistle-blowing, the instructor determines that the students have understood the information when they state which of the following about potential whistle-blowers?",
        "Choice 1": "Often experience a schism between what they “should do” and what they actually do",
        "Choice 2": "Frequently overestimate the potential negative consequences of their whistle-blowing",
        "Choice 3": "Are generally applauded and supported by their peers but not by management",
        "Choice 4": "Typically overcome the stressful feelings after blowing the whistle",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "384",
        "Question": "Nurses have an obligation to be whistle-blowers if",
        "Choice 1": "Management does not do what they want them to.",
        "Choice 2": "The organization does not seem to care about its employees.",
        "Choice 3": "Serious and considerable harm to the public is involved.",
        "Choice 4": "They lack the time to go up the chain of command in an organization.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "385",
        "Question": "A nurse is reviewing the American Nurses Association (ANA) Code of Ethics for Nurses With Interpretive Statements related to whistle-blowing. Which of the following would the nurse expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Little guidance for nurses about issues related to whistle-blowing and whether to become whistle-blowers",
        "Choice 2": "Suggestions on how to avoid whistle-blowing if it means that such action would result in disruption of patient care",
        "Choice 3": "Recommendation that as a patient advocate, nurses must be alert to and take appropriate action regarding any individual or practice placing a patient's rights or best interest in jeopardy",
        "Choice 4": "Arguments that nurses are charged with the responsibility to act in a manner consistent with their professional responsibilities and practice standards, unless the personal risks are too great",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "386",
        "Question": "To reduce their risk of retaliation, which action by a potential whistle-blower would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "Make necessary complaints anonymously, hoping media or someone else will follow up on it.",
        "Choice 2": "Determine legal duty for reporting, researching carefully the specifics of legal protection.",
        "Choice 3": "Go public with information rather than trying to solve the problem internally.",
        "Choice 4": "Threaten those accused of wrongdoing, not really follow through on the whistle-blowing.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "387",
        "Question": "A nurse demonstrates a deontological view of whistle-blowing by which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Seeing whistle-blowing as aimed at achieving good outcomes by changing a situation for the better",
        "Choice 2": "Determining whether the harm caused by whistle-blowing is greater than the harm caused by the employer's actions",
        "Choice 3": "Eliminating any possible intrapersonal conflict in regard to his or her duty to the patient over that to his or her employer",
        "Choice 4": "Seeing whistle-blowing as the fulfillment of a duty to keep promises, tell the truth, and protect patients",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "388",
        "Question": "Whistle-blowing suggests a failure of organizational ethics exists because",
        "Choice 1": "Most employees are unhappy with their work environment.",
        "Choice 2": "Employees whistle-blow only if they are morally sensitized.",
        "Choice 3": "Policies and procedures to raise an organization's awareness have not been in place to respond to staff concerns.",
        "Choice 4": "The motive of most whistle-blowers is to cause trouble.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "389",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements best reflects the current status of legal protection for whistle-blowers in the United States?",
        "Choice 1": "There is no universal legal protection for whistle-blowers.",
        "Choice 2": "One state has passed legislation with three more states introducing some type of whistle-blower legislation.",
        "Choice 3": "The majority of states have laws protecting whistle-blowers with standards for proving retaliation.",
        "Choice 4": "Employees are guaranteed protection under common law if actions are deemed to be in good faith.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "390",
        "Question": "A nurse notes a problem that may be an issue for whistle-blowing. Which action would be most important for the nurse to do first?",
        "Choice 1": "Seek validation from colleagues.",
        "Choice 2": "Act immediately before considering the risks.",
        "Choice 3": "Confront the wrongdoer individually.",
        "Choice 4": "Verify via resources that a problem exists.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "391",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about ethical codes of conduct and whistle-blowing, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which of the following as the most important underlying principle?",
        "Choice 1": "Justice",
        "Choice 2": "Advocacy",
        "Choice 3": "Duty",
        "Choice 4": "Responsibility",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "392",
        "Question": "A nurse files a qui tam lawsuit, which would involve which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Patient injury",
        "Choice 2": "Medication error",
        "Choice 3": "Defraud of government",
        "Choice 4": "Retaliation for whistle-blowing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "393",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing the literature to develop a list of states that have legal protection for whistle-blowing. Which state would the group include in this list?",
        "Choice 1": "Oklahoma",
        "Choice 2": "Florida",
        "Choice 3": "Pennsylvania",
        "Choice 4": "Arkansas",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "394",
        "Question": "Which of the following would provide the best protection for whistle-blowing with public companies if the individual was a nongovernment employee?",
        "Choice 1": "The Whistleblower Protection Act of 1989",
        "Choice 2": "The National Labor Relations Act",
        "Choice 3": "Sarbanes-Oxley Act of 2002",
        "Choice 4": "False Claims Act",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "395",
        "Question": "The United Kingdom's Public Interest Disclosure Act is important for which reason?",
        "Choice 1": "It addresses whistle-blowing as a national issue.",
        "Choice 2": "Whistle-blowers are protected from retaliation by employers.",
        "Choice 3": "The decisions involving this act can be appealed for final review.",
        "Choice 4": "The act covers individuals who are considered subcontractors.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "396",
        "Question": "When filing a whistle-blower complaint under the False Claims Act, which of the following would a nurse need to do first?",
        "Choice 1": "Exhaust the internal chain of command.",
        "Choice 2": "File a complaint with the Department of Health and Human Services.",
        "Choice 3": "Validate the complaint with evidence.",
        "Choice 4": "Prepare for litigation against the employer.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "397",
        "Question": "A person who is engaged in whistle-blowing is subject to significant personal and professional risk because that person is most likely avoiding which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Autonomous decision making",
        "Choice 2": "Ethical behavior",
        "Choice 3": "Standards of care",
        "Choice 4": "Groupthink",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "398",
        "Question": "Based on the current status of health care, which of the following best reflects the status of whistle-blowing?",
        "Choice 1": "Overall risks have increased, increasing the need for whistle-blowing.",
        "Choice 2": "Federal health care legislation has decreased the need for whistle-blowing.",
        "Choice 3": "Increased consumer knowledge has led to a decreased need for whistle-blowing.",
        "Choice 4": "Whistle blowing is primarily limited to individuals and organizations in the United States.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "399",
        "Question": "A group of students is studying for an examination about whistle-blowing. The students demonstrate a need for additional study when they identify which of the following as a benefit of whistle-blowing?",
        "Choice 1": "Patient protection",
        "Choice 2": "Improved quality of care",
        "Choice 3": "Validation of concerns",
        "Choice 4": "Professional risk",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When describing the issue of substance misuse in nursing, which of the following would be most accurate?",
        "Choice 1": "Is a relatively new phenomenon, being documented in the literature primarily since the 1980s",
        "Choice 2": "Is rare, occurring in fewer than 2 out of every 100 nurses",
        "Choice 3": "Is significantly less common than substance misuse in the other health professions",
        "Choice 4": "Is difficult to quantify due to the sensitive nature of the information and associated stigma",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4",
        "Test Number": "400"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "401",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about substance misuse by health care professionals, the instructor determines that the students need additional instruction when they identify which of the following as a risk factor?",
        "Choice 1": "Younger age",
        "Choice 2": "Social contact",
        "Choice 3": "Access to narcotics",
        "Choice 4": "Job strain",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "402",
        "Question": "Which statement most accurately reflects ideas about recognizing chemical impairment in a nurse?",
        "Choice 1": "Is generally fairly easy after training has been provided on how to do so",
        "Choice 2": "Is easier if the employee is impaired by alcohol rather than by drugs",
        "Choice 3": "Should involve confrontation with a specified plan in place",
        "Choice 4": "Requires a period of extensive data-gathering to confirm all suspicions",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "403",
        "Question": "Reentry of the chemically impaired employee into the workplace",
        "Choice 1": "Is successful in only a small number of cases despite active treatment programs.",
        "Choice 2": "Is discouraged by most boards of registered nursing.",
        "Choice 3": "Should not occur until 3 years after the employee has completed the treatment program.",
        "Choice 4": "Often includes a requirement for random drug-testing by the employer.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "404",
        "Question": "When describing diversion programs for chemically impaired nurses, which of the following would be included?",
        "Choice 1": "Are an alternative to formal discipline in all 50 states of the United States",
        "Choice 2": "Were the norm in most states through the 1980s, but now being replaced with disciplinary action",
        "Choice 3": "Are highly variable in terms of what they offer and the degree or extent of being voluntary",
        "Choice 4": "Have been standardized across state lines in terms of requirements for completion",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "405",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements best reflects the current status of research related to impaired nursing practice?",
        "Choice 1": "Huge amounts of data are available, but it is difficult to quantify for interpretation.",
        "Choice 2": "Research is lacking due to nurses' difficulty in talking openly about the topic.",
        "Choice 3": "Federal funding has significantly increased, which is allowing for new research.",
        "Choice 4": "Although the stigma associated with substance use has diminished, studies are few.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "406",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing information about various treatment programs offered for nurses with substance-abuse problems in preparation for a class presentation. Which of the following would the students identify as the first treatment program offered?",
        "Choice 1": "California Board of Registered Nurses Diversion Program",
        "Choice 2": "Texas Peer Assistance Program for Nurses",
        "Choice 3": "Intervention Project for Nurses in Florida",
        "Choice 4": "Kentucky Peer Assistance Program for Nurses, Inc.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "407",
        "Question": "When accessing the Board of Registered Nursing websites for information about impaired nursing practice, which of the following would a nurse expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "A wide range of information about the reentry process",
        "Choice 2": "Actions to take if a nurse suspects an impaired colleague",
        "Choice 3": "Specified length of time for random drug-testing during recovery",
        "Choice 4": "Methods for reporting an impaired colleague",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "408",
        "Question": "A health care facility has developed specific policies for impaired practice. The facility would expect to introduce these policies at which time?",
        "Choice 1": "During hospital orientation for new employees",
        "Choice 2": "When the staff identify an impaired colleague",
        "Choice 3": "At a specially designed in-service for mental-health professionals",
        "Choice 4": "During the accreditation review process",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "409",
        "Question": "Which of the following would lead a nurse to suspect that a colleague is misusing substances?",
        "Choice 1": "Participation in unit social functions",
        "Choice 2": "Sudden change in personal grooming",
        "Choice 3": "Even-tempered mood",
        "Choice 4": "Acknowledgement of medication errors",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "410",
        "Question": "Which of the following would least likely be a barrier to reporting an impaired colleague?",
        "Choice 1": "Sense of loyalty to the colleague",
        "Choice 2": "Fear of confrontation",
        "Choice 3": "Fear of jeopardizing own license",
        "Choice 4": "Fear of label as whistle-blower",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "411",
        "Question": "A nurse suspects that a colleague is chemically dependent. Before reporting the colleague, which of the following would be most important for the nurse to do?",
        "Choice 1": "Offer the colleague help",
        "Choice 2": "Suggest the colleague find a treatment program",
        "Choice 3": "Check the state board of nursing's reporting requirements",
        "Choice 4": "Talk to others to confirm the suspicions",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "412",
        "Question": "When addressing the issue of impaired nursing practice, which of the following would be of primary importance?",
        "Choice 1": "Health of the impaired nurse",
        "Choice 2": "Type of substance being misused",
        "Choice 3": "Process for reporting",
        "Choice 4": "Safety of the patients",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "413",
        "Question": "When reviewing the literature about the prevalence of impaired nursing practice, which of the following is suggested?",
        "Choice 1": "Studying the patterns of abuse",
        "Choice 2": "Determining actual numbers",
        "Choice 3": "Focusing on short-term outcomes",
        "Choice 4": "Attempting to dispute the problem's existence",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "414",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing recent research about impaired nursing practice. Which of the following would the students most likely find?",
        "Choice 1": "Experimental research methods",
        "Choice 2": "Longitudinal studies",
        "Choice 3": "Quantitative research designs",
        "Choice 4": "Anecdotal accounts",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "415",
        "Question": "To reduce the risks for impaired practice, education of which group would be most important?",
        "Choice 1": "Practicing nurses",
        "Choice 2": "Nursing students",
        "Choice 3": "Nurses preparing for retirement",
        "Choice 4": "Foreign nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "416",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is preparing a teaching plan for a group of students about the American Nurses' Association policy on impaired practice. Which of the following would the instructor include?",
        "Choice 1": "A focus on discipline as a major means of treatment",
        "Choice 2": "Little emphasis on the process of facilitating reentry",
        "Choice 3": "Policy development in nursing education",
        "Choice 4": "Duty to report based on advocacy role",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "417",
        "Question": "A nurse is reviewing the literature about impaired nursing practice. Which of the following would the nurse expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Evident that nurses using substances moderately were more critical of nurses who used substances irresponsibly.",
        "Choice 2": "Nurses with permissive attitudes placed more value on the substances involved in misuse.",
        "Choice 3": "There is lack of a consistent theme on substance abuse among nurses, nursing students, and health care professionals in general.",
        "Choice 4": "Nurses used similar approaches when reporting an impaired peer as when reporting technical incompetence.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "418",
        "Question": "Which of the following would characterize the Texas Peer Assistance Program for Nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "It does not include services for mental-health disorders.",
        "Choice 2": "Participation in the program is not voluntary.",
        "Choice 3": "It is independent of the state licensing board.",
        "Choice 4": "Efforts to maintain confidentiality are limited.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "419",
        "Question": "A nurse is interviewing nurses about their feelings and beliefs related to impaired nursing practice. Which of the following would the interviewing nurse most likely expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Fear",
        "Choice 2": "Anger",
        "Choice 3": "Denial",
        "Choice 4": "Disbelief",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When describing collective bargaining in the United States, which of the following statements would most likely apply?",
        "Choice 1": "Union membership in the private sector is slowly declining.",
        "Choice 2": "Participation in nursing unions is decreasing.",
        "Choice 3": "The majority of registered nurses currently belong to collective bargaining units.",
        "Choice 4": "This history of labor unions in the United States is marked by more peaceful collaboration.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Test Number": "420"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "421",
        "Question": "Based on history, which of the following would most likely result when there is an increased demand for nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "Nurses engaging in greater union activity",
        "Choice 2": "No change in the unionization activity of nurses",
        "Choice 3": "Typically a decrease in union activity by nurses",
        "Choice 4": "No historical perspective indicating a result",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "422",
        "Question": "A review of the literature indicates that nurses seek unionization most commonly when",
        "Choice 1": "Salaries keep pace with the economy.",
        "Choice 2": "Organizations are insensitive to the worker.",
        "Choice 3": "There is an economic downturn.",
        "Choice 4": "Jobs are scarce.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "423",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about nurses and collective bargaining, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the group states which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Most nurses belong to some kind of union.",
        "Choice 2": "The ANA discourages unionization as being unprofessional.",
        "Choice 3": "Blue-collar union membership continues to grow.",
        "Choice 4": "Nurses could not join unions until amendment of the Wagner Act.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "424",
        "Question": "In the early 1990s, the National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) ruled that",
        "Choice 1": "Licensed practical/vocational nurses, who make daily work assignments, oversee aides, and report to management should be classified as “supervisors,” thereby making them ineligible for protection under the National Labor Relations Act (NLRA).",
        "Choice 2": "Nurses' supervisory work is directed at meeting patient needs rather than employer needs, therefore all nurses should be eligible for protection under the NLRA.",
        "Choice 3": "The interest of the patient and the interest of the employer were not mutually exclusive; therefore, nurses should be eligible for protection under the NLRA.",
        "Choice 4": "Licensed practical/vocational nurses cannot be classified as supervisors; only registered nurses can.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "425",
        "Question": "Nurses in a health care facility are considering unionization. Before beginning an organizing campaign, the collective-bargaining agent would require demonstration of at least how much employee interest?",
        "Choice 1": "30%",
        "Choice 2": "40%",
        "Choice 3": "50%",
        "Choice 4": "60%",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "426",
        "Question": "A group of 150 registered nurses has voted on establishing a union. For the union to be recognized, how many votes are needed?",
        "Choice 1": "51",
        "Choice 2": "76",
        "Choice 3": "101",
        "Choice 4": "150",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "427",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is describing the role of the ANA and collective bargaining. Which of the following would the instructor plan to include?",
        "Choice 1": "Is recognized by the NLRB as a collective-bargaining agent",
        "Choice 2": "Is strongly opposed to nurses joining unions",
        "Choice 3": "Is primarily a professional association that encourages unionization",
        "Choice 4": "Rejects the rights of nurses to strike, even as a last resort",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "428",
        "Question": "A group of nursing students is reviewing various labor legislation in preparation for an examination. The students demonstrate an understanding of the material when they identify which legislation as responsible for providing a more equal balance of power between union and management?",
        "Choice 1": "Wagner Act",
        "Choice 2": "Taft-Hartley Amendment",
        "Choice 3": "Kennedy Executive Order 10988",
        "Choice 4": "NLRB ruling of 1989",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "429",
        "Question": "Passage of which of the following resulted in unions no longer being the primary source of security for workers?",
        "Choice 1": "Equal Employment Opportunity Act",
        "Choice 2": "Labor-Management Relations Act",
        "Choice 3": "National Industrial Recovery Act",
        "Choice 4": "Taft-Hartley Act",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "430",
        "Question": "A nurse is reviewing information about unions representing nurses. Which of the following would the nurse expect to find as the largest union representing health care?",
        "Choice 1": "International Brotherhood of Teamsters",
        "Choice 2": "American Nurses Association",
        "Choice 3": "Service Employees International Union",
        "Choice 4": "United Steelworkers of America",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "431",
        "Question": "Research related to unions and nursing reveals which of the following as an effect?",
        "Choice 1": "Increase in mandatory overtime",
        "Choice 2": "Improvement in nurse-to-patient ratios",
        "Choice 3": "Reduction in supervised management practices",
        "Choice 4": "Negative patient outcomes",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "432",
        "Question": "A group of nurses is discussing whether to join a union. Which of the following statements indicates that one of the nurses would be resistant to joining a union?",
        "Choice 1": "“I want more individual power.”",
        "Choice 2": "“I want a higher salary for what I do.”",
        "Choice 3": "“I want limited mandatory overtime.”",
        "Choice 4": "“I want to advance on my merits.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "433",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be least likely to violate the Wagner Act of 1935?",
        "Choice 1": "Spying on union gatherings",
        "Choice 2": "Withholding tenure",
        "Choice 3": "Bargaining in good faith",
        "Choice 4": "Giving money to a labor organization",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "434",
        "Question": "The management of a health care facility and the labor union demonstrate mutual respect and establishment of mutual goals. This relationship demonstrates which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Acceptance",
        "Choice 2": "Accommodation",
        "Choice 3": "Opposition",
        "Choice 4": "Union-busting",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "435",
        "Question": "After teaching a class on the dilemma created by the dual role of the ANA, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when they identify which state as having broken away from the ANA?",
        "Choice 1": "California",
        "Choice 2": "New York",
        "Choice 3": "Massachusetts",
        "Choice 4": "Florida",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "436",
        "Question": "A nurses' union is preparing to strike. The union is required to notify the hospital of the intent to strike how many days before the strike?",
        "Choice 1": "30 days",
        "Choice 2": "15 days",
        "Choice 3": "10 days",
        "Choice 4": "5 days",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "437",
        "Question": "When discussing the various reasons for and against nursing unionization, which of the following would most likely be cited as the major reason for fearing union activity?",
        "Choice 1": "Issue of striking",
        "Choice 2": "Fear of employer reprisal",
        "Choice 3": "Lack of knowledge",
        "Choice 4": "Ethical conflict",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "438",
        "Question": "According to the NLRA/NLRB, which of the following groups would be prohibited from joining a union?",
        "Choice 1": "Part-time nurse's aides",
        "Choice 2": "Full-time staff nurses",
        "Choice 3": "Full-time charge nurses",
        "Choice 4": "Rotating charge nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "439",
        "Question": "When reviewing the history of unionization in America, a student would note that unions have been present in the United States since which time?",
        "Choice 1": "Early 1700s",
        "Choice 2": "1790s",
        "Choice 3": "Late 1800s",
        "Choice 4": "1930s",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When describing assessment of professional competency, which of the following would be included?",
        "Choice 1": "Recent participation in practice assures adequate competency for professional registered nurses.",
        "Choice 2": "In many states, competency is determined via initial licensure continuing unless proven otherwise.",
        "Choice 3": "Graduation from an accredited nursing program assures a practitioner minimum competency throughout his or her career.",
        "Choice 4": "Professional competency can only be ascertained by examination.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Test Number": "440"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "441",
        "Question": "Initial licensure in nursing",
        "Choice 1": "Assures the public that the practitioner will provide quality nursing care.",
        "Choice 2": "Suggests achievement of content mastery needed for successful functioning in multiple practice areas.",
        "Choice 3": "Assures continuing competence will be achieved for future relicensure.",
        "Choice 4": "Indicates that minimum competency standards have been met at that time.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "442",
        "Question": "When describing the NCLEX examination to a group of students, which of the following would the nursing instructor include?",
        "Choice 1": "Is developed using a process that is prospective rather than retrospective in its analysis of the nursing skills necessary for high-quality practice",
        "Choice 2": "Is more sophisticated and future-oriented in assessing competence for practice than examinations in most of the other health disciplines in the United States",
        "Choice 3": "Must be retaken to assure continued competency if the nurse has not practiced for more than 5 consecutive years",
        "Choice 4": "Shows little relevance to the different competencies achieved in the various types of education programs for nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "443",
        "Question": "When describing the issue of continuing education (CE) for license renewal in nursing, which of the following would be most accurate?",
        "Choice 1": "Is mandated in all 50 states of the United States",
        "Choice 2": "Is voluntary in all 50 states of the United States",
        "Choice 3": "Highly variable from few hours to 30 hours every 2 years",
        "Choice 4": "Assures continued competence as a professional registered nurse",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "444",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about certification and the American Nurses Credentialing Center (ANCC), the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students state which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "It allows advanced-practice nurses to substitute work experience for the master's degree.",
        "Choice 2": "It is the only accrediting body specifically for nursing certification.",
        "Choice 3": "A subsidiary of the ANA, it is the largest U.S. nursing-credentialing organization.",
        "Choice 4": "It develops and administers both the NCLEX-RN and NCLEX-PN licensure examinations.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "445",
        "Question": "Nurses attending an in-service program on the issues associated with continuing competency are introduced to the reflective-practice model. Which of the following would be addressed?",
        "Choice 1": "Use of self-assessment",
        "Choice 2": "Frequent attendance at educational courses",
        "Choice 3": "Attainment of a graduate degree",
        "Choice 4": "Use of external sources for validation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "446",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements is most accurate?",
        "Choice 1": "Professional certification ensures that the nurse has some specialized area of knowledge and practice expertise.",
        "Choice 2": "The need for CE is clearly greater for some health care professionals than for others.",
        "Choice 3": "Most states do not require pharmacists to complete CE for license renewal.",
        "Choice 4": "Professional certification is typically conferred for a lifetime without the need for reexamination or work experience for renewal.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "447",
        "Question": "A nurse manager is describing professional certification to a group of staff nurses. Which of the following would the manager expect to include?",
        "Choice 1": "Affords title protection and recognition of accomplishment but does not include a legal scope of practice",
        "Choice 2": "Guarantees the nurse has continued competence to practice in any area of nursing specialty he or she chooses",
        "Choice 3": "Is required for a nurse to practice in an advanced-practice nursing role in the United States",
        "Choice 4": "Is typically granted for successfully passing a comprehensive examination without the need for work experience or minimum education levels",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "448",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements most accurately reflects the status of continuing competence in nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "Professional organizations are actively implementing continuing competence mandates.",
        "Choice 2": "State regulatory agencies should be the ones to monitor competency.",
        "Choice 3": "No national standards exist for defining and measuring competency.",
        "Choice 4": "A current consensus has been reached for measuring competency.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "449",
        "Question": "Licensure for physicians differs from that for nursing in which way?",
        "Choice 1": "Unlike nurses, physicians take an examination after each year of education.",
        "Choice 2": "Nurses are not required to take a clinical skills examination, but physicians are.",
        "Choice 3": "Physicians take a state law examination while nurses do not.",
        "Choice 4": "Nursing licensure examinations use a competency-based process while medicine does not.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "450",
        "Question": "A nurse working in the state of California is required to validate participation in how many hours of CE for relicensure?",
        "Choice 1": "12 hours every 2 years",
        "Choice 2": "15 hours every year",
        "Choice 3": "20 hours every 3 years",
        "Choice 4": "30 hours every 2 years",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "451",
        "Question": "A group of students is preparing a debate on the pros and cons of mandatory CE. The students are ready for the debate when they identify which of the following as a positive aspect?",
        "Choice 1": "Improved outcomes are clearly noted.",
        "Choice 2": "Nursing practice is positively affected.",
        "Choice 3": "Numerous courses are available for specialists.",
        "Choice 4": "The quality of courses is exceptionally high.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "452",
        "Question": "When describing the role of the American Board of Nursing Specialties, which of the following most likely would be included?",
        "Choice 1": "Allows for variety in nursing certification",
        "Choice 2": "Increases nurses' awareness of the value of certification",
        "Choice 3": "Advocates for protection of the nurse being certified",
        "Choice 4": "Provides a peer-review process for accreditation of certification programs",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "453",
        "Question": "Which of the following best describes certification for advanced-practice nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "This group was the first to use certification to demonstrate advanced knowledge.",
        "Choice 2": "The individual must possess a doctoral degree to take the certification examination.",
        "Choice 3": "Certification for advanced practice is used in addition to a second licensure for practice.",
        "Choice 4": "Advanced-practice certification is considered voluntary.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "454",
        "Question": "After describing the results of research related to certification and its impact to a group of nursing students, an instructor determines that the teaching was successful when they state which of the following as an effect?",
        "Choice 1": "Lesser feelings of empowerment",
        "Choice 2": "Enhanced professional credibility",
        "Choice 3": "Diminished feelings of accomplishment",
        "Choice 4": "Decreased level of professional commitment",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "455",
        "Question": "A nurse manager is working to foster a climate for encouraging certification. Which of the following would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "Privately recognize the individuals who earn certification",
        "Choice 2": "Encourage staff to purchase certification prep books on their own",
        "Choice 3": "Allow paid time off to take the certification examination",
        "Choice 4": "Limit the number of staff nurses becoming certified to two or three",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "456",
        "Question": "A nursing administrator is interviewing several staff members about their reasons for not obtaining certification. Which of the following would the administrator expect to hear as the most common reason?",
        "Choice 1": "Cost of the examination",
        "Choice 2": "Lack of institutional reward",
        "Choice 3": "No support from their nurse manager",
        "Choice 4": "Lack of study time",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "457",
        "Question": "When engaging in reflective practice, which of the following would a nurse need to do first?",
        "Choice 1": "Develop a learning plan",
        "Choice 2": "Self-assessment of learning needs",
        "Choice 3": "Evaluate learning activities",
        "Choice 4": "Implement a learning plan",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "458",
        "Question": "A nurse is creating a portfolio to demonstrate competence. Which of the following would the nurse be least likely to include?",
        "Choice 1": "Employment history",
        "Choice 2": "Certifications",
        "Choice 3": "Diary of practice",
        "Choice 4": "Presentations",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "459",
        "Question": "When describing who has the responsibility for competence assessment in nursing, which of the following would be identified as being most certainly involved?",
        "Choice 1": "Professional association",
        "Choice 2": "Individual",
        "Choice 3": "Employer",
        "Choice 4": "Regulatory board",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is describing benchmarking to a group of students. Which of the following would the instructor include in the description?",
        "Choice 1": "The process of translating research findings into useful interventions for practice",
        "Choice 2": "Identification of the business methods of successful companies to use their approach as the gold standard and replicating and refining those methods",
        "Choice 3": "The use of evidence-based statements by practitioners and patients to make high-quality decisions in specific health care situations",
        "Choice 4": "A statistical tool used to determine the validity of evidence-based approaches to decision making",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Test Number": "460"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "461",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be important for a nurse to keep in mind when preparing to implement an evidence-based approach to care?",
        "Choice 1": "Need for integration of best research evidence with clinical expertise and patient values in making decisions about the health care of patients",
        "Choice 2": "Use primarily by health care members who have achieved graduate degrees and advanced training in research techniques",
        "Choice 3": "Necessity of significantly more time and expense for implementation than simply following best practices",
        "Choice 4": "Lack of appropriate opportunities for patients to have input into decision making about their care",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "462",
        "Question": "Which of the following strategies best supports the creation of an organizational culture that promotes the identification and implementation of evidence-based practice?",
        "Choice 1": "Nurses are given incentives such as time off from their shift to go to the facility's library to consult with the librarian about accessing possible studies.",
        "Choice 2": "The designation of a specialized title for nurses who have been positively singled out by patients in hospital patient-satisfaction surveys",
        "Choice 3": "Nurses are instructed not to deviate from established policies and procedures in performing care so as to reduce personal and institutional legal liability.",
        "Choice 4": "A free child-care service is created within the hospital so that nurses are able to work additional shifts without the stress of finding high-quality child care.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "463",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the accountability of health care providers today related to evidence-based practice?",
        "Choice 1": "Showing that the care they provide is the least expensive option that meets minimum required outcomes",
        "Choice 2": "Knowing and following the best-practice standards in place at the time they completed their initial licensure examination for entry into their profession",
        "Choice 3": "Having knowledge of and implementing the most effective and reliable evidence-based approaches to care",
        "Choice 4": "Conducting research to determine what constitutes best practices in the institution in which they work",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "464",
        "Question": "Which of the following questions would be most appropriate for a nurse to ask in the spirit of looking for opportunities to improve nursing practice and patient outcomes through evidence-based practice?",
        "Choice 1": "How many patients can the average nurse care for on a medical-surgical hospital unit before quality of care is compromised?",
        "Choice 2": "Should nurses join professional associations to foster unity within the profession?",
        "Choice 3": "Which medical supply company offers the greatest price discount on high-volume purchases of IV tubing?",
        "Choice 4": "What continuing-education courses am I most interested in for self-renewal?",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "465",
        "Question": "When reviewing a research article, the nurse notes that a randomized controlled trial (RCT) was used. The nurse needs to keep in mind that this type of research",
        "Choice 1": "Is often considered the gold standard of clinical research evidence",
        "Choice 2": "Yields very limited evidence regarding the results of several similar studies",
        "Choice 3": "Is the most common research methodology used in nursing studies",
        "Choice 4": "Is more commonly a tradition-based approach",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "466",
        "Question": "A nurse uses the National Guideline Clearinghouse as a resource based on the rationale that this source",
        "Choice 1": "Conducts best-practices clinical research on diseases with the highest morbidity and mortality in the United States",
        "Choice 2": "Offers providers practice guidelines developed through systematic searches and reviews of research literature and scientific evidence",
        "Choice 3": "Provides consumers with report-card-type information about a provider's credentials and malpractice records",
        "Choice 4": "Is the most significant “Protocol for Practice” published by the American Association of Critical Care Nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "467",
        "Question": "Which of the following strategies is most appropriate for the new nurse to use in promoting evidence-based best practices?",
        "Choice 1": "Using the institutional policy and procedure manual as the primary resource for clinical problem solving",
        "Choice 2": "Seeking out current, established sources of evidence in his or her area of specialty practice",
        "Choice 3": "Adhering to long-established nursing traditions, symbols, and interventions",
        "Choice 4": "Role-modeling behaviors and actions of experienced nurses who have been practicing for some time",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "468",
        "Question": "Which of the following would the nurse identify as a potential barrier to implementation of evidence-based practice?",
        "Choice 1": "An increasing number of nurses educated at the graduate or doctoral level",
        "Choice 2": "Institutional support for research activities and researchers",
        "Choice 3": "The high degree of technical information that is often difficult to understand",
        "Choice 4": "Confidence that the nursing staff has the skill set needed to conduct research",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "469",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about evidence-based practice and approaches, the instructor determines that additional teaching is needed when the students identify which of the following as an example of evidence-based practice?",
        "Choice 1": "Integrative reviews",
        "Choice 2": "Meta-analyses",
        "Choice 3": "Institutional standards",
        "Choice 4": "Randomized control trials",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "470",
        "Question": "As part of the preparation for implementing an evidence-based practice intervention on a nursing unit, an in-service program is being done. Which of the following would the presenter cite as the overall goal of this intervention?",
        "Choice 1": "Cost-effectiveness",
        "Choice 2": "Enhanced professional credibility",
        "Choice 3": "Increased work efficiency",
        "Choice 4": "Improved patient outcomes",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "471",
        "Question": "A nurse involved in research for evidence-based practice is evaluating the effects of an intervention with that of another intervention using a limited population. The nurse is engaged in which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Randomized control trial",
        "Choice 2": "Integrative review",
        "Choice 3": "Practice-based evidence for continuous process improvement",
        "Choice 4": "Meta-analysis",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "472",
        "Question": "A nursing staff wants to implement an evidence-based intervention on the unit. Which of the following would the staff need to do first?",
        "Choice 1": "Collaborate with a research mentor.",
        "Choice 2": "Get support from the administration.",
        "Choice 3": "Seek out the medical librarian.",
        "Choice 4": "Contact the professional nursing organization.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "473",
        "Question": "During an orientation group, a new nurse asks the advanced practice nurse about ways to promote evidence-based practice. Which of the following suggestions would be least helpful?",
        "Choice 1": "“Stay true to the nursing traditions because these are essential to practice.”",
        "Choice 2": "“Subscribe to several professional journals and read them for information.”",
        "Choice 3": "“Check for sources of evidence already out there so you don't reinvent the wheel.”",
        "Choice 4": "“Don't stick to just one source of evidence, use multiple sources.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "474",
        "Question": "A nurse is looking for critiques of existing nursing research studies. Which of the following sources would be most helpful?",
        "Choice 1": "Cochrane Collaboration",
        "Choice 2": "National Guideline Clearinghouse",
        "Choice 3": "Agency for Healthcare Research and Quality",
        "Choice 4": "Worldviews on Evidence-Based Nursing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "475",
        "Question": "After teaching a class about benchmarking and institutions considered to be national leaders in evidence-based nursing practice, the instructor determines that additional teaching is needed when the class identifies which institution as a leader?",
        "Choice 1": "University of Iowa",
        "Choice 2": "University of Chicago",
        "Choice 3": "Arizona State University",
        "Choice 4": "McMaster University of Ontario",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "476",
        "Question": "When incorporating new evidence into clinical practice, which of the following is considered essential to achieve successful implementation?",
        "Choice 1": "Health care institutional review",
        "Choice 2": "Buy-in from the interdisciplinary team",
        "Choice 3": "Patient and family support",
        "Choice 4": "Participation of other nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "477",
        "Question": "When describing the term best practice to a group of students, a nursing instructor would associate this term with which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Shared decision making",
        "Choice 2": "Clinical expertise",
        "Choice 3": "Benchmarking",
        "Choice 4": "Evidenced-based nursing practice",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "478",
        "Question": "A nursing student asks the instructor, “Where does evidence-based practice begin?” Which response by the instructor would be the most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "“It starts with questions that arise in practice settings.”",
        "Choice 2": "“There really is no actual beginning; it is ongoing.”",
        "Choice 3": "“Changes in technology are usually the stimulus.”",
        "Choice 4": "“A physician identifies a problem, which prompts nurses to respond.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "479",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of nursing students about evidenced-based practice, the instructor determines the need for additional teaching when the students identify which of the following as a source of evidence?",
        "Choice 1": "Meta-analyses",
        "Choice 2": "Quasi-experimental studies",
        "Choice 3": "Consultation with an experienced nurse",
        "Choice 4": "Integrative reviews",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "An instructor is describing the public image of the nursing profession to a group of new students. Which of the following would the instructor be most likely to include?",
        "Choice 1": "Nurses are typically described as being one dimensional.",
        "Choice 2": "Nursing is viewed as an honest and prestigious profession.",
        "Choice 3": "Most think of young women altruistically caring for the ill, under a doctor's supervision.",
        "Choice 4": "The public usually see broadly educated professionals who provide care based on science.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Test Number": "480"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "481",
        "Question": "A family of a patient calls a nurse an “angel of mercy.” The nurse understands which of the following about this stereotype?",
        "Choice 1": "Is fairly recent, originating with nurses from the Vietnam era",
        "Choice 2": "Often associated with the belief of nursing being depicted as almost a saintly vocation",
        "Choice 3": "Is the least common of all contemporary nursing stereotypes",
        "Choice 4": "Depicts a nurse with little independent thought as an adoring backdrop to the omnipotent physician",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "482",
        "Question": "A group of nurses is working with other groups to help dispel stereotypical images of nursing. Which of the following would the group need to keep in mind about these images?",
        "Choice 1": "Are decreasing in contemporary media, particularly on television",
        "Choice 2": "Have little impact on the public's perception of the nursing role",
        "Choice 3": "Often begin in early childhood and so are difficult to modify",
        "Choice 4": "Have little impact on recruitment into the profession",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "483",
        "Question": "A group of students is working on a group project about nursing stereotypes. Knowledge of which of the following would be most important for the group to integrate into their project?",
        "Choice 1": "Nursing as ranked as one of the most desirable careers in the United States, ranking in the top 10 for career desirability.",
        "Choice 2": "Nurses having acted collectively and effectively to correct stereotypical and inaccurate images of nursing in the media.",
        "Choice 3": "Contemporary male nurses having overcome their stereotypes as being homosexual, nonachieving, and feminine.",
        "Choice 4": "The confusion of the public and their lack of understanding about what professional nursing is.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "484",
        "Question": "A nurse is preparing a presentation for “career day” at a local high school. Which of the following would the nurse need to keep in mind about young people today?",
        "Choice 1": "Are more apt to pursue nursing as a career than their mothers or fathers",
        "Choice 2": "Typically have an accurate, factual understanding of what nursing is",
        "Choice 3": "Beliefs and stereotypes being ingrained at early ages",
        "Choice 4": "No longer believe that nursing is “women's work”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "485",
        "Question": "When describing the corporate initiatives launched by Johnson and Johnson in 2002, which of the following would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "Provision of over millions of dollars in scholarships for all students interested in pursuing nursing as a career",
        "Choice 2": "Initiative for recruitment and increased awareness of the value of nursing educators in the nursing profession",
        "Choice 3": "Funding for weekly hour-long television specials about the value of nurses to society throughout the ages",
        "Choice 4": "Launching of national advertising campaign titled “Campaign for Nursing's Future” in an effort to highlight nursing practice and promote diversity.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "486",
        "Question": "Sociologically, conflicting stereotypes of nursing",
        "Choice 1": "Have united nurses in actively fighting for a common cause.",
        "Choice 2": "Continue to contribute to the disconnect between the reality of nursing and its public image.",
        "Choice 3": "Have resulted in nurses being viewed as dishonest or unethical by much of the public.",
        "Choice 4": "Are a significant part of the nursing profession's history and culture needing to be encouraged.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "487",
        "Question": "A nursing student is reviewing information about the Center for Nursing Advocacy. Which of the following would the student identify as the Center's goal?",
        "Choice 1": "Provide funding to increase the recruitment of nurses",
        "Choice 2": "Address the media's negative and disrespectful portrayal of nursing",
        "Choice 3": "Foster an increase in the diversity of students entering nursing school",
        "Choice 4": "Promoting the need for nurses to dress as professionals",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "488",
        "Question": "When reviewing the long-established, inaccurate nursing stereotypes, which of the following would most likely apply?",
        "Choice 1": "Could be changed easily if nurses banded together to write protest letters to media sources",
        "Choice 2": "Can easily be altered by presenting accurate career information to high school students",
        "Choice 3": "Are perpetuated, at least in part, by nursing's “invisibility” as a profession",
        "Choice 4": "Have led to the erosion of the public's trust and respect for nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "489",
        "Question": "As part of a research project, a nurse is conducting a telephone survey on the public's perception of nursing. Which of the following terms would the nurse expect to hear? Select all that apply?",
        "Choice 1": "Hardworking",
        "Choice 2": "Caring",
        "Choice 3": "Highly educated",
        "Choice 4": "Independent thinking",
        "Choice 5": "Powerful",
        "Choice 6": "Honest",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 2, 6"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "490",
        "Question": "When reviewing the literature for evidence of stereotypes in nursing, the nurse would expect to find which of the following as one of the most famous portrayals of a nurse as a sex bombshell?",
        "Choice 1": "Hot Lips Houlihan in M*A*S*H*",
        "Choice 2": "Nurse Betty",
        "Choice 3": "Hana in The English Patient",
        "Choice 4": "Nurse Ratched in One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "491",
        "Question": "A nurse is preparing to interact with the media. Which of the following would be most helpful for the nurse to do?",
        "Choice 1": "Focus on at least 5 to 7 key points",
        "Choice 2": "Explain answers using specific details and examples",
        "Choice 3": "Use professional language for answering",
        "Choice 4": "Remember that nothing is off the record",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "492",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be most helpful in changing nursing's image in the public eye?",
        "Choice 1": "Focusing on one specific strategy to foster change",
        "Choice 2": "Passively interacting with the media",
        "Choice 3": "Restricting the use of nurse to licensed RNs",
        "Choice 4": "Limiting involvement in the political process",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "493",
        "Question": "When attempting to change nursing's image with the media, which of the following would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "Wait for the media service to contact the nurse for information",
        "Choice 2": "Write letters to the professional organization",
        "Choice 3": "Actively initiate contact with individuals in the media",
        "Choice 4": "Contact the institution's public relations department",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "494",
        "Question": "After teaching a class about measures to reclaim the title of “nurse,” the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the class identifies which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Having nurses return to wearing the white uniform",
        "Choice 2": "Identifying selves as nurses using surnames when introducing themselves",
        "Choice 3": "Acting as ambassadors for the profession with the public",
        "Choice 4": "Emphasizing how nursing is a combination of caring and curing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "495",
        "Question": "When describing who is responsible for changing the public's image of nursing, which of the following would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "Professional nursing organizations",
        "Choice 2": "Corporate coalitions",
        "Choice 3": "Nurses",
        "Choice 4": "Media",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "496",
        "Question": "Which of the following nursing stereotypes was typically reflected in printed novels and books?",
        "Choice 1": "Angel of mercy",
        "Choice 2": "Love interest",
        "Choice 3": "Naughty nurse",
        "Choice 4": "Handmaiden to the physician",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "497",
        "Question": "When reviewing the literature about stereotypes and male nurses, which of the following characteristics would a nurse expect to find? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Sex-bombshell role",
        "Choice 2": "Homosexual orientation",
        "Choice 3": "Lazy attitude",
        "Choice 4": "Sexually predatory",
        "Choice 5": "Nonachiever",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "2, 3, 4, 5"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "498",
        "Question": "As part of a class assignment, students were asked to watch the movie, “One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest” to view an example of a nursing stereotype. Which stereotype would the students most likely have seen?",
        "Choice 1": "Angel of mercy",
        "Choice 2": "Love interest",
        "Choice 3": "Battle-axe",
        "Choice 4": "Handmaiden",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "499",
        "Question": "When introducing oneself to a patient, which of the following would be most appropriate to promote a change in the public's image of nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "“Hi, I'm Joe, your nurse for the day.”",
        "Choice 2": "“Hello, my name is Joe Smith, the registered nurse who will be caring for you today.”",
        "Choice 3": "“Hi, my name is Joe S. I'm a registered nurse here if you need me.”",
        "Choice 4": "“Hello, I'm Mr. Smith. I'm your nurse and I will be caring for you until 7 p.m.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about the various types of advanced practice nurses, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students state which of the following as the most common type?",
        "Choice 1": "Nurse practitioners (NPs)",
        "Choice 2": "Clinical nurse specialists (CNS)",
        "Choice 3": "Certified nurse midwives (CNMs)",
        "Choice 4": "Certified registered nurse anesthetists (CRNAs)",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Test Number": "500"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "501",
        "Question": "A group of nurses is attending a presentation about advanced practice nursing. Which of the following would the group expect to hear about the scope of practice?",
        "Choice 1": "It has been standardized for all 50 states in the United States.",
        "Choice 2": "It includes prescribing or furnishing drugs in only about one half of the states in the United States.",
        "Choice 3": "It is dependent upon if the national certifying exam has been taken for the specialty practice area.",
        "Choice 4": "It differs greatly among the various types of advanced practice.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "502",
        "Question": "A nurse is considering becoming a clinical nurse specialist (CNS). Which activities would the nurse expect to be involved in? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Managing complex medical conditions",
        "Choice 2": "Providing expert consultation with nursing staffs",
        "Choice 3": "Administering anesthesia",
        "Choice 4": "Providing specialized direct care",
        "Choice 5": "Providing pregnancy care",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "2, 4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "503",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the doctor of nursing practice degree?",
        "Choice 1": "Required as mandatory for nurse practitioners and clinical nurse specialists as of the year 2012",
        "Choice 2": "Focused concentration on assessment and diagnostic skills with little or no emphasis on nursing theory and health-policy components common to most current master's degree programs",
        "Choice 3": "Endorsed by the American Association of Colleges of Nursing (AACN) as the appropriate degree for advanced practice nurses to gain entry to practice",
        "Choice 4": "Awarded the doctor of nursing (ND) degree after successful completion of the program",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "504",
        "Question": "A nurse is looking into a doctoral degree with an interest in direct-care provision and policies. Which of the following would be most appropriate for this nurse to obtain?",
        "Choice 1": "Doctor of nursing science",
        "Choice 2": "Doctor of philosophy",
        "Choice 3": "Clinical nurse leader",
        "Choice 4": "Doctor of nursing practice",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "505",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements by a nurse would indicate that a doctor of nursing practice (DNP) degree would be the most appropriate choice for advanced practice?",
        "Choice 1": "“I would like to participate in research studies.”",
        "Choice 2": "“I'm really interested in practicing at a microsystem level.”",
        "Choice 3": "“I want to apply research findings to improving health care outcomes.”",
        "Choice 4": "“I want to maximize my patient's self-care and decision-making abilities.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "506",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the view of the National Organization of Nurse Practitioner Faculties (NONPF) about the doctor of nursing practice degree?",
        "Choice 1": "It supports the recommended deadline for NP entry to practice.",
        "Choice 2": "It suggests that the DNP should be a worthwhile goal to attain.",
        "Choice 3": "It includes the development of additional criteria for each specialty of APRNs.",
        "Choice 4": "It believes that the timeline for mandating the DNP for entry be instituted immediately.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "507",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about the issues and concerns related to the DNP as entry level for APRN practice, the instructor determines that additional teaching is needed when the students identify which of the following as a concern?",
        "Choice 1": "The timing of the recommendation is inappropriate because there are more pressing matters related to patient safety that need to be addressed.",
        "Choice 2": "Important parties who would be involved did not have an opportunity to engage in a discussion about the recommendation.",
        "Choice 3": "There is agreement among those in nursing education about the core competencies to be included in a typical program.",
        "Choice 4": "DNP graduates may not be able to obtain tenure and equal status in the educational field like their PhD counterparts.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "508",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the position of the AACN related to DNP and PhD graduates who want to teach at the collegiate level?",
        "Choice 1": "PhD graduates are better prepared to teach as the collegiate level than DNP graduates.",
        "Choice 2": "Both graduates must pursue additional coursework that focuses on teaching.",
        "Choice 3": "DNP and PhD graduates can apply research findings that focus on educational settings.",
        "Choice 4": "PhD graduates understand curriculum development while DNP graduates do not.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "509",
        "Question": "A nurse is preparing to become a clinical nurse leader. At which level would this nurse expect to practice?",
        "Choice 1": "Microsystems level",
        "Choice 2": "Population-based level",
        "Choice 3": "Community-based level",
        "Choice 4": "Macrosystem level",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "510",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be the most appropriate response to critics of the DNP who are concerned that the curriculum does not include theory?",
        "Choice 1": "DNP programs focus primarily on nursing theories, which are essential to advanced practice nurses.",
        "Choice 2": "Since nurses work as part of an interdisciplinary team, they need to understand many types of theories.",
        "Choice 3": "DNP programs focus on using appropriate research methodologies to generate new nursing theories.",
        "Choice 4": "The DNP graduate would be able to make decisions based on expertise and practice rather than on theory.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "511",
        "Question": "A group of nursing students are reviewing the two types of doctoral degrees for nursing. The students demonstrate a need for additional study when they identify which of the following as a research-focused doctorate?",
        "Choice 1": "PhD",
        "Choice 2": "DNS",
        "Choice 3": "DNP",
        "Choice 4": "DNSc",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "512",
        "Question": "After teaching a class about the views of medicine and the DNP, the instructor determines that additional teaching is necessary when the students identify which of the following as a current belief supported by the American Medical Association?",
        "Choice 1": "The physician has the final authority for the patient.",
        "Choice 2": "Doctors of nursing practice can practice independently.",
        "Choice 3": "Medicine has the right to regulate advanced practice nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "Medicine can identify the roles and functions of a DNP.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "513",
        "Question": "Which of the following would best characterize the clinical nurse leader (CNL) role?",
        "Choice 1": "Master's-prepared advanced practice specialist nurse",
        "Choice 2": "Focus on management systems for institutional health care delivery",
        "Choice 3": "Integration of the care provided by each of the disciplines involved in patient care",
        "Choice 4": "Limited focus on health promotion with greater emphasis on population-based care",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "514",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing information about the clinical nurse leader role (CNL) and how it differs from other advanced practice roles. The students demonstrate understanding of the information when they state which of the following about the CNL role?",
        "Choice 1": "Focuses on a specific group of patients in a particular setting",
        "Choice 2": "Picks up care where the role of the clinical nurse specialist ends",
        "Choice 3": "Participates in care before admission and after discharge",
        "Choice 4": "Is a consistent figure to act as a point person for those involved",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "515",
        "Question": "When describing the functions of the nurse practitioner (NP), which of the following would be included?",
        "Choice 1": "Prescribing medications for treatment",
        "Choice 2": "Administering anesthesia during labor",
        "Choice 3": "Providing care during pregnancy",
        "Choice 4": "Providing expert consultation for nursing staffs",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "516",
        "Question": "According to the AACN, which role would assume guardianship for the nursing profession?",
        "Choice 1": "Nurse practitioners",
        "Choice 2": "Clinical nurse leaders",
        "Choice 3": "Doctors of nursing practice",
        "Choice 4": "Clinical nurse specialists",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "517",
        "Question": "When describing the clinical nurse leader to a group of nursing students, which of the following would the instructor most likely include? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Practice guidelines based on evidence",
        "Choice 2": "Interdisciplinary but not intradisciplinary client centered care",
        "Choice 3": "Self-care and client decision making maximized",
        "Choice 4": "Lack of emphasis on fiscal stewardship",
        "Choice 5": "Avoidance of social justice",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "518",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be a key area of focus for a certified nurse midwife (CNM)?",
        "Choice 1": "Health promotion",
        "Choice 2": "Improvements in health care delivery systems",
        "Choice 3": "Diagnosis of common acute problems",
        "Choice 4": "Specialization in ambulatory care",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "519",
        "Question": "When describing the differences between a doctor of nursing practice degree and a doctor of nursing science degree, which of the following would the instructor include as characteristics of a DNP degree? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Less emphasis on scientific content",
        "Choice 2": "Increased content on research methodology",
        "Choice 3": "Similar dissertation requirements",
        "Choice 4": "Emphasis on practice with research",
        "Choice 5": "No required clinical practicum",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "An instructor is preparing a teaching plan about policy and politics. Which of the following would be most important for the instructor to keep in mind?",
        "Choice 1": "Are terms that can be used interchangeably since they mean essentially the same thing",
        "Choice 2": "Differ in that politics is the process of making decisions and governing while policy is reflective of the ideology and belief systems of how the world should work",
        "Choice 3": "Differ in that politics is manipulative and destructive and policy is proactive and forward thinking",
        "Choice 4": "Are very similar although politics refers to a governmental or legislative action and policy is limited to the private sector",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Test Number": "520"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "521",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about the types of policy, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which of the following as an example of a domestic health-related policy?",
        "Choice 1": "Deciding to give smallpox vaccinations to military personnel and their dependents",
        "Choice 2": "The creation of a Medicare prescription-drug plan for the elderly",
        "Choice 3": "Giving billions of dollars to less developed nations for the care of people with HIV",
        "Choice 4": "Opposing the president's request for funding of new nuclear weapons",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "522",
        "Question": "A nurse is working on a committee for policy development that is using Kingdon's three “streams.” Which of the following would the nurse identify as characterizing the policy stream?",
        "Choice 1": "Definition of problems, indicators of a problem, and the social construction of problems",
        "Choice 2": "Associated benefits and costs to subgroups of the population",
        "Choice 3": "Examination of ideas based on technical feasibility and value acceptability",
        "Choice 4": "Component that becomes insignificant if any of the other streams is stronger",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "523",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements best reflects a strong political stream?",
        "Choice 1": "Often is impacted greatly by ideological interest groups",
        "Choice 2": "Is more likely to be logical and reasoned in approach rather than passionate and values laden",
        "Choice 3": "Allows legislators to vote their conscience and not be influenced by outside parties",
        "Choice 4": "Encourages policy makers to propose legislative or regulatory proposals that are unlikely to pass and/or be implemented",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "524",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the belief of those who criticize the systems-model approach to policy?",
        "Choice 1": "Too much influence given to special interest groups",
        "Choice 2": "Decisions never reached due to lack of implementation and evaluation",
        "Choice 3": "Partisan influences usually with little impact on reasoned decision making",
        "Choice 4": "Lack of elected government's policy agenda rarely, if ever, reflecting a consensus",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "525",
        "Question": "An instructor is preparing a teaching plan for a group of students about nursing leaders as public-policy pioneers. Which of the following would the instructor expect to include about the nursing leaders in the early 1900s?",
        "Choice 1": "Were committed to collective strength, being politically astute and active in advancing sociopolitical causes",
        "Choice 2": "Recognized politics as a necessary evil but did whatever they could to avoid active involvement in social or political issues",
        "Choice 3": "Avoided politics, turning to leaders in organized medicine to advance the health care and nursing agenda",
        "Choice 4": "Were active in influencing policy within the nursing profession but had little influence on greater social issues of the time",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "526",
        "Question": "A student is reviewing the literature about legislative efforts to establish a national health insurance. Which of the following would the student expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Initially introduced by Theodore Roosevelt in 1912 but failed despite support by nursing leaders such as Lillian Wald, Lavinia Dock, and Annie W. Goodrich",
        "Choice 2": "Actively supported by the American Medical Association when introduced by Franklin Delano Roosevelt's administration",
        "Choice 3": "First proposed by President Bill Clinton's Health Security Act in the early 1990s but failed as a result of the powerful insurance-industry lobby",
        "Choice 4": "Lost its attraction is the 1950s and has not been supported by major professional nursing associations since that time",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "527",
        "Question": "Which of the following would an ideological interest group be least likely to provide?",
        "Choice 1": "Money",
        "Choice 2": "Voter mobilization",
        "Choice 3": "Image",
        "Choice 4": "Policy solutions",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "528",
        "Question": "A group of nurses is attending a presentation on nurses and policy and politics. Which of the following would the nurses expect to hear related to nurses and their involvement?",
        "Choice 1": "Should not be involved in contemporary politics because it diverts their energy away from caring for patients",
        "Choice 2": "Have both a professional and a moral obligation, as providers with the closest perspective on patients, to see that patients' best interests are represented in health care policy decisions",
        "Choice 3": "Do not have the knowledge, experience, or desire needed to be an integral force in health care policymaking",
        "Choice 4": "Have little political influence because grassroots activity is rarely recognized by legislators as important",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "529",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about Kingdon's streams of policy development, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which of the following as the best example of convergence of Kingdon's “streams?”",
        "Choice 1": "A local school board president calls for the reinstatement of school nurses in the county after everyone in her child's class contracts head lice with parents unanimously demanding action.",
        "Choice 2": "A senator introduces a bill based on pressure from a constituent interest group that he knows is unlikely to pass.",
        "Choice 3": "Despite public outcry, a school principal refuses to change her ruling to dismiss a student from school for reading aloud from a Bible in class.",
        "Choice 4": "The local mayor decides to give all city officials an extra paid day off in recognition of budget surpluses recorded the prior year.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "530",
        "Question": "A nurse votes in every election and stays informed about issues affecting the health care system. The nurse would fall into which category?",
        "Choice 1": "Leader",
        "Choice 2": "Activist",
        "Choice 3": "Professional",
        "Choice 4": "Political change agent",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "531",
        "Question": "When discussing the continuum model for political involvement, which of the following would be used to describe a nurse who makes things happen?",
        "Choice 1": "Nurse who participates in activity that is personally important",
        "Choice 2": "Nurse who is a political change agent",
        "Choice 3": "Nurse who exposes self to political stimuli",
        "Choice 4": "Nurse who votes occasionally",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "532",
        "Question": "Which of the following nurses would be credited for making birth control available to women?",
        "Choice 1": "Lillian Wald",
        "Choice 2": "Lavinia Dock",
        "Choice 3": "Margaret Sanger",
        "Choice 4": "Martha Minerva Franklin",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "533",
        "Question": "A nurse is working on a committee to address policies related to environmental health. Which of the following would the committee be least likely to address?",
        "Choice 1": "Workplace conditions",
        "Choice 2": "Nursing shortage",
        "Choice 3": "Health risks of low-income population",
        "Choice 4": "Toxic wastes",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "534",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is describing the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act (PPACA). Which of the following would the instructor identify as the major focus of this legislation?",
        "Choice 1": "Funding for Medicare",
        "Choice 2": "Restricted nursing roles in models of health care delivery",
        "Choice 3": "Health care provider protection",
        "Choice 4": "Health care reform with controlled costs",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "535",
        "Question": "A nurse is reviewing the two major political parties from a health perspective and decides to join the Democratic party based on the understanding that this party favors which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Market strategy",
        "Choice 2": "Choices based on cost and quality",
        "Choice 3": "Public systems",
        "Choice 4": "Choices keeping prices down",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "536",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be most effective in influencing politics?",
        "Choice 1": "Getting involved in campaigns early on",
        "Choice 2": "Becoming a member of a professional organization",
        "Choice 3": "Subscribing to electronic listservs of elected officials",
        "Choice 4": "Writing lobbying letters",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "537",
        "Question": "When using a systems-based model that considers policymaking in sequential stages, which of the following would occur first?",
        "Choice 1": "Development of a policy agenda",
        "Choice 2": "Identification of a problem",
        "Choice 3": "Creation of a policy",
        "Choice 4": "Modification of the policy",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "538",
        "Question": "A nurse is developing political skill. As part of this, the nurse is using herself to influence others to promote behavior and action that is productive. The nurse is demonstrating which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Social astutement",
        "Choice 2": "Networking ability",
        "Choice 3": "Appraisal sincerity",
        "Choice 4": "Interpersonal influences",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "539",
        "Question": "A group of nursing students is reviewing information about early nursing leaders as public-policy pioneers. The students demonstrate understanding of the material when they identify which of the following as the founder of public health nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "Lavinia Dock",
        "Choice 2": "Lillian Wald",
        "Choice 3": "Margaret Sanger",
        "Choice 4": "Martha Minerva Franklin",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "A nurse who is the president of a local chapter of a professional association is preparing a presentation for a group of nursing students about professional associations. Which of the following would the nurse integrate into the presentation?",
        "Choice 1": "Professional associations are an integral part of contemporary nursing culture with a wide variety of nursing associations available.",
        "Choice 2": "The number of associations has decreased since the 1980s due to nurses having less time to devote to outside interests.",
        "Choice 3": "Associations advocate for the practice of nursing within health care but play a limited role in advocating with the public and government.",
        "Choice 4": "Although professional associations have a few significant goals, they provide invaluable opportunities for professional networking and coalition building.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1",
        "Test Number": "540"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "541",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects early nursing associations?",
        "Choice 1": "Sharing of a goal of creating career pathways for advanced practice nurses",
        "Choice 2": "Frequently being at odds with each other doing little to advance and support the profession",
        "Choice 3": "Primarily representing specialty areas of practice and the needs of their individual members",
        "Choice 4": "Working together to build the base for public recognition of nursing as a profession",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "542",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be a major reason for joining a professional nursing association?",
        "Choice 1": "Having a collective voice to influence nursing's future",
        "Choice 2": "Being able to list membership on a resume",
        "Choice 3": "Getting discounts for attending professional conferences",
        "Choice 4": "Receiving copies of association journals or publications",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "543",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is describing membership in professional associations. Which of the following would the instructor include?",
        "Choice 1": "Are unable to contribute to the association unless they are engaged as an officer, committee chair, or spokesperson",
        "Choice 2": "Most commonly share similar motivations for joining",
        "Choice 3": "Seek value from professional associations, playing a role to ensure it can produce that value",
        "Choice 4": "Typically have the same rights and privileges regardless of the type of membership",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "544",
        "Question": "When comparing the work of associations to that of most businesses, which of the following would be considered a similarity?",
        "Choice 1": "Both are concerned with seeking a profit as one of the most important goals",
        "Choice 2": "Each has a charter, a mission, and legal status in the state in which it resides",
        "Choice 3": "Most associations are for-profit organizations and as such are ineligible for tax-exempt status",
        "Choice 4": "Associations may not create separate organizations such as foundations",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "545",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about professional nursing associations and membership, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which of the following as an example of a professional association that has an exclusive membership?",
        "Choice 1": "The American Nurses Association",
        "Choice 2": "The International Council of Nurses",
        "Choice 3": "Sigma Theta Tau International",
        "Choice 4": "The National League for Nursing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "546",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be most important to ensure future viability of professional associations?",
        "Choice 1": "Create a more rule-bound society that clearly dictates the roles and responsibilities of association members.",
        "Choice 2": "Balance traditional attitudes and practices with contemporary ways of managing and interacting, and prioritize use of resources.",
        "Choice 3": "Transition to a fully electronic communication environment to accommodate the needs of working nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "Re-create the fundamental mission and goals to more closely align with those of other “competitor” professional associations.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "547",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be considered one of the greatest challenges facing contemporary professional nursing associations?",
        "Choice 1": "Allocation of increasing revenues to meet membership priorities",
        "Choice 2": "Stagnation in membership numbers due to lack of interest",
        "Choice 3": "Best method to prepare for a future that is unknown",
        "Choice 4": "Determination of traditional rules of order, procedures, and protocols",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "548",
        "Question": "A nurse is thinking about joining a professional association categorized as a professional development association. The nurse would be able to participate in which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Legislative advocacy",
        "Choice 2": "Research projects",
        "Choice 3": "Establishment of practice standards",
        "Choice 4": "Networking",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "549",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about the early professional associations in nursing, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which of the following as the forerunner to the American Nurses Association (ANA)?",
        "Choice 1": "International Council of Nurses",
        "Choice 2": "National League for Nursing",
        "Choice 3": "The Nurses Associated Alumnae of the United States and Canada",
        "Choice 4": "The Society of Superintendents of Training Schools for Nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "550",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing the historical development of specialty-nursing professional associations. The students demonstrate knowledge of this topic when they identify which of the following as one of the oldest?",
        "Choice 1": "Association of Operating Room Nurses",
        "Choice 2": "American Association of Industrial Nurses",
        "Choice 3": "American Association of Nurse Anesthetists",
        "Choice 4": "The American College of Nurse Midwifery",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "551",
        "Question": "A nurse joins a professional association as a liason member. The nurse's membership would include which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Access to all programs",
        "Choice 2": "Ability to vote",
        "Choice 3": "Access to selected services",
        "Choice 4": "Access to information with limited privileges",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "552",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be most appropriate for a professional association to do to sustain and increase its membership?",
        "Choice 1": "Continue with the traditions and rituals of the current association",
        "Choice 2": "Design programs and services to address increasing diversity",
        "Choice 3": "Limit the use of technology in providing services",
        "Choice 4": "Focus on an important cause geared to younger members",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "553",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be considered as the least effective means for financing a professional association?",
        "Choice 1": "Increasing membership dues",
        "Choice 2": "Partnering with a common interest group",
        "Choice 3": "Collecting advertising fees in journals",
        "Choice 4": "Seeking vendor support for programs",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "554",
        "Question": "Which of the following typically would characterize a professional association of the future?",
        "Choice 1": "Resolution of issues with a long life cycle",
        "Choice 2": "Flexible organizational patterns",
        "Choice 3": "Independency of each association",
        "Choice 4": "Concentration on nursing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "555",
        "Question": "A nurse is looking for a professional association that is geared to promote excellence in nursing education. Joining which association would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "National League for Nurses",
        "Choice 2": "American Nurses Association",
        "Choice 3": "Sigma Theta Tau",
        "Choice 4": "International Council of Nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "556",
        "Question": "The Rich Report was significant for professional associations in nursing because it",
        "Choice 1": "Ensured that associations would develop codes of ethics.",
        "Choice 2": "Led to the reorganization of associations to advance the profession.",
        "Choice 3": "Created the need for stewardship.",
        "Choice 4": "Addressed the need for mandatory licensure.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "557",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about the development of professional associations, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify that professional associations began to take shape around which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Passage of the first nurse practice act in 1903",
        "Choice 2": "Time of the Industrial Revolution",
        "Choice 3": "1950s",
        "Choice 4": "Publication of American Journal of Nursing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "558",
        "Question": "A nurse is a member of a professional association which provides professional development. Which of the following activities would be included? Select all that apply",
        "Choice 1": "Networking",
        "Choice 2": "Standards of practice",
        "Choice 3": "Career programs",
        "Choice 4": "Government relations",
        "Choice 5": "Credentialing",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 3, 5"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "A nurse is preparing a presentation for a group of nurses about the need for effective leadership to meet the demands of the current American health care system. When describing issues in the health care system, which of the following would the nurse include?",
        "Choice 1": "The doubling of costs over the past 10 years",
        "Choice 2": "Improving rates of patients receiving care",
        "Choice 3": "Rising medical errors",
        "Choice 4": "Increasing surplus of physicians but not nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Test Number": "559"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "560",
        "Question": "A group of nursing students are reviewing the concept of leadership in preparation for a class discussion on the topic? Which of the following if stated by the students indicates a need for additional review?",
        "Choice 1": "Leadership involves solitary, independent action.",
        "Choice 2": "Successful leaders use effective communication skills.",
        "Choice 3": "Upcoming leaders need to be innovative.",
        "Choice 4": "Leadership is embedded in relationships",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "561",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the leadership challenges in the 21st century? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Need to increase productivity within budgetary constraints",
        "Choice 2": "Maintaining current evidence-based practice recommendations",
        "Choice 3": "Embracing multidisciplinary health care",
        "Choice 4": "Balancing technology and interpersonal relationships",
        "Choice 5": "Encouraging teamwork",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 4, 5"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "562",
        "Question": "Which of the following best indicates the current status of evidence-based practice (EBP) in health care today?",
        "Choice 1": "The majority of nurse leaders are implementing EBP individually.",
        "Choice 2": "EBP is the standard of practice in most health care organizations.",
        "Choice 3": "Staff members are acting as EBP role models in institutions.",
        "Choice 4": "Institutions are fostering cultures for EBP throughout the country.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "563",
        "Question": "A nurse leader is working to develop an internal mechanism in the organization that will help in the promotion of nurses from within the organization. The nurse leader is involved in which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Mentoring",
        "Choice 2": "Coaching",
        "Choice 3": "Transactional leadership",
        "Choice 4": "Succession planning",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "564",
        "Question": "A nurse is reviewing information from the Institute of Medicine (IOM). Which of the following would the nurse expect to find as one of the markers of safe and highly reliable care?",
        "Choice 1": "Team communication",
        "Choice 2": "Formal mentorship",
        "Choice 3": "Proactive decision making",
        "Choice 4": "Innovation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "565",
        "Question": "After discussing effective team communication with a group of students, the instructor determines that the discussion was effective when the students state which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "“Team communication requires individual commitment.”",
        "Choice 2": "“Worldviews and values are similar among team members.”",
        "Choice 3": "“Team communication is a complex social process.”",
        "Choice 4": "“Effective communication is indirect and broad in scope.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "566",
        "Question": "A nurse leader is working as part of a transdisciplinary health care team. Which of the following would be a key component of this team?",
        "Choice 1": "Individual disciplines working toward the same goal",
        "Choice 2": "Collaboration among all health care providers",
        "Choice 3": "Minimal trust among a variety of health care providers",
        "Choice 4": "Use of commonalities based on each discipline's specialized knowledge",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "567",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be most effective in promoting nursing's influence in decision making for organizational and health policy?",
        "Choice 1": "Providing passive contributions to discussion forums on health care",
        "Choice 2": "Being proactive in ensuring representation by the best nurses",
        "Choice 3": "Engaging in limited participation in health policy venues",
        "Choice 4": "Working from the sidelines to promote health issues",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "568",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be the first step in creating a culture of innovation and change?",
        "Choice 1": "Active participation",
        "Choice 2": "Role-modeling",
        "Choice 3": "Mentorship",
        "Choice 4": "Change in personal leadership practices",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "569",
        "Question": "As a nurse leader, which of the following would be the primary focus?",
        "Choice 1": "Change",
        "Choice 2": "The vision",
        "Choice 3": "Patient",
        "Choice 4": "Trust",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "570",
        "Question": "A nurse leader, working with the team, understands that trust is essential for effective team functioning. Which of the following would be inappropriate for developing this trust?",
        "Choice 1": "Transparency",
        "Choice 2": "Pride",
        "Choice 3": "Honesty",
        "Choice 4": "Integrity",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "571",
        "Question": "A group of nursing students are reviewing information about the characteristics of a transformative leader? The students demonstrate understanding of the material when they identify which of the following as a characteristic? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Ability to micromanage",
        "Choice 2": "Willingness to take risks",
        "Choice 3": "Focus on the team",
        "Choice 4": "Satisfaction with the present",
        "Choice 5": "Entrepreneurial spirit",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "2, 3, 5"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "572",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is describing how technology has impacted health care and leadership. Which of the following would the instructor most likely include in this discussion?",
        "Choice 1": "Information transmission, although faster, is less efficient.",
        "Choice 2": "Lag times for information have significantly increased.",
        "Choice 3": "Work and personal time boundaries have become blurred.",
        "Choice 4": "Control of communication pathways remains unchanged.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "573",
        "Question": "A group of nursing students are reviewing information about models of leadership and health care. The students demonstrate understanding of these models when they identify which of the following as the most common style used in health care?",
        "Choice 1": "Transactional leadership",
        "Choice 2": "Inspirational leadership",
        "Choice 3": "Transformational leadership",
        "Choice 4": "Complexity leadership",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "574",
        "Question": "A nurse leader is considering using transformational leadership. Which of the following would the nurse leader need to keep in mind?",
        "Choice 1": "The locus of power rests with the employees.",
        "Choice 2": "Informal leadership is highly recognized.",
        "Choice 3": "Empowerment of both the leader and follower occurs.",
        "Choice 4": "Employees are expected to lead from their organizational position.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "575",
        "Question": "A nurse is reading a journal article on the complexity leadership model. Which of the following would the nurse most likely find as being described in the article?",
        "Choice 1": "Positional leaders carry authority focused on managing organizational dynamics.",
        "Choice 2": "Control is relatively easy to obtain and maintain.",
        "Choice 3": "Power rests solely with specific individuals.",
        "Choice 4": "System boundaries are distinct and well defined.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "576",
        "Question": "A nurse leader is using the trimodal model of leadership. Which of the following would the nurse be engaged in during innovation planning?",
        "Choice 1": "Providing evidence-based patient care",
        "Choice 2": "Looking for ways to improve current ineffective processes",
        "Choice 3": "Developing suitable pathways to modify roles",
        "Choice 4": "Ensuring appropriate funding for services",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "577",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is developing a teaching plan for a class on the characteristics of the various leadership models. Which model would the instructor include as having overlapping, informal organizational boundaries?",
        "Choice 1": "Transactional",
        "Choice 2": "Inspirational",
        "Choice 3": "Transformational",
        "Choice 4": "Complexity",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "578",
        "Question": "The transformational leadership model involves which of the following? Select all that apply.",
        "Choice 1": "Defined boundaries",
        "Choice 2": "Leader in the central position",
        "Choice 3": "Communication in multiple directions",
        "Choice 4": "Coaching competencies",
        "Choice 5": "Planned work",
        "Type": "Multiple",
        "Answer": "1, 2, 5"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When describing the use of current simulators for nursing education, which of the following would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "A skills lab provides fairly realistic experiences in comparison to simulators.",
        "Choice 2": "Computer vignettes provide similar realistic experiences for students as simulators.",
        "Choice 3": "Simulators provide greater control and predictability for the learning environment.",
        "Choice 4": "Role-playing provides better decision-making skills but less clinical-reasoning skills.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Test Number": "579"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "580",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about today's patient simulators, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students state which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "The simulators are usually expensive and have limited programmability.",
        "Choice 2": "Most of the simulators available are considered high-fidelity simulators.",
        "Choice 3": "Task trainers are the mainstay of current patient simulators available.",
        "Choice 4": "Approximately 20% of accredited baccalaureate nursing schools use simulators.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "581",
        "Question": "Which of the following is a key component associated with the learning that occurs with simulation?",
        "Choice 1": "Degree of sophistication of the simulator",
        "Choice 2": "Realism of the patient scenario",
        "Choice 3": "Ability to record student's responses",
        "Choice 4": "Debriefing by a skilled educator",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "582",
        "Question": "A group of faculty is reviewing the literature in preparation for a presentation to increase the use of patient simulators in the curriculum. Which of the following would they expect to find regarding simulators?",
        "Choice 1": "Effective means for improving patient safety due to increased student competencies",
        "Choice 2": "A dramatic rise in cost due to the increased demand for the use of simulators in education",
        "Choice 3": "Benefits to the health care community due to the consistency in design of patient simulators",
        "Choice 4": "The decreased need for supervision and faculty involvement with the use of patient simulators",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "583",
        "Question": "A nursing student has participated in a patient simulation. Which of the following would be most important to happen next?",
        "Choice 1": "Documenting observations in a simulated medical record",
        "Choice 2": "Debriefing with a designated instructor",
        "Choice 3": "Discussing the results with other students",
        "Choice 4": "Preparing to repeat the simulation",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "584",
        "Question": "When describing the use of patient simulators to a group of students, which of the following would differentiate this learning experience from that of a real clinical experience?",
        "Choice 1": "Collaboration is encouraged through team communication.",
        "Choice 2": "The instructor observes many students with many scenarios at the same time.",
        "Choice 3": "Students may be allowed to experience the full consequences of decisions.",
        "Choice 4": "The level of simulation is limited based on the specific objectives.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "585",
        "Question": "A group of nursing faculty is discussing the pros and cons of implementing patient simulators into their program. Which statement most likely reflects a possible disadvantage associated with the use of simulators?",
        "Choice 1": "“We can ensure all students have exposure to specific critical learning experiences.”",
        "Choice 2": "“The level of difficulty for the student's level and objectives will need to be adapted.”",
        "Choice 3": "“We probably need to re-evaluate our student–faculty ratios with simulations.”",
        "Choice 4": "“We can assume that the students will be less anxious so they'll learn better.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "586",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be most critical when using simulation in nursing education?",
        "Choice 1": "Ensuring that faculty are well-trained in using the simulator effectively",
        "Choice 2": "Obtaining simulators that have the most extensive ability for modifications",
        "Choice 3": "Providing greater student experience with simulators than actual clinical practice",
        "Choice 4": "Encouraging students' confidence in simulation to take on tasks beyond their level of expertise",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "587",
        "Question": "A nursing educator is working with a group of students using simulation. Which of the following would be most effective in promoting learning?",
        "Choice 1": "Offering limited feedback",
        "Choice 2": "Identifying specific outcomes",
        "Choice 3": "Ensuring minimal clinical variation",
        "Choice 4": "Decreasing the difficulty level each time",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "588",
        "Question": "A nurse is working as a member of a group that is planning on developing a simulation center for a local hospital. Which of the following would the group need to do first?",
        "Choice 1": "Develop a multiyear business plan",
        "Choice 2": "Outline a clear purpose and objectives",
        "Choice 3": "Assess simulators currently available",
        "Choice 4": "Assess human resources",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "589",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the use of simulation to validate competency of health professionals?",
        "Choice 1": "It is a commonly used method to assess competency in medical practice.",
        "Choice 2": "There is current widespread agreement on its use for evaluation.",
        "Choice 3": "Many agencies have incorporated simulation for certification.",
        "Choice 4": "Simulation will become an accepted tool for competency assessment.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "590",
        "Question": "When describing the use of simulation for continuing education to a group of students, the instructor determines that additional teaching is needed when the students identify which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "The current status for continuing education is in disarray.",
        "Choice 2": "There is little evidence that lectures improve clinical practice.",
        "Choice 3": "Traditional methods for this area are being evaluated closely.",
        "Choice 4": "Effectiveness of simulation is at best similar to current methods.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "591",
        "Question": "When describing the patient simulators of today, which of the following terms would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "Task trainer",
        "Choice 2": "Critical",
        "Choice 3": "High fidelity",
        "Choice 4": "Static",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "592",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is reviewing the literature on students' responses to learning with simulation. Which of the following would the instructor most likely find?",
        "Choice 1": "Increased self-confidence",
        "Choice 2": "Higher anxiety levels",
        "Choice 3": "Difficulty in adapting",
        "Choice 4": "Limited learning",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "593",
        "Question": "After completing a patient simulation for a case scenario, the student undergoes debriefing with the instructor primarily for which purpose?",
        "Choice 1": "To obtain a grade for the activity",
        "Choice 2": "To identify errors that were made",
        "Choice 3": "To analyze the reasons for actions",
        "Choice 4": "To evaluate the student's anxiety level",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "594",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the view of the National Council of State Boards of Nursing (NCSBN) about simulation?",
        "Choice 1": "It is a valid replacement for clinical practice.",
        "Choice 2": "Clinical practice is complemented by it.",
        "Choice 3": "Simulation can negate the professionalism of practice.",
        "Choice 4": "Ample research is available to support the use of simulation.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "595",
        "Question": "Agency administrators are looking to simulation as potentially impacting which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Patient acuity level",
        "Choice 2": "Number of risk managers needed",
        "Choice 3": "Financial risks",
        "Choice 4": "Crisis management",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "596",
        "Question": "A nurse is working as a member of a committee that is working toward developing a simulation center for the facility. As part of the proposal, the committee expects to describe the cost as which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Initially cost will be high but eventually will lessen as time goes on.",
        "Choice 2": "Savings may result from risk reduction but might be difficult to quantify.",
        "Choice 3": "The budget needs to address capital expenses with minimal emphasis on repair.",
        "Choice 4": "Revenue generation need not be addressed until the center is fully operational.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "597",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements best describes the patient simulators of today?",
        "Choice 1": "They have the ability to provide assessment data for review at a later time.",
        "Choice 2": "The student can perform a skill without causing a response from the simulator.",
        "Choice 3": "A skilled operator can change parameters based on the student's actions.",
        "Choice 4": "The simulators are designed to enhance performance of a specified skill.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "598",
        "Question": "After a group of students learns about simulation in nursing practice and education, which statement by the group indicates the need for additional teaching?",
        "Choice 1": "“Simulation works regardless of how it is designed and delivered.”",
        "Choice 2": "“Simulation can help promote patient safety and optimal outcomes.”",
        "Choice 3": "“Simulation allows learning without risk to the patient.”",
        "Choice 4": "“Simulation is one way to produce higher competency levels.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When describing the current nursing shortage to a group of students, the instructors would include which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Similarity in scope to that experienced in the early 1990s",
        "Choice 2": "A result of both a reduced supply of nurses and increased demand for nursing services",
        "Choice 3": "Resolvable by bringing unemployed nurses or part-time nurses back full-time",
        "Choice 4": "Most likely not lasting for more than 4 to 5 years with resolution by 2010",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Test Number": "599"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "600",
        "Question": "Based on the most recent national RN survey, the average age of the working registered nurse in the United States",
        "Choice 1": "Has remained fairly constant over the past two decades.",
        "Choice 2": "Continues to decline due to an increased number of graduates from ADN programs.",
        "Choice 3": "Has increased by a little more than 1 year since the last estimated average.",
        "Choice 4": "Is approximately 20 years older than the current mean age of nursing graduates.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "601",
        "Question": "As part of a class project on the nursing shortage, a group of students is researching information about enrollment in nursing schools. Which information about this topic would the students expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Enrollments in nursing schools have little effect on the supply of nurses to meet the demands.",
        "Choice 2": "Nursing school enrollment has shown a steady yearly increase for almost the past 10 years.",
        "Choice 3": "Federal funding for nursing education has remained fairly stagnant for the past several decades.",
        "Choice 4": "The number of nursing school programs has dramatically increased to address the nursing shortage.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "602",
        "Question": "A nurse is attending a seminar on the nursing shortage in which the presenter discusses the major deterrents to increasing the nurse supply. Which of the following would the presenter identify as a major deterrent to increasing nursing school enrollment?",
        "Choice 1": "Lack of appropriate applicants",
        "Choice 2": "Inadequate number of faculty",
        "Choice 3": "Insufficient clinical sites",
        "Choice 4": "Costs of the program",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "603",
        "Question": "When reviewing recent research on the nursing shortage, which of the following would a student expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "There is little evidence to suggest a clear relationship exists among licensed registered nurse staffing mix, the total hours of care provided to patients, and patient outcomes.",
        "Choice 2": "Most consumers in the United States are unaware that a nursing shortage exists and believe that such a shortage would have little impact on quality of care.",
        "Choice 3": "Despite an increasing nursing shortage, U.S. nursing schools are turning away thousands of qualified applicants.",
        "Choice 4": "Higher salary is a primary driving force for graduate students to consider a nursing faculty position as a career choice.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "604",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about the economic perspectives of the nursing shortage, the instructor determines that the students have understood the information when they identify the shortage as being driven by which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "More by the supply side of the supply/demand equation than the demand side",
        "Choice 2": "More by the demand side of the supply/demand equation than the supply side",
        "Choice 3": "Equally by the supply and demand sides of the equation",
        "Choice 4": "By factors that are not related to supply and demand",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "605",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements best describes the geographic distribution of nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "Nurses are evenly distributed geographically across the United States.",
        "Choice 2": "The lowest concentration of nurses is in the Pacific region.",
        "Choice 3": "Rural and urban areas reveal an even distribution of nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "The East region has a disproportionate number of nursing vacancies.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "606",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing information related to factors contributing to the nursing shortage. The students demonstrate knowledge of the material when they identify which of the following as most significant but least addressed?",
        "Choice 1": "Workplace dissatisfaction",
        "Choice 2": "Aging workforce",
        "Choice 3": "Increase in free-agent nurses",
        "Choice 4": "Inadequate long-term pay incentives",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "607",
        "Question": "Which of the following might be considered a long-term solution to the current nursing shortage?",
        "Choice 1": "Granting sign-on bonuses to newly hired registered nurse employees",
        "Choice 2": "Providing generous continuing-education reimbursement for registered nurse employees",
        "Choice 3": "Instituting initiatives to promote a more positive image of nursing to aid in changing the public's perception",
        "Choice 4": "Granting license reciprocity to all practicing registered nurses so that they could work in any state of their choosing",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "608",
        "Question": "Several schools of nursing are working jointly to develop long-term strategies to address the shortage of nursing faculty. Which of the following strategies would be most helpful in recruiting faculty?",
        "Choice 1": "Developing relationships with state legislators for funding",
        "Choice 2": "Creating mentorship and development programs",
        "Choice 3": "Partnering with agencies to create support for higher education",
        "Choice 4": "Streamlining the academic track to higher education",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "609",
        "Question": "A nurse is working on a committee to develop effective methods to retain older nurses. Which of the following suggestions would be most appropriate?",
        "Choice 1": "Offer shift options of 8 to 10 hours",
        "Choice 2": "Discourage job-sharing",
        "Choice 3": "Provide assistance for child or elder care",
        "Choice 4": "Provide them with mentors",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "610",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is preparing a class discussion on the nursing shortage. Which of the following would the instructor expect to include?",
        "Choice 1": "The nursing shortage is limited primarily to the United States.",
        "Choice 2": "Downsizing for cost containment by hospitals contributed to the shortage.",
        "Choice 3": "The use of unlicensed assistive personnel helped to supplement staffing shortages.",
        "Choice 4": "Increasing the supply of nurses is an easy resolution to the shortage.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "611",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements would most accurately reflect the demand for professional nurses?",
        "Choice 1": "Nursing is expected to be among the top ten professions in terms of projected job growth.",
        "Choice 2": "The demand for nurses is much greater now than the demand expected by the year 2020.",
        "Choice 3": "Registered nurse employment is expected to grow faster than average for all occupations.",
        "Choice 4": "The nation's nurse supply is projected to increase significantly more than the projected demand will increase by 2020.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "612",
        "Question": "After teaching a class about the demand factors driving the current shortage, the instructor determines the need for additional teaching when the class identifies which factor as driving the demand?",
        "Choice 1": "Declining population",
        "Choice 2": "Increased patient acuity",
        "Choice 3": "Emphasis on prevention",
        "Choice 4": "Advances in medicine",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "613",
        "Question": "A nurse is reviewing the literature on nursing faculty and its relationship to the nursing shortage. Which of the following would the nurse expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Numbers of faculty are growing because of an increased interest in academic careers.",
        "Choice 2": "Practicing nurses are looking to education in a desire to expand practice opportunities.",
        "Choice 3": "The time for achieving the necessary degree for teaching has dropped significantly.",
        "Choice 4": "There is little pay incentive for a practicing nurse to become a faculty member.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "614",
        "Question": "Which of the following factors has been identified as contributing to the cause of the current nursing shortage?",
        "Choice 1": "A relatively unhealthy economy of the late 1990s and early 2000s",
        "Choice 2": "High ceiling wages for RNs without advanced degrees",
        "Choice 3": "Selection of fields other than nursing for a career",
        "Choice 4": "Decrease in the elderly population",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "615",
        "Question": "After describing the free-agent nurse to a group of students, the instructor determines that the students need additional discussion when they identify which of the following as a free-agent nurse?",
        "Choice 1": "Per diem nurse",
        "Choice 2": "Agency float nurse",
        "Choice 3": "Traveling nurse",
        "Choice 4": "Independent contractor",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "616",
        "Question": "Which of the following would most likely be a result of a high level of nurse turnover?",
        "Choice 1": "Enhanced organizational functioning",
        "Choice 2": "Increased quality of patient care",
        "Choice 3": "Increased cost for replacement",
        "Choice 4": "Enhanced competition for resources",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "617",
        "Question": "A group of students is discussing various strategies to address the nursing shortage. One of the students mentions the self-service model, describing it as which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Use of ergonomic measures to reduce nurse injury",
        "Choice 2": "Provision of benefits for older nurses while requiring them to work fewer hours",
        "Choice 3": "Advanced education to assume a role as a mentor",
        "Choice 4": "Use of family as beside caregivers to supplement RN care",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "618",
        "Question": "A nursing student is reading a journal article on the nursing shortage that describes the issue of pay as a possible contributing factor. Which of the following would the student expect to find in the article related to the issue of pay?",
        "Choice 1": "Continued decrease in wages with the progression of the nursing shortage",
        "Choice 2": "Salaries as remaining fairly constant from one state to another",
        "Choice 3": "Experienced nurses earning significantly more than newly licensed RNs",
        "Choice 4": "Nurse practitioners as earning less than nursing faculty with similar education",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "After describing the nursing shortage, foreign nurses, and the current status throughout the world to a class of nursing students, the instructor determines that the students have understood the topic when they identify which of the following as true?",
        "Choice 1": "The United States is primarily the only industrialized country in the world with a severe shortage of registered nurses.",
        "Choice 2": "Active planning of large-scale international nurse recruitment is a current practice.",
        "Choice 3": "Nurses represent a small number of international migrants.",
        "Choice 4": "Developing countries have been able to develop sustainable health care systems.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2",
        "Test Number": "619"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "620",
        "Question": "When looking at the countries providing the largest numbers of nurses, which of the following is considered to be one of the largest donors?",
        "Choice 1": "United States",
        "Choice 2": "Philippines",
        "Choice 3": "Canada",
        "Choice 4": "Ireland",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "621",
        "Question": "During a seminar on foreign nurses, one of the participants asks the presenter, “What do you mean when you use the term brain drain?” Which of the following would the presenter need to integrate into the response?",
        "Choice 1": "It revitalizes a country's human resources as experienced workers are replaced by younger, more energetic workers.",
        "Choice 2": "It is a phenomenon that is quite specific to the nursing profession.",
        "Choice 3": "It refers to the loss of skilled personnel and investment in education from migration of human resources.",
        "Choice 4": "It is a significant problem experienced by importer nations when imported nurses are less educated and experienced than native nurses.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "622",
        "Question": "Which of the following statements best reflects a utilitarian concern?",
        "Choice 1": "Each nurse should be able to decide if he or she wants to migrate.",
        "Choice 2": "A nurse's desire to migrate is more important than what is best for the nation left.",
        "Choice 3": "Governments need to determine if a country will allow import or export of nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "Nurse migration impacts a donor nation's health due to loss of nursing resources.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "623",
        "Question": "A nurse reviews the ethical guidelines established by the International Council of Nurses (ICN) for international nurse migration and recruitment. Which of the following positions would the nurse identify as meeting these guidelines?",
        "Choice 1": "Individual nurses have the right to migrate but importer countries should address human resource planning and problems that cause nurses to leave the profession and discourage them from returning to nursing.",
        "Choice 2": "Nurse export should be restricted to underdeveloped nations to ensure nurses the right to improve living conditions and have career advancement opportunities previously unavailable.",
        "Choice 3": "A determination of whether a country should import or export nurses should be left to the discretion of the individual government instead of to any international oversight agencies.",
        "Choice 4": "Recruiting nurses for positions where they lack sufficient qualifications, skills, and experience is acceptable if appropriate training will be provided after they reach the importer nation.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "624",
        "Question": "When planning a presentation about the mistreatment of foreign imported nurses, the presenter would need to integrate which of the following into the discussion?",
        "Choice 1": "It rarely occurs because the cost in terms of time, energy, and money to import such nurses is so high.",
        "Choice 2": "It is most common in underdeveloped countries that actively seek to import nurses from other countries.",
        "Choice 3": "It may occur when imported nurses are offered wages significantly less than the prevailing wage in the importer country.",
        "Choice 4": "It has been abolished with the creation of state regulatory bodies to monitor the content of employment contracts offered to foreign nurses.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "625",
        "Question": "When assisting a foreign nurse to adapt to the American workplace, which of the following must occur first?",
        "Choice 1": "Introducing the nurse to American jargon and variations in nursing practice delivery",
        "Choice 2": "Supporting the nurse through a period of cultural, professional, and psychological dissonance",
        "Choice 3": "Assisting the nurse in dealing with anxiety, homesickness, and isolation",
        "Choice 4": "Integrating the nurse within the institution to develop a sense of community life",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "626",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects foreign nurse graduates who seek employment in the United States?",
        "Choice 1": "They pass the NCLEX-RN at a rate similar to that of nurses educated in the United States.",
        "Choice 2": "They must travel to one of four sites in the United States to take the CGFNS qualifying examination for licensure.",
        "Choice 3": "They must take a test to evaluate their knowledge of the English language before taking the CGFNS examination.",
        "Choice 4": "They typically require some assistance in assimilating into their new work environments and cultures.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "627",
        "Question": "Which of the following best describes pull factors for international nurse migration?",
        "Choice 1": "They are more powerful than push factors in influencing a nurse's decision to migrate.",
        "Choice 2": "They include a fear for personal safety and poor working conditions.",
        "Choice 3": "They discourage foreign nurses from migrating to other countries.",
        "Choice 4": "They include items such as higher pay and better career structures.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "628",
        "Question": "The principle of justice is exemplified by which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Right to freedom of movement",
        "Choice 2": "The action that is best for the donor nation",
        "Choice 3": "Unfairness of the unequal distribution of health care",
        "Choice 4": "Dream of a better life",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "629",
        "Question": "Which of the following best describes the main purpose of labor certification and immigration laws in the United States?",
        "Choice 1": "Protect the alien being hired",
        "Choice 2": "Provide equal services to all",
        "Choice 3": "Protect the domestic labor market",
        "Choice 4": "Eliminate preferential treatment",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "630",
        "Question": "A nurse who came to the United States during the 1970s would be granted which type of visa to work?",
        "Choice 1": "H-1 temporary work visa",
        "Choice 2": "H-1A occupation visa",
        "Choice 3": "H-1B occupational visa",
        "Choice 4": "W-1 visa",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "631",
        "Question": "A foreign nurse has taken the CGFNS examination. To obtain licensure, which step is next?",
        "Choice 1": "Contact the state board for an application",
        "Choice 2": "Take the NCLEX-RN examination",
        "Choice 3": "Secure a job offer",
        "Choice 4": "Obtain a green card",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "632",
        "Question": "Which of the following factors would be least likely to contribute to a migrant nurse's inability to assimilate?",
        "Choice 1": "Fear of being sent home",
        "Choice 2": "Reluctance to ask for help",
        "Choice 3": "Anxiety over voicing dissatisfaction",
        "Choice 4": "Participation with a buddy program",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "633",
        "Question": "A nurse who is describing the process of a nurse moving from one country to another in search of employment refers to this as which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "International recruitment",
        "Choice 2": "Nurse migration",
        "Choice 3": "Pull factor",
        "Choice 4": "Push factor",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "634",
        "Question": "Which of the following characteristics reflects nurse migration of today?",
        "Choice 1": "One-way exchange",
        "Choice 2": "Involvement of a few countries",
        "Choice 3": "Limited use of websites",
        "Choice 4": "A complicated winding process",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "635",
        "Question": "A nurse is talking with a foreign nurse about the reasons for migrating to the United States. Which of the following if stated by the foreign nurse would the nurse identify as a push factor?",
        "Choice 1": "Area engaged in an ongoing armed conflict",
        "Choice 2": "Economic stability",
        "Choice 3": "Higher pay",
        "Choice 4": "Career opportunities",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "636",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is describing the effects of nurse migration on the various countries from which the nurses are leaving. The instructor determines additional discussion is needed when the class identifies which effect?",
        "Choice 1": "Brain drain",
        "Choice 2": "Increased specialization",
        "Choice 3": "Reduced level of care",
        "Choice 4": "Decreased quality of service",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "637",
        "Question": "The Philippines had actively encouraged the outflow of nurses for which reason?",
        "Choice 1": "The need for nursing services decreased due to a decline in population.",
        "Choice 2": "The service demand dropped in response to an influx of nurses from other areas.",
        "Choice 3": "The country received a remittance income for nurses who left.",
        "Choice 4": "The nurses were easily replaceable by less skilled practitioners.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "638",
        "Question": "A staff nurse is talking with another staff nurse who is from the Philippines. Which of the following if stated by the foreign nurse would lead the staff nurse to suspect the possibility of questionable practice?",
        "Choice 1": "Providing the foreign nurse with appropriate housing",
        "Choice 2": "Participating in the 4-week orientation along with other new employees",
        "Choice 3": "Receiving wages for hours that are actually worked",
        "Choice 4": "Working many hours of overtime without any differential pay",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "In delegating to unlicensed assistive personnel (UAP), the registered nurse (RN)",
        "Choice 1": "Can safely assume that the employee has at least a high school diploma as a minimum hiring criterion.",
        "Choice 2": "Should be aware that all UAP have achieved at least minimum standardized training pursuant to the Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act of 1987.",
        "Choice 3": "Should be aware that no federal or community standards have been established for training the broad classification of UAP.",
        "Choice 4": "Is protected from liability if he or she allows the UAP to perform only those tasks the employee states he or she is capable of completing independently.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Test Number": "639"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "640",
        "Question": "A nurse manager is preparing to delegate tasks to unlicensed assistive personnel (UAP). Which of the following would be most important for the nurse to do?",
        "Choice 1": "Carefully assess the skills and knowledge of each UAP.",
        "Choice 2": "Safely assign a UAP the duties of a nurse aide.",
        "Choice 3": "Ask each UAP if they can do a task before assigning the task.",
        "Choice 4": "Use UAP in a manner that will get the work completed.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "641",
        "Question": "As part of a class discussion, an instructor is reviewing the impact of health care restructuring of the 1990s. Which of the following would the instructor most likely cite as a result?",
        "Choice 1": "Increased representation of RNs and LVNs in the staffing mix",
        "Choice 2": "Increased numbers of nursing administrators and fewer staff nurses",
        "Choice 3": "Increased numbers of UAPs and reduced numbers of RNs",
        "Choice 4": "Decreased use of ancillary health care support workers",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "642",
        "Question": "After a class discussion regarding the roles of RNs and UAPs in health care organizations, which of the following statements would demonstrate that the class has understood the information?",
        "Choice 1": "Most RNs in acute-care institutions and long-term care facilities are currently involved in some capacity with the assignment, delegation, and supervision of UAP in the delivery of nursing care.",
        "Choice 2": "The skill mix in many hospitals and health care organizations today has proportionately more RNs than UAP.",
        "Choice 3": "Numerous valid empirical research studies agree on the percentage of the staffing mix that can be represented safely by UAP without negatively impacting patient outcomes.",
        "Choice 4": "Cost savings associated with increased UAP use are significant, with most health care institutions reporting at least 50% reductions in personnel expense.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "643",
        "Question": "In the early 1990s, the American Nurses Association took the position that",
        "Choice 1": "Use of unlicensed assistive personnel should be eliminated from the nursing workforce.",
        "Choice 2": "Control and monitoring of assistive personnel in clinical settings should be the same as for those used for nursing practice.",
        "Choice 3": "A practice act should be created for UAP similar to the state practice acts that exist for nurses.",
        "Choice 4": "UAP should be allowed a broader scope of practice with RN supervision than that advocated by state boards of nursing.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "644",
        "Question": "A nurse is reviewing recent benchmark research examining the link between staffing mix and patient outcomes. Which of the following would the nurse expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Considerable evidence of a direct link between decreased RN staffing and declines in patient outcomes",
        "Choice 2": "Lack of a significant relationship between staffing mix and patient outcomes",
        "Choice 3": "Evidence that adverse events increase as UAP representation in the staffing mix declines",
        "Choice 4": "Higher levels of RN staffing in hospitals are associated with an increased risk of potentially fatal complications in patients",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "645",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be most important for a registered nurse to consider when delegating to unlicensed assistive personnel (UAP)?",
        "Choice 1": "Whose turn it is to be delegated",
        "Choice 2": "Qualifications of the person to carry out the task",
        "Choice 3": "The fiscal cost of the delegation",
        "Choice 4": "Whether the person has done the task before",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "646",
        "Question": "After teaching a class about RN liability for delegating and supervising UAP, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which of the following about the RN's liability?",
        "Choice 1": "Is the same as when delegating to another competent RN",
        "Choice 2": "Is minimized if the RN agrees to supervise the UAP in completing their tasks",
        "Choice 3": "Is ultimately responsible if UAP perform tasks that involve interpreting findings",
        "Choice 4": "Is small because UAP are fully accountable for own actions in a court of law",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "647",
        "Question": "A student nurse is researching information about workforce data and UAP. Which of the following would the student expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "While there is currently a shortage of unlicensed assistive personnel (UAP) in all settings, this should resolve within the next 5 years.",
        "Choice 2": "There are shortages of UAP in acute-care settings but surpluses in long-term care settings.",
        "Choice 3": "UAP actively seek out employment in long-term care settings because minimum government staffing standards are higher in long-term care than in acute care.",
        "Choice 4": "The demand for UAP is growing rapidly with current shortages worsening because the population of persons who have traditionally filled these jobs is declining.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "648",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing information about UAP for an upcoming examination. The students demonstrate the need for additional study when they identify which of the following as an example of a UAP?",
        "Choice 1": "Nurse extender",
        "Choice 2": "Physician's assistant",
        "Choice 3": "Nursing assistant",
        "Choice 4": "Orderly",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "649",
        "Question": "Which of the following is most commonly identified as the primary reason for using UAP in acute-care settings?",
        "Choice 1": "Control of nursing shortage",
        "Choice 2": "Improved time management",
        "Choice 3": "Cost containment",
        "Choice 4": "Improved staff mix",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "650",
        "Question": "A nurse is determining tasks that would be appropriate to delegate to UAP. Which of the following would be appropriate to delegate?",
        "Choice 1": "Teaching a patient how to check his pulse",
        "Choice 2": "Auscultating the chest for breath sounds",
        "Choice 3": "Identifying specific patient outcomes",
        "Choice 4": "Measuring the patient's intake and output",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "651",
        "Question": "A certified nurse's aide differs from most UAP in which of the following ways?",
        "Choice 1": "Must complete a minimum of 75 hours of theory and practice",
        "Choice 2": "No examination need be taken for certification",
        "Choice 3": "Employing agency typically provides the training",
        "Choice 4": "Educational training primarily in skills needed for the facility",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "652",
        "Question": "A nursing instructor is preparing a class about the educational preparation and regulation of UAP, incorporating the ANA's recommendations of 2007. Which of the following would the instructor expect to include?",
        "Choice 1": "Recognizing UAP as a replacement for RNs",
        "Choice 2": "RN delegation reflects supervision on behalf of the employer",
        "Choice 3": "Development of recognized competencies for safe practice",
        "Choice 4": "Preparation of UAP to provide specialized care for patients",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "653",
        "Question": "Which of the following activities would be outside the scope of practice for UAP?",
        "Choice 1": "Assisting a patient with personal hygiene",
        "Choice 2": "Interpreting a trend in vital signs",
        "Choice 3": "Measuring intake and output",
        "Choice 4": "Obtaining a patient's daily weight",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "654",
        "Question": "In 2007, the ANA has stopped using the term UAP, replacing it with which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "CNA",
        "Choice 2": "UMAP",
        "Choice 3": "NAP",
        "Choice 4": "MT",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "655",
        "Question": "A nurse researcher is reviewing the literature evaluating patient outcomes and the increased use of UAP with decreased RN staffing. Which of the following would the researcher expect to find?",
        "Choice 1": "Decreased incidence of patient falls",
        "Choice 2": "Improved rates of wound healing",
        "Choice 3": "A greater number of medication errors",
        "Choice 4": "Less physical restraint use",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "656",
        "Question": "Which of the following would be essential to create a safe work environment with UAP?",
        "Choice 1": "Broadly defined job descriptions",
        "Choice 2": "Clearly defined organizational structure",
        "Choice 3": "Credentials kept on file in nursing administration",
        "Choice 4": "Training programs based on UAP education",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "657",
        "Question": "After discussing the shortage of UAP and factors contributing to it, which of the following if identified by the students as a factor indicates successful teaching?",
        "Choice 1": "High turnover rate",
        "Choice 2": "Positive messages from managers",
        "Choice 3": "Employer-paid health insurance",
        "Choice 4": "Wide ranging career paths",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "658",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing material about RN delegation and supervision of UAP. The group demonstrates understanding of this concept when they state which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "The RN's liability is limited if the RN used the state's nurse practice act as the basis for the delegation.",
        "Choice 2": "The RN is not responsible for instructing UAP about who needs care and when.",
        "Choice 3": "The RN, not the UAP, is responsible for knowing when the UAP should ask for help in certain tasks.",
        "Choice 4": "The RN is accountable for ensuring that the UAP knows how to properly perform the assigned tasks of patient care.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "When discussing the topic of oppressed groups and horizontal violence, which of the following would most likely be included about oppressed groups?",
        "Choice 1": "Often have inflated egos and high self-esteem levels",
        "Choice 2": "Typically have well-defined and self-articulated values and goals",
        "Choice 3": "Often show disempowering and controlling behaviors within the hierarchical structure",
        "Choice 4": "Frequently have a tendency to achieve greater productivity than their oppressors",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Test Number": "659"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "660",
        "Question": "After teaching a class about horizontal violence, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students describe horizontal violence as which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Rare in nursing because most nurses tend to be caring, dedicated, and nurturing",
        "Choice 2": "Unique to nursing as a result of its female gender predominance",
        "Choice 3": "Absent when nurses have been mentored appropriately",
        "Choice 4": "Possibly including a variety of negative socialization behaviors such as bullying",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "661",
        "Question": "Students demonstrate an understanding of mentoring when they identify which of the following statements as true?",
        "Choice 1": "The intensity and duration of relationships are similar in mentoring, preceptoring, and role modeling.",
        "Choice 2": "Mentoring has been identified as one of the most positive interventions to promote socialization for professional and career advancement.",
        "Choice 3": "“Mentees” must be willing to put aside their personal goals and beliefs in an effort to identify more closely with their mentor.",
        "Choice 4": "Most nurses will have the opportunity for many mentoring relationships during their careers.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "662",
        "Question": "A nurse is the supervisor of a new RN graduate. Which action would be most helpful for the supervisor to take to help this graduate successfully socialize to his new role?",
        "Choice 1": "Advise the new graduate to avoid confrontations with doctors during the first 3 months of his employment.",
        "Choice 2": "Suggest to the new graduate that this is the real world and encourage him to change his values.",
        "Choice 3": "Assign the new graduate to work with a willing and qualified preceptor.",
        "Choice 4": "Encourage the new graduate to discard nursing school values and adopt those of the current unit culture.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "663",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects the traditional differences in the socialization of men and women?",
        "Choice 1": "“Belonging” is often associated with male socialization.",
        "Choice 2": "“Achievement” is often the focus of socialization for women.",
        "Choice 3": "Boys are encouraged to engage in team sports, developing teamwork skills for later use.",
        "Choice 4": "Mentoring is inconsistent with traditional feminine socialization because it emphasizes competition and winning.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "664",
        "Question": "Which of the following characterizes the last stage of most mentoring relationships?",
        "Choice 1": "Occurs within 6 months after the relationship begins",
        "Choice 2": "Is commonly challenging because each may not be ready to separate at the same time",
        "Choice 3": "Includes coaching, protection, sponsorship, counseling, acceptance, and the creation of a sense of competence",
        "Choice 4": "Begins when the mentee decides he or she no longer needs such intense coaching",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "665",
        "Question": "Which of the following would most likely apply to women who are seeking mentoring relationships?",
        "Choice 1": "Difficulty finding mentor due to lack of availability of women in higher level positions",
        "Choice 2": "Generally find more women more willing to be mentors than men",
        "Choice 3": "Have little difficulty finding a mentor if they make it known that they want one",
        "Choice 4": "Often find such relationships meaningless if self-directed and achievement oriented",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "666",
        "Question": "Which type of relationship would most likely be used to characterize the mentor relationship?",
        "Choice 1": "Nurse–patient",
        "Choice 2": "Parent–child",
        "Choice 3": "Husband–wife",
        "Choice 4": "Employer–employee",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "667",
        "Question": "After teaching a class on professional socialization/resocialization, the instructor determines that the students have grasped the concept when they describe the need as which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Static throughout the professional nurse's career",
        "Choice 2": "Decreased in the new graduate nurse transitioning from school to full-time employment",
        "Choice 3": "Decreased for the registered nurse with age and life experiences",
        "Choice 4": "Increased for nurses changing work settings within an organization or in a new one",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "668",
        "Question": "Students demonstrate understanding of negative socialization when they identify which of the following as an example?",
        "Choice 1": "Staff nurses make fun of the new graduate nurse for taking the time to fill out care plans.",
        "Choice 2": "A staff nurse refuses to help her colleague because she says she is too busy caring for her own patients.",
        "Choice 3": "A manager delegates a difficult task to a subordinate in an effort to increase her self-confidence.",
        "Choice 4": "A preceptor gradually turns over the responsibility of planning and implementing care to the new graduate.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "669",
        "Question": "Kramer's work in 1974 and 1981 on which of the following led to a renaissance of thinking about professional socialization?",
        "Choice 1": "Oppression",
        "Choice 2": "Horizontal violence",
        "Choice 3": "Reality shock",
        "Choice 4": "Mentoring",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "670",
        "Question": "A new graduate is seeking a mentor. Which of the following statements would suggest that the person would be ineffective as a mentor?",
        "Choice 1": "“I believe in you.”",
        "Choice 2": "“It's better to do it my way.”",
        "Choice 3": "“Feel free to talk to me anytime.”",
        "Choice 4": "“I can see your point.”",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "671",
        "Question": "A nurse involved in a mentoring relationship is demonstrating increasing confidence and competence. The nurse is most likely in which phase of the relationship?",
        "Choice 1": "Finding and connecting",
        "Choice 2": "Learning and listening",
        "Choice 3": "Changing and shifting",
        "Choice 4": "Mentoring others",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "672",
        "Question": "A nurse is encouraging a relationship among other nurses to help each other succeed and progress. The nurse is functioning in which role?",
        "Choice 1": "Mentor",
        "Choice 2": "Guide",
        "Choice 3": "Sponsor",
        "Choice 4": "Peer pal",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "673",
        "Question": "After teaching a class on positive and negative socialization, the instructor determines that the students have understood the information when they cite which of the following as an example of positive socialization?",
        "Choice 1": "Harassment",
        "Choice 2": "Coaching",
        "Choice 3": "Intimidation",
        "Choice 4": "Bullying",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "674",
        "Question": "A nurse manager is working with a group of staff nurses to foster positive socialization on their unit. Which of the following strategies would be most important to include?",
        "Choice 1": "Achieving average performance",
        "Choice 2": "Providing broad, vague expectations",
        "Choice 3": "Giving constructive criticism openly",
        "Choice 4": "Demonstrating mutual respect in communication",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "675",
        "Question": "Typically a person who is a mentor",
        "Choice 1": "Is in a recognized position of power.",
        "Choice 2": "Needs others to fight for the mentee.",
        "Choice 3": "Demonstrates a willingness to share.",
        "Choice 4": "Emphasizes the value of teaching.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "676",
        "Question": "After a class on oppressed-group behavior, the students demonstrate a need for additional discussion when they identify which of the following as a characteristic?",
        "Choice 1": "Inferiority",
        "Choice 2": "Powerlessness",
        "Choice 3": "Inequality",
        "Choice 4": "Self-confidence",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "677",
        "Question": "A nurse manager is interviewing several nurses to determine which one would be an effective preceptor. Which nurse would the nurse manager be least likely to select?",
        "Choice 1": "The nurse who demonstrates a positive attitude",
        "Choice 2": "The nurse who reports becoming easily frustrated",
        "Choice 3": "The nurse who shows a desire to motivate others",
        "Choice 4": "The nurse who often supports other nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "678",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about the mentoring relationship, the instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the group identifies which of the following as the first stage?",
        "Choice 1": "Mentoring others",
        "Choice 2": "Changing and shifting",
        "Choice 3": "Learning and listening",
        "Choice 4": "Finding and connecting",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Question": "Which of the following would the instructor need to integrate into the discussion when preparing a teaching plan for a class on ethnic and gender diversity in nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "It has kept pace with changing population demographics, with statistics matching the changes.",
        "Choice 2": "It has increased significantly in the past decade due to federal, state, and professional association initiatives.",
        "Choice 3": "It is far more limited than in the population at large despite less successful efforts to increase it.",
        "Choice 4": "It not an issue because all nurses are educated to provide high-quality, culturally sensitive, and proficient health care.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3",
        "Test Number": "679"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "680",
        "Question": "In preparing a research paper on diversity in nursing, a nurse is reviewing the literature about current U.S. demographic census data. Which of the following would be an expected finding?",
        "Choice 1": "U.S. population has experienced minimal diversification over the past 30 years.",
        "Choice 2": "Hispanic population is still the largest minority group in the United States.",
        "Choice 3": "Blacks are now the largest minority in the United States.",
        "Choice 4": "Ethnic minorities will comprise almost two thirds of the population of the United States by 2025.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "681",
        "Question": "When evaluating demographic data of the nursing population, which of the following would be noted?",
        "Choice 1": "Almost half of all RNs in the United States are from one or more racial or ethnic minority backgrounds.",
        "Choice 2": "Minority representation in nursing is about the same as that of the general population of the United States.",
        "Choice 3": "Minority representation in nursing has seen a dramatic decline over the past 10 to 15 years.",
        "Choice 4": "Fewer than 13% of full-time faculty members in BSN and graduate programs represent racial or ethnic minority groups.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "682",
        "Question": "Which of the following best reflects diversity in the field of health care management?",
        "Choice 1": "Females and males are equally represented.",
        "Choice 2": "Minorities and Whites are equally represented.",
        "Choice 3": "A gap exists between male and female representation but women are rapidly closing in.",
        "Choice 4": "Minorities are underrepresented, especially in top-tier management jobs.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "683",
        "Question": "A nurse is preparing a presentation for a career seminar for a group of male and female high school students and young adults at a local community center about nursing. Which of the following would be most important for the nurse to include when discussing males in nursing?",
        "Choice 1": "Account for the fastest growing minority segment in nursing, with almost 50% of nurses now being male",
        "Choice 2": "Often face stereotypes of being different or homosexual due to their close working relationship with women",
        "Choice 3": "Have numerous role models from which to mentor, especially in terms of male faculty role models in nursing",
        "Choice 4": "Are less capable, caring, compassionate, and nurturing due to their genetic makeup than female nurses",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "684",
        "Question": "When describing the minority status of men in nursing, which of the following would be most appropriate to include?",
        "Choice 1": "Often results in advantages, including hiring and promotion, that help rather than hinder their careers, unlike women in male-dominated professions",
        "Choice 2": "Often results in an economic disadvantage to male nurses, with male nurses earning up to 10% less than their female counterparts",
        "Choice 3": "Is difficult to change because traditional health care organizations were organized and managed along the lines of matriarchal family structures favoring female dominance",
        "Choice 4": "Is likely to improve because males are leaving nursing due to job dissatisfaction at a proportionately lower rate than women",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "685",
        "Question": "A nursing student is to participate in a debate to discuss affirmative action as a means to recruit men into nursing. Which of the following would the student need to incorporate into the argument?",
        "Choice 1": "Little promise for increasing male recruitment because it was ineffective in recruiting women into other traditionally male-dominated professions such as medicine",
        "Choice 2": "Eagerly supported by legislative bodies and the health care professions as a means for increasing ethnic and gender diversity in nursing",
        "Choice 3": "Successfully used to increase the presence of some underrepresented minorities in health care",
        "Choice 4": "Most likely results in an overrepresentation of ethnic minorities and men in nursing based on history of use",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "686",
        "Question": "Concerns about generational diversity in nursing center on the fact that",
        "Choice 1": "The nursing profession lacks the generational diversity that is seen in the population it serves.",
        "Choice 2": "Different values systems of the different generations greatly impact the settings in which they work.",
        "Choice 3": "Generational diversity provides a variety of perspectives and outlooks that alter workplace balance and decrease productivity.",
        "Choice 4": "Generational diversity is new to nursing with no more than two generations of nurses having typically worked side by side.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "687",
        "Question": "A nurse working on the unit belongs to Generation X. Which of the following would most likely apply?",
        "Choice 1": "Born between 1925 and 1942 and often respectful of authority, supportive of hierarchy, and disciplined",
        "Choice 2": "Called the “silent generation” and tend to have more traditional work values and ethics",
        "Choice 3": "Taught to think as individuals from a young age and to express themselves creatively and independently",
        "Choice 4": "Possibly lack interest in lifetime employment at one place, instead valuing greater work-hour flexibility and a need to define success in their own terms",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "688",
        "Question": "A group of nursing professionals is working locally to increase the diversity in nursing. When exploring the various efforts and methods, which of the following would the group need to keep in mind?",
        "Choice 1": "Wide support by professional organizations such as the American Nurses Association and American Organization of Nurse Executives is lacking.",
        "Choice 2": "Historically, efforts focused on “change-by-drift” strategies, although more proactive efforts and attention to the issue are underway.",
        "Choice 3": "The numerous professional associations that represent almost every ethnic group in nursing are primarily responsible.",
        "Choice 4": "Professional associations such as the American Assembly for Men in Nursing and the Bureau of Health Professions typically demonstrate resistance.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "689",
        "Question": "After describing the impact of the lack of diversity in nursing, an instructor determines that the teaching was successful when the students identify which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "The nursing workforce needs to be slightly less diverse than the populations served.",
        "Choice 2": "Minority health care professionals typically work in communities with high degrees of service.",
        "Choice 3": "Lack of diversity in nursing and health disparities are inextricably linked.",
        "Choice 4": "Increased numbers of the White nursing workforce in underserved areas improve access of underrepresented groups.",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "690",
        "Question": "A group of students is reviewing material in preparation for an examination on ethnic diversity in nursing. The students demonstrate understanding of the material when they identify which ethnic group as having the lowest representation in the nursing workforce?",
        "Choice 1": "Hispanics",
        "Choice 2": "African Americans",
        "Choice 3": "Asians",
        "Choice 4": "American Indians",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "691",
        "Question": "Which of the following would most likely contribute to low recruitment and retention rates for underrepresented groups?",
        "Choice 1": "Ready access to advanced preparation in the natural sciences",
        "Choice 2": "Adequately developed reading and writing skills",
        "Choice 3": "Increased economic advantages",
        "Choice 4": "Increased risk of inferior preparatory education",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "692",
        "Question": "When describing the various factors associated with the retention of minority students, which of the following would be of least importance?",
        "Choice 1": "Financial support",
        "Choice 2": "Secondary educational preparation",
        "Choice 3": "Social adjustment",
        "Choice 4": "Degree level of the program",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "693",
        "Question": "A student who is applying for a Nursing Workforce Diversity (NWD) grant must demonstrate which of the following?",
        "Choice 1": "Cultural sensitivity for others",
        "Choice 2": "Educationally disadvantaged background",
        "Choice 3": "Adequate financial family support",
        "Choice 4": "Participation in a preadmission program",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "694",
        "Question": "When reviewing the most recent data related to the number of men in nursing, which of the following most likely would be noted?",
        "Choice 1": "Remained fairly constant",
        "Choice 2": "Dropped by one half",
        "Choice 3": "Almost quadrupled",
        "Choice 4": "Increased by just under 6%",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "695",
        "Question": "Which of the following ethnic professional associations appeared first?",
        "Choice 1": "National Black Nurses Association",
        "Choice 2": "National Association of Hispanic Nurses",
        "Choice 3": "The Philippine Nurses Association of America",
        "Choice 4": "National Alaska Native American Indian Nurses Association",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "696",
        "Question": "After teaching a group of students about the different generations represented in nursing, the instructor confirms that the students demonstrate understanding when they identify which generation as the “digital natives?”",
        "Choice 1": "Baby boomers",
        "Choice 2": "Generation X",
        "Choice 3": "Veteran generation",
        "Choice 4": "Generation Y",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "697",
        "Question": "A student is assigned to research professional organizations for position statements related to diversity in nursing. For which organization would the student have difficulty finding a position statement?",
        "Choice 1": "American Association of Colleges of Nursing (AACN)",
        "Choice 2": "American Nurses Association (ANA)",
        "Choice 3": "American Organization of Nurse Executives (AONE)",
        "Choice 4": "International Council of Nurses (ICN)",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Exam Name": "Proffessional issues",
        "Test Number": "698",
        "Question": "A new graduate, who is 34 years old, has just started working on the nursing unit. From which generation would this nurse be?",
        "Choice 1": "Veteran generation",
        "Choice 2": "Baby boomer",
        "Choice 3": "Generation X",
        "Choice 4": "Generation Y",
        "Type": "Single",
        "Answer": "3"
    }
]